{
  "name": "JPDB 10K",
  "cards": [
  {
    "question": "混じり",
    "answer": "まじり",
    "meaning": "mixed, mingled"
  },
  {
    "question": "後回し",
    "answer": "あとまわし",
    "meaning": "putting off, postponing"
  },
  {
    "question": "徹底",
    "answer": "てってい",
    "meaning": "thoroughness, completeness, consistency, thorough enforcement, seeing to it that a policy, etc. is c"
  },
  {
    "question": "欲求",
    "answer": "よっきゅう",
    "meaning": "desire, want, will, wish, urge, craving"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚ろ",
    "answer": "うつろ",
    "meaning": "cavity, hollow, void, hollow (voice, smile, etc.), blank (eyes, look, etc.), vacant (expression, sta"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠目",
    "answer": "とおめ",
    "meaning": "distant view, looking from a distance, good long distance vision, farsightedness"
  },
  {
    "question": "籠",
    "answer": "かご,ろう",
    "meaning": "basket (shopping, etc.), hamper, cage, prison, jail, gaol, firm, solid, strong"
  },
  {
    "question": "叔父",
    "answer": "おじ,しゅくふ,おとおじ",
    "meaning": "uncle, uncle (one's father's younger brother)"
  },
  {
    "question": "度胸",
    "answer": "どきょう",
    "meaning": "courage, bravery, pluck, nerve, grit, guts"
  },
  {
    "question": "万能",
    "answer": "ばんのう,まんのう",
    "meaning": "all-purpose, utility, universal, all-powerful, almighty, omnipotent, all-round (e.g. athlete)"
  },
  {
    "question": "孤児院",
    "answer": "こじいん",
    "meaning": "orphanage"
  },
  {
    "question": "重量",
    "answer": "じゅうりょう",
    "meaning": "weight, heavyweight boxer"
  },
  {
    "question": "無人",
    "answer": "むじん,ぶにん,むにん",
    "meaning": "unmanned, uninhabited, unattended, deserted, shorthandedness, lack of help"
  },
  {
    "question": "緩い",
    "answer": "ぬるい,ゆるい",
    "meaning": "lenient, loose, lax, gentle (curve, slope, etc.), slow, weak, soft, not firm, difficult, hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "手出し",
    "answer": "てだし",
    "meaning": "meddling, interfering, choosing to keep the drawn tile and discarding a different one"
  },
  {
    "question": "見計らう",
    "answer": "みはからう",
    "meaning": "to choose at one's own discretion, to choose when to do something, to estimate (the time for somethi"
  },
  {
    "question": "退ける",
    "answer": "しりぞける,のける,どける",
    "meaning": "to repel, to drive away, to repulse, to reject, to put something out of the way, to move (something,"
  },
  {
    "question": "開放",
    "answer": "かいほう",
    "meaning": "opening (a door, window, etc.), leaving open, opening up (e.g. to the public), allowing (public) acc"
  },
  {
    "question": "羞恥",
    "answer": "しゅうち",
    "meaning": "shyness, bashfulness, shame"
  },
  {
    "question": "語",
    "answer": "ご,かたり",
    "meaning": "language, word, talk, recital, narration, topic"
  },
  {
    "question": "失態",
    "answer": "しったい",
    "meaning": "blunder, fault, error, mistake, failure, disgrace"
  },
  {
    "question": "向上",
    "answer": "こうじょう",
    "meaning": "elevation, rise, improvement, advancement, progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚しい",
    "answer": "むなしい",
    "meaning": "empty, void, vacant, vain, fruitless, futile, ineffective, lifeless"
  },
  {
    "question": "見て取る",
    "answer": "みてとる",
    "meaning": "to perceive, to grasp (the situation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "婚姻",
    "answer": "こんいん",
    "meaning": "marriage, matrimony"
  },
  {
    "question": "今晩",
    "answer": "こんばん",
    "meaning": "tonight, this evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻で笑う",
    "answer": "はなでわらう",
    "meaning": "to laugh scornfully"
  },
  {
    "question": "経験値",
    "answer": "けいけんち",
    "meaning": "amount of experience, experience point (in video games, etc.), exp, XP"
  },
  {
    "question": "定番",
    "answer": "ていばん,じょうばん",
    "meaning": "standard, routine, regular, basic, staple, standing guard, watchman, watchman at the shogun's palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "有無",
    "answer": "うむ,ゆうむ",
    "meaning": "existence or nonexistence, presence or absence, consent or refusal, yes or no"
  },
  {
    "question": "鱗",
    "answer": "うろこ,こけ,こけら",
    "meaning": "scale (of fish, snake, etc.), serif (on kana or kanji (e.g. in Mincho font))"
  },
  {
    "question": "柵",
    "answer": "さく,しがらみ,き",
    "meaning": "fence, paling, railing, fortress, weir, bonds, fetters, ties of obligation, fortress (surrounded by"
  },
  {
    "question": "濃厚",
    "answer": "のうこう",
    "meaning": "rich (in flavor, color, smell, etc.), thick, dense, strong, very likely, highly possible, passionate"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り離す",
    "answer": "きりはなす",
    "meaning": "to detach, to decapitate, to cut loose, to let loose, to dismember"
  },
  {
    "question": "光を放つ",
    "answer": "ひかりをはなつ",
    "meaning": "to shed light, to cast light"
  },
  {
    "question": "人手",
    "answer": "ひとで",
    "meaning": "starfish, sea star, asteroid, any echinoderm of the class Asteroidea, northern Pacific seastar (Aste"
  },
  {
    "question": "余韻",
    "answer": "よいん",
    "meaning": "reverberation, swelling (of a hymn), trailing note, lingering memory, aftertaste, suggestiveness (of"
  },
  {
    "question": "足跡",
    "answer": "あしあと,そくせき",
    "meaning": "footprints, record of page visitors (e.g. in social networking sites)"
  },
  {
    "question": "知性",
    "answer": "ちせい",
    "meaning": "intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "償う",
    "answer": "つぐなう,つぐのう",
    "meaning": "to make up for, to compensate for, to indemnify, to recompense, to redeem (e.g. a fault), to atone f"
  },
  {
    "question": "平等",
    "answer": "びょうどう",
    "meaning": "equality, impartiality, evenness"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕切る",
    "answer": "しきる",
    "meaning": "to partition, to divide, to mark off, to direct, to manage, to run, to organize, to take responsibil"
  },
  {
    "question": "所有",
    "answer": "しょゆう",
    "meaning": "one's possessions, ownership"
  },
  {
    "question": "計る",
    "answer": "はかる",
    "meaning": "to measure, to weigh, to survey, to time (sound, gauge, estimate), to conjecture, to infer, to surmi"
  },
  {
    "question": "無難",
    "answer": "ぶなん",
    "meaning": "safe (e.g. choice), secure, innocuous, inoffensive, acceptable, passable, satisfactory, adequate, fa"
  },
  {
    "question": "集まり",
    "answer": "あつまり",
    "meaning": "gathering, meeting, assembly, collection, attendance"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗っ取る",
    "answer": "のっとる",
    "meaning": "to take over, to capture, to seize, to commandeer, to occupy, to usurp, to hijack (vehicle, account,"
  },
  {
    "question": "気の毒",
    "answer": "きのどく",
    "meaning": "pitiful, unfortunate, poor, miserable, wretched, unpardonable, regrettable"
  },
  {
    "question": "無くす",
    "answer": "なくす",
    "meaning": "to lose (something), to mislay, to get rid of, to eliminate, to remove"
  },
  {
    "question": "科",
    "answer": "か,しな,とが",
    "meaning": "department, section, faculty, school, arm, course (of study), branch of study, specialization, (taxo"
  },
  {
    "question": "機体",
    "answer": "きたい",
    "meaning": "fuselage, airframe"
  },
  {
    "question": "奪い取る",
    "answer": "うばいとる",
    "meaning": "to plunder, to grab, to snatch"
  },
  {
    "question": "住まう",
    "answer": "すまう",
    "meaning": "to live, to reside, to inhabit"
  },
  {
    "question": "埋もれる",
    "answer": "うもれる,うずもれる,うづもれる",
    "meaning": "to be buried, to be covered, to be hidden"
  },
  {
    "question": "動じる",
    "answer": "どうじる",
    "meaning": "to be perturbed, to be agitated"
  },
  {
    "question": "出血",
    "answer": "しゅっけつ",
    "meaning": "bleeding, haemorrhage, hemorrhage, bleeding money, red ink, selling below cost"
  },
  {
    "question": "集落",
    "answer": "しゅうらく",
    "meaning": "settlement, village, community, town, (bacterial) colony"
  },
  {
    "question": "偵察",
    "answer": "ていさつ",
    "meaning": "scouting, reconnaissance"
  },
  {
    "question": "表向き",
    "answer": "おもてむき",
    "meaning": "outward appearance, ostensible, public, official"
  },
  {
    "question": "納める",
    "answer": "おさめる",
    "meaning": "to dedicate, to make an offering, to pay (fees), to supply, to store, to finish, to bring to a close"
  },
  {
    "question": "艶やか",
    "answer": "あでやか,つややか",
    "meaning": "glamorous, charming, beguiling, bewitching, beautiful, fascinatingly elegant, glossy (e.g. hair), sl"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕日",
    "answer": "ゆうひ,せきじつ",
    "meaning": "evening sun, setting sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "威厳",
    "answer": "いげん",
    "meaning": "dignity, majesty, solemnity, gravity"
  },
  {
    "question": "華麗",
    "answer": "かれい",
    "meaning": "splendid, magnificent, gorgeous"
  },
  {
    "question": "長身",
    "answer": "ちょうしん",
    "meaning": "tall figure, high stature"
  },
  {
    "question": "介入",
    "answer": "かいにゅう",
    "meaning": "intervention"
  },
  {
    "question": "根本的",
    "answer": "こんぽんてき",
    "meaning": "fundamental, basic"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺する",
    "answer": "ゆする",
    "meaning": "to shake, to jolt, to rock (cradle), to swing, to blackmail, to extort, to shake down"
  },
  {
    "question": "高位",
    "answer": "こうい",
    "meaning": "dignity, eminent, high ranking, high-order (digit, bit, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "占い",
    "answer": "うらない",
    "meaning": "fortune-telling, divination"
  },
  {
    "question": "強気",
    "answer": "つよき,ごうぎ,ごうき",
    "meaning": "confident, assured, self-assured, firm, strong, cocksure, bullish (e.g. market), great, grand, obsti"
  },
  {
    "question": "出力",
    "answer": "しゅつりょく",
    "meaning": "output (electrical, signal, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "態勢",
    "answer": "たいせい",
    "meaning": "attitude, posture, preparedness, readiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "深まる",
    "answer": "ふかまる",
    "meaning": "to deepen, to heighten, to intensify"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀髪",
    "answer": "ぎんぱつ",
    "meaning": "silver hair, gray hair, grey hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "前線",
    "answer": "ぜんせん",
    "meaning": "(weather) front, front line, forward area, action zone"
  },
  {
    "question": "委員",
    "answer": "いいん",
    "meaning": "committee member"
  },
  {
    "question": "心境",
    "answer": "しんきょう",
    "meaning": "state of mind, mental state, mental attitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "破裂",
    "answer": "はれつ",
    "meaning": "explosion, rupture, break off"
  },
  {
    "question": "課",
    "answer": "か",
    "meaning": "lesson, section (in an organization), division, department, counter for lessons and chapters (of a b"
  },
  {
    "question": "同等",
    "answer": "どうとう",
    "meaning": "equality, equal, same rights, same rank, equivalence"
  },
  {
    "question": "予言",
    "answer": "よげん,かねごと",
    "meaning": "prediction, prophecy, prognostication, promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "業務",
    "answer": "ぎょうむ",
    "meaning": "business, affairs, duties, work, procedure, task, action, function, (business) operations, operation"
  },
  {
    "question": "実在",
    "answer": "じつざい",
    "meaning": "actual existence, real existence, existing in real life"
  },
  {
    "question": "打撃",
    "answer": "だげき",
    "meaning": "blow, shock, strike, damage, batting"
  },
  {
    "question": "連れ去る",
    "answer": "つれさる",
    "meaning": "to take (someone) away, to carry off, to abduct, to kidnap"
  },
  {
    "question": "透ける",
    "answer": "すける",
    "meaning": "to be transparent, to show through"
  },
  {
    "question": "緩やか",
    "answer": "ゆるやか",
    "meaning": "loose, slack, gentle (slope, curve), slow (speed), lenient, liberal, lax"
  },
  {
    "question": "手を組む",
    "answer": "てをくむ",
    "meaning": "to join hands together, to join forces, to collaborate"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆け込む",
    "answer": "かけこむ",
    "meaning": "to run into, to rush into, to (run and) seek refuge in, to take shelter in"
  },
  {
    "question": "読書",
    "answer": "どくしょ,とくしょ",
    "meaning": "reading (books)"
  },
  {
    "question": "飢える",
    "answer": "うえる,かつえる",
    "meaning": "to starve, to be famished, to be hungry, to be starved of (e.g. love), to be thirsty for (e.g. knowl"
  },
  {
    "question": "屍",
    "answer": "しかばね,かばね,し",
    "meaning": "corpse, kanji 'corpse' radical"
  },
  {
    "question": "見過ごす",
    "answer": "みすごす",
    "meaning": "to let go by, to let pass, to overlook, to miss"
  },
  {
    "question": "責任者",
    "answer": "せきにんしゃ",
    "meaning": "person in charge (including a supervisory role for other staff), person responsible for ..., respons"
  },
  {
    "question": "観光",
    "answer": "かんこう",
    "meaning": "sightseeing, tourism"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り除く",
    "answer": "とりのぞく",
    "meaning": "to remove, to deinstall, to take away, to set apart"
  },
  {
    "question": "遂げる",
    "answer": "とげる",
    "meaning": "to accomplish, to achieve, to carry out, to arrive at (a certain outcome), to come to, to end with"
  },
  {
    "question": "官",
    "answer": "かん,つかさ",
    "meaning": "government service, the bureaucracy, office, official, chief, head"
  },
  {
    "question": "積もる",
    "answer": "つもる",
    "meaning": "to pile up, to accumulate, to estimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "警戒心",
    "answer": "けいかいしん",
    "meaning": "wariness"
  },
  {
    "question": "沸く",
    "answer": "わく",
    "meaning": "to grow hot (e.g. water), to boil, to get excited (at), to erupt (in applause, cheering, etc.), to b"
  },
  {
    "question": "低下",
    "answer": "ていか",
    "meaning": "fall, decline, lowering, deterioration, degradation"
  },
  {
    "question": "同い年",
    "answer": "おないどし",
    "meaning": "the same age"
  },
  {
    "question": "死人",
    "answer": "しにん,しびと",
    "meaning": "corpse, dead person"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞き覚え",
    "answer": "ききおぼえ",
    "meaning": "learning by ear, memory of having heard something before"
  },
  {
    "question": "陽気",
    "answer": "ようき",
    "meaning": "cheerful, jovial, merry, lively, weather, season, spirit of yang"
  },
  {
    "question": "現地",
    "answer": "げんち",
    "meaning": "actual place, local, on-site"
  },
  {
    "question": "人員",
    "answer": "じんいん",
    "meaning": "number of persons, personnel"
  },
  {
    "question": "口々",
    "answer": "くちぐち",
    "meaning": "every person, every mouth, every entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "長引く",
    "answer": "ながびく",
    "meaning": "to be prolonged, to drag on"
  },
  {
    "question": "一帯",
    "answer": "いったい",
    "meaning": "whole area, whole region, stretch (of land), tract, belt, zone"
  },
  {
    "question": "途絶える",
    "answer": "とだえる",
    "meaning": "to stop, to cease, to come to an end, to cut off"
  },
  {
    "question": "理",
    "answer": "り,ことわり",
    "meaning": "reason, principle, logic, general principle (as opposed to individual concrete phenomenon), (in neo-"
  },
  {
    "question": "公開",
    "answer": "こうかい",
    "meaning": "opening to the public, making available to the public, putting on display, exhibiting, showing (play"
  },
  {
    "question": "装着",
    "answer": "そうちゃく",
    "meaning": "equipping, installing, fitting, mounting, putting on"
  },
  {
    "question": "艦",
    "answer": "かん",
    "meaning": "warship"
  },
  {
    "question": "昼寝",
    "answer": "ひるね",
    "meaning": "nap (afternoon), siesta"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し出す",
    "answer": "おしだす",
    "meaning": "to crowd out, to push out, to squeeze out, to start together, to set out en masse, to highlight, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "各国",
    "answer": "かっこく,かくこく",
    "meaning": "each nation, many nations, many countries"
  },
  {
    "question": "小走り",
    "answer": "こばしり",
    "meaning": "trot, half run, jog, girl in charge of menial tasks in a samurai family"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽々",
    "answer": "かるがる,かろがろ,けいけい",
    "meaning": "lightly, easily, carelessly, indiscreetly, thoughtlessly, frivolously"
  },
  {
    "question": "都会",
    "answer": "とかい",
    "meaning": "city, Tokyo Metropolitan Assembly"
  },
  {
    "question": "衛兵",
    "answer": "えいへい",
    "meaning": "guard, sentinel, garrison"
  },
  {
    "question": "体育",
    "answer": "たいいく,たいく",
    "meaning": "physical education, PE, gym (class)"
  },
  {
    "question": "解析",
    "answer": "かいせき",
    "meaning": "analysis, analytical study, parsing, parse"
  },
  {
    "question": "特化",
    "answer": "とっか",
    "meaning": "specialization, specialisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "務め",
    "answer": "つとめ",
    "meaning": "service, duty, business, responsibility, task, Buddhist religious services"
  },
  {
    "question": "済ます",
    "answer": "すます",
    "meaning": "to finish, to get it over with, to conclude, to settle, to pay back, to get along (without something"
  },
  {
    "question": "当分",
    "answer": "とうぶん",
    "meaning": "for the present, for the time being, for a while, for some time"
  },
  {
    "question": "承諾",
    "answer": "しょうだく",
    "meaning": "consent, approval, acceptance, agreement, compliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹部",
    "answer": "ふくぶ",
    "meaning": "abdomen"
  },
  {
    "question": "妥当",
    "answer": "だとう",
    "meaning": "valid, proper, right, appropriate, reasonable"
  },
  {
    "question": "嫌悪",
    "answer": "けんお",
    "meaning": "disgust, hate, repugnance, loathing"
  },
  {
    "question": "城壁",
    "answer": "じょうへき",
    "meaning": "rampart, castle walls"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜会",
    "answer": "やかい",
    "meaning": "evening party"
  },
  {
    "question": "借り",
    "answer": "かり",
    "meaning": "borrowing, debt, loan"
  },
  {
    "question": "怠る",
    "answer": "おこたる",
    "meaning": "to be negligent in doing something, to shirk, to be off one's guard"
  },
  {
    "question": "報う",
    "answer": "むくう",
    "meaning": "to reward, to recompense, to repay, to retaliate, to get revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "年寄り",
    "answer": "としより",
    "meaning": "old person, elderly person, senior citizen, trustee of the Japan Sumo Association, retired high-rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮",
    "answer": "みや,きゅう",
    "meaning": "shrine, palace, imperial residence, Imperial prince, Imperial princess, headboard with built-in shel"
  },
  {
    "question": "一環",
    "answer": "いっかん",
    "meaning": "link (e.g. in a chain of events), part (of a plan, campaign, activities, etc.), monocyclic"
  },
  {
    "question": "必須",
    "answer": "ひっす,ひっしゅ,ひっすう",
    "meaning": "indispensable, essential, requisite, required, compulsory, necessary"
  },
  {
    "question": "奉仕",
    "answer": "ほうし",
    "meaning": "service, ministry, attendance, church work, offering goods at a reduced price, providing a service f"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺れ",
    "answer": "ゆれ",
    "meaning": "shaking, shake, jolt, jolting, vibration, tremor, flickering, unsettledness, instability, vacillatin"
  },
  {
    "question": "諭す",
    "answer": "さとす",
    "meaning": "to admonish, to persuade, to warn, to remonstrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "出歩く",
    "answer": "であるく",
    "meaning": "to go out, to go around, to walk about, to roam"
  },
  {
    "question": "繰り返し",
    "answer": "くりかえし",
    "meaning": "repetition, repeat, reiteration, iteration, refrain, cycle, repeatedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き戻す",
    "answer": "ひきもどす",
    "meaning": "to bring back, to restore"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠かす",
    "answer": "かかす",
    "meaning": "to miss (doing), to fail (to do)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮮明",
    "answer": "せんめい",
    "meaning": "vivid, clear, distinct"
  },
  {
    "question": "気温",
    "answer": "きおん",
    "meaning": "air temperature"
  },
  {
    "question": "所へ",
    "answer": "ところへ",
    "meaning": "thereupon, shortly thereafter"
  },
  {
    "question": "侵攻",
    "answer": "しんこう",
    "meaning": "invasion"
  },
  {
    "question": "残骸",
    "answer": "ざんがい",
    "meaning": "ruins, wreckage, wreck, broken remains, debris"
  },
  {
    "question": "推薦",
    "answer": "すいせん",
    "meaning": "recommendation, referral, endorsement"
  },
  {
    "question": "右側",
    "answer": "みぎがわ,うそく",
    "meaning": "right side, right-hand side"
  },
  {
    "question": "喘ぐ",
    "answer": "あえぐ",
    "meaning": "to gasp, to pant, to breathe hard, to suffer, to struggle"
  },
  {
    "question": "丈夫",
    "answer": "じょうぶ,じょうふ,ますらお",
    "meaning": "healthy, robust, strong, solid, durable, hero, manly person, warrior"
  },
  {
    "question": "見惚れる",
    "answer": "みとれる,みほれる",
    "meaning": "to be fascinated (by), to be captivated by, to be enchanted by, to gaze admiringly at, to watch in f"
  },
  {
    "question": "大金",
    "answer": "たいきん,おおがね",
    "meaning": "large amount of money, great cost"
  },
  {
    "question": "意図的",
    "answer": "いとてき",
    "meaning": "intentional, on purpose"
  },
  {
    "question": "咥える",
    "answer": "くわえる",
    "meaning": "to hold in one's mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "彩る",
    "answer": "いろどる",
    "meaning": "to colour, to color, to paint, to apply make-up, to decorate, to garnish, to adorn, to add flair"
  },
  {
    "question": "大気",
    "answer": "たいき",
    "meaning": "atmosphere, air, magnanimity, generosity"
  },
  {
    "question": "野球",
    "answer": "やきゅう",
    "meaning": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "question": "反則",
    "answer": "はんそく",
    "meaning": "foul play (sport), breaking the rules, infringement, irregularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "体質",
    "answer": "たいしつ",
    "meaning": "constitution (physical), physical make-up, predisposition (to disease), disposition, tendency, chara"
  },
  {
    "question": "果てる",
    "answer": "はてる",
    "meaning": "to end, to be finished, to be exhausted, to die, to perish, to do utterly, to do completely"
  },
  {
    "question": "大層",
    "answer": "たいそう",
    "meaning": "very, extremely, exceedingly, greatly, terribly, extreme, excessive, great many, large number of, sp"
  },
  {
    "question": "半端",
    "answer": "はんぱ",
    "meaning": "remnant, fragment, incomplete set, incompleteness, fraction, odd sum, halfway, half-hearted, perfunc"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅い",
    "answer": "かたい",
    "meaning": "hard, solid, tough, stiff, tight, wooden, unpolished (e.g. writing), strong, firm (not viscous or ea"
  },
  {
    "question": "障壁",
    "answer": "しょうへき",
    "meaning": "enclosing wall, boundary fence, obstacle, barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "攫う",
    "answer": "さらう",
    "meaning": "to carry off, to run away with, to sweep away, to snatch, to kidnap, to abduct, to take entirely for"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳",
    "answer": "ちち,ち",
    "meaning": "milk, breast, loop, decorative bump (on a hanging bell)"
  },
  {
    "question": "同調",
    "answer": "どうちょう",
    "meaning": "sympathy, agreement with, alignment, conformity, tuning"
  },
  {
    "question": "強者",
    "answer": "きょうしゃ,つわもの",
    "meaning": "strong person, the strong, the powerful, warrior, soldier, courageous person"
  },
  {
    "question": "不可解",
    "answer": "ふかかい",
    "meaning": "incomprehensible, mysterious, inexplicable, inscrutable, enigmatic, baffling"
  },
  {
    "question": "賛同",
    "answer": "さんどう",
    "meaning": "approval, endorsement"
  },
  {
    "question": "片付く",
    "answer": "かたづく",
    "meaning": "to be put in order, to be put to rights, to be disposed of, to be solved, to be finished, to be marr"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡くす",
    "answer": "なくす",
    "meaning": "to lose (through death) (e.g. wife, child)"
  },
  {
    "question": "本命",
    "answer": "ほんめい",
    "meaning": "favorite (to win), favourite, likely winner, one's heart's desire, first choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "直し",
    "answer": "なおし",
    "meaning": "correction, rectification, mending, repair"
  },
  {
    "question": "手順",
    "answer": "てじゅん",
    "meaning": "process, procedure, sequence, protocol, instruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑",
    "answer": "ざつ,ぞう",
    "meaning": "rough, crude, sloppy, messy, miscellaneous, miscellany (classification of Japanese poetry unrelated"
  },
  {
    "question": "補う",
    "answer": "おぎなう",
    "meaning": "to supplement, to make up for, to compensate for, to cover (a shortage, loss, etc.), to fill (e.g. a"
  },
  {
    "question": "見比べる",
    "answer": "みくらべる",
    "meaning": "to compare with the eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "速やか",
    "answer": "すみやか",
    "meaning": "quick, speedy, prompt, rapid, swift"
  },
  {
    "question": "尋問",
    "answer": "じんもん",
    "meaning": "questioning, interrogation, examination (of a witness)"
  },
  {
    "question": "校内",
    "answer": "こうない",
    "meaning": "within a school"
  },
  {
    "question": "警官",
    "answer": "けいかん",
    "meaning": "police officer, policeman, constable"
  },
  {
    "question": "炸裂",
    "answer": "さくれつ",
    "meaning": "violent explosion, bursting"
  },
  {
    "question": "実績",
    "answer": "じっせき",
    "meaning": "achievements, actual results, accomplishments, past results, track record"
  },
  {
    "question": "一分",
    "answer": "いちぶ,いちぶん,いっぷん",
    "meaning": "one tenth, one hundredth, one percent, one tenth of a sun, one quarter ryō (an old coin), duty, hono"
  },
  {
    "question": "落胆",
    "answer": "らくたん",
    "meaning": "discouragement, despondency, dejection, disappointment"
  },
  {
    "question": "村長",
    "answer": "そんちょう,むらおさ",
    "meaning": "village headman, village mayor"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾つか",
    "answer": "いくつか",
    "meaning": "(a) few, some, several"
  },
  {
    "question": "適切",
    "answer": "てきせつ",
    "meaning": "appropriate, suitable, fitting, apt, proper, right, pertinent, relevant"
  },
  {
    "question": "奏でる",
    "answer": "かなでる",
    "meaning": "to play an instrument (esp. string instruments), to dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "下品",
    "answer": "げひん",
    "meaning": "vulgar, indecent, coarse, crude"
  },
  {
    "question": "反転",
    "answer": "はんてん",
    "meaning": "rolling over, turning over, turning around (the other way), reversal (of direction, course, etc.), i"
  },
  {
    "question": "形相",
    "answer": "ぎょうそう,けいそう",
    "meaning": "look (esp. an angry or upset look), expression, form (esp. in Aristotelian philosophy)"
  },
  {
    "question": "会釈",
    "answer": "えしゃく",
    "meaning": "slight bow (as a greeting or sign of gratitude), nod, salutation, consideration, thoughtfulness"
  },
  {
    "question": "独占",
    "answer": "どくせん",
    "meaning": "monopoly, monopolization, exclusivity, hogging, keeping to oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "越す",
    "answer": "こす",
    "meaning": "to cross over (e.g. mountain), to go across, to get over (e.g. hardship), to pass time (e.g. a winte"
  },
  {
    "question": "新作",
    "answer": "しんさく",
    "meaning": "new work, new production"
  },
  {
    "question": "人殺し",
    "answer": "ひとごろし",
    "meaning": "murder, murderer"
  },
  {
    "question": "火事",
    "answer": "かじ",
    "meaning": "fire, conflagration"
  },
  {
    "question": "翻弄",
    "answer": "ほんろう",
    "meaning": "trifling with, toying with, playing with, making sport of, making fun of, leading around by the nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "衣",
    "answer": "ころも,きぬ,い",
    "meaning": "clothes, garment, gown, robe, coating (e.g. glaze, batter, icing), clothing, dress"
  },
  {
    "question": "章",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "chapter, section, medal, badge, insignia"
  },
  {
    "question": "追求",
    "answer": "ついきゅう",
    "meaning": "pursuit (of a goal, ideal, etc.), search, chase, seeking after"
  },
  {
    "question": "進展",
    "answer": "しんてん",
    "meaning": "progress, development"
  },
  {
    "question": "膣",
    "answer": "ちつ",
    "meaning": "vagina"
  },
  {
    "question": "挿入",
    "answer": "そうにゅう",
    "meaning": "insertion, incorporation, infixing"
  },
  {
    "question": "各々",
    "answer": "おのおの",
    "meaning": "each, you (plural)"
  },
  {
    "question": "共感",
    "answer": "きょうかん",
    "meaning": "sympathy, empathy, response"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き出し",
    "answer": "ひきだし",
    "meaning": "drawer, withdrawal (of money from an account), variety of knowledge and experience useful for handli"
  },
  {
    "question": "帝都",
    "answer": "ていと",
    "meaning": "imperial capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "毎朝",
    "answer": "まいあさ,まいちょう",
    "meaning": "every morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "物凄い",
    "answer": "ものすごい",
    "meaning": "terrific, staggering, tremendous, incredible, extreme, frightful, ghastly, horrific, terrible, awful"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠し事",
    "answer": "かくしごと,かくしこと",
    "meaning": "secret, secrecy"
  },
  {
    "question": "砲",
    "answer": "じゅう,ほう",
    "meaning": "gun, rifle, small arms, cannon, artillery, ordnance"
  },
  {
    "question": "先行",
    "answer": "せんこう",
    "meaning": "preceding, going first, leading, going ahead, taking priority"
  },
  {
    "question": "当の",
    "answer": "とうの",
    "meaning": "the ... in question"
  },
  {
    "question": "羊",
    "answer": "ひつじ",
    "meaning": "sheep (Ovis aries)"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣伝",
    "answer": "せんでん",
    "meaning": "publicity, advertisement, advertising, propaganda"
  },
  {
    "question": "直る",
    "answer": "なおる",
    "meaning": "to get mended, to be repaired, to be fixed, to return to normal, to recover (e.g. one's temper), to"
  },
  {
    "question": "作用",
    "answer": "さよう",
    "meaning": "action, operation, effect, function"
  },
  {
    "question": "有る",
    "answer": "ある",
    "meaning": "to be, to exist, to live, to have, to be located, to be equipped with, to happen, to come about"
  },
  {
    "question": "夫妻",
    "answer": "ふさい",
    "meaning": "husband and wife, married couple"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗り切る",
    "answer": "のりきる",
    "meaning": "to weather (a storm, rough seas), to ride across, to sail across, to get through (adversity), to wea"
  },
  {
    "question": "出世",
    "answer": "しゅっせ",
    "meaning": "success in life, getting ahead, successful career, promotion, climbing the corporate ladder, eminenc"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち寄る",
    "answer": "たちよる",
    "meaning": "to stop by, to drop in for a short visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬱陶しい",
    "answer": "うっとうしい,うっとおしい",
    "meaning": "gloomy (e.g. mood), depressing, irritating, troublesome, heavy (weather), cloudy"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶器",
    "answer": "きょうき",
    "meaning": "dangerous weapon, lethal weapon, deadly weapon, murder weapon"
  },
  {
    "question": "経由",
    "answer": "けいゆ,けいゆう",
    "meaning": "going through, going via, going by way of"
  },
  {
    "question": "問答無用",
    "answer": "もんどうむよう",
    "meaning": "there being no use in arguing (about it)"
  },
  {
    "question": "信念",
    "answer": "しんねん",
    "meaning": "belief, faith, conviction"
  },
  {
    "question": "匹敵",
    "answer": "ひってき",
    "meaning": "to be a match for, to rival, to equal, to compare with, to be equivalent to"
  },
  {
    "question": "作家",
    "answer": "さっか",
    "meaning": "author, writer, novelist, artist"
  },
  {
    "question": "費やす",
    "answer": "ついやす",
    "meaning": "to spend, to expend, to consume, to waste, to squander, to throw away, to devote"
  },
  {
    "question": "順に",
    "answer": "じゅんに",
    "meaning": "in order, in turn, one by one"
  },
  {
    "question": "徹夜",
    "answer": "てつや",
    "meaning": "staying up all night"
  },
  {
    "question": "寒気",
    "answer": "さむけ,かんき",
    "meaning": "chill, the shivers, shivering fit, cold, coldness, cold air"
  },
  {
    "question": "神話",
    "answer": "しんわ",
    "meaning": "myth, legend"
  },
  {
    "question": "覚める",
    "answer": "さめる",
    "meaning": "to wake, to wake up, to become sober, to sober up, to regain consciousness (e.g. after anaesthesia),"
  },
  {
    "question": "強敵",
    "answer": "きょうてき",
    "meaning": "formidable enemy, strong enemy, tough enemy"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち歩く",
    "answer": "もちあるく",
    "meaning": "to carry around, to carry on one's person"
  },
  {
    "question": "抱え込む",
    "answer": "かかえこむ",
    "meaning": "to hold a thing in one's arms, to carry in one's arms, to embrace (e.g. a baby), to take upon onesel"
  },
  {
    "question": "疑惑",
    "answer": "ぎわく",
    "meaning": "doubt, misgivings, distrust, suspicion"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛液",
    "answer": "あいえき",
    "meaning": "genital secretions, sexual fluids, semen, cum"
  },
  {
    "question": "保健室",
    "answer": "ほけんしつ",
    "meaning": "school infirmary"
  },
  {
    "question": "坊主",
    "answer": "ぼうず",
    "meaning": "Buddhist priest, bonze, close-cropped hair, crew cut, person with a shorn head, boy, sonny, lad, not"
  },
  {
    "question": "防具",
    "answer": "ぼうぐ",
    "meaning": "guard, protector, defensive armament, personal armor (armour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "占める",
    "answer": "しめる",
    "meaning": "to occupy, to hold, to account for, to make up, to take up"
  },
  {
    "question": "自称",
    "answer": "じしょう",
    "meaning": "self-proclaimed, self-professed, self-styled, would-be, professing oneself to be, calling oneself, d"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃げ場",
    "answer": "にげば",
    "meaning": "refuge, escape"
  },
  {
    "question": "変換",
    "answer": "へんかん",
    "meaning": "change, conversion, transformation"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪快",
    "answer": "ごうかい",
    "meaning": "hearty, tremendous, magnificent, glorious, splendid, heroic, stirring"
  },
  {
    "question": "転校",
    "answer": "てんこう",
    "meaning": "changing schools"
  },
  {
    "question": "当事者",
    "answer": "とうじしゃ",
    "meaning": "person concerned, interested party, related party"
  },
  {
    "question": "気安い",
    "answer": "きやすい",
    "meaning": "relaxed, familiar, easy to access, friendly"
  },
  {
    "question": "悲痛",
    "answer": "ひつう",
    "meaning": "grief, sorrow, extreme sadness, heartbreak"
  },
  {
    "question": "皆殺し",
    "answer": "みなごろし",
    "meaning": "massacre, annihilation, wholesale slaughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "成り行き",
    "answer": "なりゆき",
    "meaning": "course (of events), development, progress, outcome, result, market order, order without limit"
  },
  {
    "question": "授ける",
    "answer": "さずける",
    "meaning": "to grant, to give, to confer, to award, to teach, to instruct, to impart (knowledge)"
  },
  {
    "question": "違反",
    "answer": "いはん,いへん",
    "meaning": "violation, offense, offence, breach, transgression, infringement, contravention, breaking (a contrac"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽器",
    "answer": "がっき",
    "meaning": "musical instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "系統",
    "answer": "けいとう",
    "meaning": "system, lineage, ancestry, family line, group (e.g. of colors) (colours), family (e.g. of languages)"
  },
  {
    "question": "肺",
    "answer": "はい",
    "meaning": "lung"
  },
  {
    "question": "正反対",
    "answer": "せいはんたい",
    "meaning": "exactly opposite (of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "四方",
    "answer": "しほう,よも,よほう",
    "meaning": "the four cardinal directions, north, east, south and west, all directions, surroundings, many countr"
  },
  {
    "question": "工夫",
    "answer": "くふう,こうふ",
    "meaning": "scheme, device, scheming, devising, figuring out, coming up with, solving ingeniously, dedication to"
  },
  {
    "question": "一滴",
    "answer": "いってき,ひとしずく",
    "meaning": "drop (of fluid)"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭脳",
    "answer": "ずのう",
    "meaning": "head, brains, intellect, understanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "属する",
    "answer": "ぞくする,しょくする",
    "meaning": "to belong to, to come under, to be affiliated with, to be subject to, to entrust, to send (a message"
  },
  {
    "question": "臨む",
    "answer": "のぞむ",
    "meaning": "to look out on, to overlook, to front onto, to face (a situation, crisis, etc.), to meet (e.g. death"
  },
  {
    "question": "無縁",
    "answer": "むえん",
    "meaning": "unrelated, unconnected, irrelevant, indifferent, divorced from, having nothing to do with one, being"
  },
  {
    "question": "長時間",
    "answer": "ちょうじかん",
    "meaning": "long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜群",
    "answer": "ばつぐん,ばっくん",
    "meaning": "outstanding, excellent, exceptional, surpassing, extraordinary, distinguished, preeminence, distinct"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷ややか",
    "answer": "ひややか",
    "meaning": "cold, chilly, cool, cold (attitude, stare, etc.), frigid, indifferent, distant, surly, curt, compose"
  },
  {
    "question": "無責任",
    "answer": "むせきにん",
    "meaning": "irresponsibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "居心地",
    "answer": "いごこち",
    "meaning": "comfort"
  },
  {
    "question": "浸かる",
    "answer": "つかる",
    "meaning": "to be submerged, to be soaked, to be pickled, to be well seasoned, to be totally immersed (in a cond"
  },
  {
    "question": "己が",
    "answer": "おのが",
    "meaning": "my, one's own, I ..., one ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "呼ばわり",
    "answer": "よばわり",
    "meaning": "denouncing, calling (e.g. somebody a thief), branding (as)"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧乏",
    "answer": "びんぼう",
    "meaning": "poverty-stricken, destitute, poor, penurious"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠点",
    "answer": "けってん",
    "meaning": "fault, defect, flaw, weak point, weakness, shortcoming, drawback, failure (in an examination), faili"
  },
  {
    "question": "縋る",
    "answer": "すがる",
    "meaning": "to cling to, to hang onto, to rely on, to depend on, to implore, to entreat"
  },
  {
    "question": "境遇",
    "answer": "きょうぐう",
    "meaning": "one's circumstances, environment, situation (in life)"
  },
  {
    "question": "先週",
    "answer": "せんしゅう",
    "meaning": "last week, the week before"
  },
  {
    "question": "確証",
    "answer": "かくしょう",
    "meaning": "conclusive evidence, positive proof, definite proof, confirmation"
  },
  {
    "question": "横切る",
    "answer": "よこぎる",
    "meaning": "to cross (e.g. road), to traverse"
  },
  {
    "question": "就職",
    "answer": "しゅうしょく",
    "meaning": "finding employment, getting a job"
  },
  {
    "question": "頑固",
    "answer": "がんこ",
    "meaning": "stubborn, obstinate, pigheaded"
  },
  {
    "question": "役者",
    "answer": "やくしゃ",
    "meaning": "actor, actress, man of wits, clever person, cunning fellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "身勝手",
    "answer": "みがって",
    "meaning": "selfish, self-centred, egotistical"
  },
  {
    "question": "接続",
    "answer": "せつぞく",
    "meaning": "connection, attachment, union, join, joint, link, changing trains, conjunction"
  },
  {
    "question": "快い",
    "answer": "こころよい",
    "meaning": "pleasant, agreeable, comfortable, refreshing"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳打ち",
    "answer": "みみうち",
    "meaning": "whispering into a person's ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "囮",
    "answer": "おとり",
    "meaning": "decoy (for hunting), stool, lure, decoy, stool pigeon, trap"
  },
  {
    "question": "学",
    "answer": "がく",
    "meaning": "learning, scholarship, study, erudition, knowledge, education, study of ..., -ology, -ics"
  },
  {
    "question": "手当て",
    "answer": "てあて",
    "meaning": "salary, pay, compensation, allowance (e.g. housing allowance), benefit, bonus, medical care, treatme"
  },
  {
    "question": "撃退",
    "answer": "げきたい",
    "meaning": "repulse, repelling (e.g. the enemy), driving back"
  },
  {
    "question": "月明かり",
    "answer": "つきあかり",
    "meaning": "moonlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜明け",
    "answer": "よあけ",
    "meaning": "dawn, daybreak"
  },
  {
    "question": "境",
    "answer": "さかい,きょう",
    "meaning": "border, boundary, turning point, watershed, area, region, spot, space, environment, psychological st"
  },
  {
    "question": "花嫁",
    "answer": "はなよめ",
    "meaning": "bride"
  },
  {
    "question": "急かす",
    "answer": "せかす",
    "meaning": "to hurry (up), to urge on, to press, to rush"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄越す",
    "answer": "よこす",
    "meaning": "to send, to forward, to hand over (e.g. money)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冊",
    "answer": "さつ,さく",
    "meaning": "counter for books, volume, imperial edict to confer nobility titles (in ancient China)"
  },
  {
    "question": "脈",
    "answer": "みゃく",
    "meaning": "pulse, vein, chain (of mountains, etc.), hope, thread (of an argument)"
  },
  {
    "question": "治安",
    "answer": "ちあん,じあん",
    "meaning": "public order, Jian era (1021.2.2-1024.7.13)"
  },
  {
    "question": "信号",
    "answer": "しんごう",
    "meaning": "signal, signalling, signaling, traffic light, traffic signal"
  },
  {
    "question": "法律",
    "answer": "ほうりつ",
    "meaning": "law"
  },
  {
    "question": "本名",
    "answer": "ほんみょう,ほんめい",
    "meaning": "real name"
  },
  {
    "question": "見合う",
    "answer": "みあう",
    "meaning": "to exchange glances, to correspond, to counterbalance"
  },
  {
    "question": "長男",
    "answer": "ちょうなん",
    "meaning": "eldest son (may be the only son), first-born son"
  },
  {
    "question": "生産",
    "answer": "せいさん,せいざん",
    "meaning": "production, manufacture, live birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "子犬",
    "answer": "こいぬ",
    "meaning": "puppy, small dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "区画",
    "answer": "くかく",
    "meaning": "division, section, compartment, block, plot, lot, partition, boundary"
  },
  {
    "question": "食卓",
    "answer": "しょくたく",
    "meaning": "dining table"
  },
  {
    "question": "負傷",
    "answer": "ふしょう",
    "meaning": "injury, wound"
  },
  {
    "question": "淑女",
    "answer": "しゅくじょ",
    "meaning": "lady"
  },
  {
    "question": "火花",
    "answer": "ひばな",
    "meaning": "spark"
  },
  {
    "question": "広める",
    "answer": "ひろめる",
    "meaning": "to spread, to propagate, to popularize, to disseminate, to broaden, to extend, to widen, to enlarge"
  },
  {
    "question": "園",
    "answer": "その,えん",
    "meaning": "garden (esp. man-made), orchard, park, plantation, place, location"
  },
  {
    "question": "区別",
    "answer": "くべつ",
    "meaning": "distinction, differentiation, classification"
  },
  {
    "question": "封",
    "answer": "ふう",
    "meaning": "seal"
  },
  {
    "question": "公式",
    "answer": "こうしき",
    "meaning": "official, formal, formula (e.g. mathematical), official (social media) account (of a company, organi"
  },
  {
    "question": "裂ける",
    "answer": "さける",
    "meaning": "to split, to tear, to burst, to be separated, to be divided"
  },
  {
    "question": "手応え",
    "answer": "てごたえ",
    "meaning": "response (felt in the hands), resistance, reaction, response, effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "悶える",
    "answer": "もだえる",
    "meaning": "to writhe (in pain), to be in agony, to be anguished, to be agonized, to be troubled"
  },
  {
    "question": "一年生",
    "answer": "いちねんせい",
    "meaning": "annual (plant), first-year student"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔やむ",
    "answer": "くやむ",
    "meaning": "to mourn, to lament, to be sorry, to regret, to repent"
  },
  {
    "question": "捻る",
    "answer": "ひねる,ねじる",
    "meaning": "to twist, to wrench, to turn (a switch on or off, etc.), to wring (a neck), to puzzle over, to defea"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱がす",
    "answer": "ぬがす",
    "meaning": "to strip someone, to help someone remove (clothes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝者",
    "answer": "しょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "winner, victor"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱気",
    "answer": "ねっき,ねつけ",
    "meaning": "heat, hot air, enthusiasm, feverish"
  },
  {
    "question": "対立",
    "answer": "たいりつ",
    "meaning": "confrontation, opposition, antagonism"
  },
  {
    "question": "当人",
    "answer": "とうにん",
    "meaning": "the person concerned, the person in question, the said person"
  },
  {
    "question": "突っ伏す",
    "answer": "つっぷす",
    "meaning": "to fall prostrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞き流す",
    "answer": "ききながす",
    "meaning": "to pay no attention to (while listening), to take no notice of, to ignore, to let go in one ear and"
  },
  {
    "question": "千年",
    "answer": "せんねん,ちとせ",
    "meaning": "millennium, one thousand years, long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "反する",
    "answer": "はんする",
    "meaning": "to be contrary to, to be inconsistent with, to contradict, to act contrary to (rules or guidelines),"
  },
  {
    "question": "没頭",
    "answer": "ぼっとう",
    "meaning": "immersing oneself in, being absorbed in, devoting oneself to, giving oneself up entirely to"
  },
  {
    "question": "現時点",
    "answer": "げんじてん",
    "meaning": "present point (i.e. in history), at the present time"
  },
  {
    "question": "口実",
    "answer": "こうじつ",
    "meaning": "excuse, pretext"
  },
  {
    "question": "先導",
    "answer": "せんどう",
    "meaning": "guidance, leadership, leading the way"
  },
  {
    "question": "自分勝手",
    "answer": "じぶんかって,じぶんがって",
    "meaning": "selfishness, egotism, egoism, (being) self-centered, without consulting, (doing) as one pleases, one"
  },
  {
    "question": "脅迫",
    "answer": "きょうはく",
    "meaning": "threat, menace, coercion, terrorism"
  },
  {
    "question": "初恋",
    "answer": "はつこい",
    "meaning": "first love, puppy love"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝転がる",
    "answer": "ねころがる",
    "meaning": "to lie down, to throw oneself down"
  },
  {
    "question": "一息",
    "answer": "ひといき",
    "meaning": "one breath, time of one breath, pause, break, rest, breather, (doing in) one go, doing without stopp"
  },
  {
    "question": "助手",
    "answer": "じょしゅ,すけて",
    "meaning": "assistant, helper, assistant (to a professor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻覚",
    "answer": "げんかく",
    "meaning": "hallucination, illusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "要因",
    "answer": "よういん",
    "meaning": "main cause, primary factor"
  },
  {
    "question": "全裸",
    "answer": "ぜんら",
    "meaning": "stark naked, nude"
  },
  {
    "question": "行事",
    "answer": "ぎょうじ",
    "meaning": "event, function"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁護士",
    "answer": "べんごし",
    "meaning": "lawyer, attorney"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱気",
    "answer": "よわき",
    "meaning": "timid, weak-kneed, fainthearted, bearish (e.g. market)"
  },
  {
    "question": "渋い",
    "answer": "しぶい",
    "meaning": "astringent, bitter, puckery, rough, harsh, tart, austere, elegant (and unobtrusive), refined, quiet"
  },
  {
    "question": "本性",
    "answer": "ほんしょう,ほんせい",
    "meaning": "true character, real nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "各自",
    "answer": "かくじ",
    "meaning": "each (person), everyone, individual, respective"
  },
  {
    "question": "待ち",
    "answer": "まち",
    "meaning": "waiting, waiting time, wait tile, tile which would complete one's hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕上げる",
    "answer": "しあげる",
    "meaning": "to finish up, to complete, to finish off, to get through, to polish off"
  },
  {
    "question": "版",
    "answer": "はん,ばん",
    "meaning": "edition, version, printing, impression, implementation (e.g. software), plate, block, cast, editions"
  },
  {
    "question": "初耳",
    "answer": "はつみみ",
    "meaning": "something heard for the first time, hearing something for the first time"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り組む",
    "answer": "とりくむ",
    "meaning": "to grapple with, to wrestle with, to engage in a bout, to be matched against, to tackle (e.g. a prob"
  },
  {
    "question": "検索",
    "answer": "けんさく",
    "meaning": "looking up (e.g. a word in a dictionary), retrieval (e.g. data), searching for, referring to"
  },
  {
    "question": "正す",
    "answer": "ただす",
    "meaning": "to enquire of someone about something (inquire), to question, to correct, to rectify, to reform, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "数学",
    "answer": "すうがく",
    "meaning": "mathematics, arithmetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "自在",
    "answer": "じざい",
    "meaning": "freely, at will"
  },
  {
    "question": "要",
    "answer": "かなめ,よう",
    "meaning": "pivot, vital point, cornerstone, keystone, Japanese photinia, main point, requirement, need, necessa"
  },
  {
    "question": "芽生える",
    "answer": "めばえる",
    "meaning": "to bud, to sprout"
  },
  {
    "question": "拍子",
    "answer": "ひょうし",
    "meaning": "(musical) time, tempo, beat, rhythm, the moment, the instance, chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "滑稽",
    "answer": "こっけい",
    "meaning": "funny, comical, humorous, laughable, ridiculous, silly, absurd"
  },
  {
    "question": "放題",
    "answer": "ほうだい",
    "meaning": "(doing) as one pleases, to one's heart's content, letting (something) go unchecked, leaving uncontro"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕獲",
    "answer": "ほかく",
    "meaning": "capture, seizure"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥深い",
    "answer": "おくふかい,おくぶかい",
    "meaning": "profound, deep, deep (of a cave, etc.), innermost, interior"
  },
  {
    "question": "設計",
    "answer": "せっけい",
    "meaning": "plan, design, layout"
  },
  {
    "question": "連行",
    "answer": "れんこう",
    "meaning": "taking (a suspect to the police), dragging (someone) away"
  },
  {
    "question": "個性",
    "answer": "こせい",
    "meaning": "individuality, personality, quirk, idiosyncrasy, character, individual characteristic"
  },
  {
    "question": "絵画",
    "answer": "かいが",
    "meaning": "painting, picture"
  },
  {
    "question": "補助",
    "answer": "ほじょ",
    "meaning": "assistance, support, aid, help, subsidy, supplement, subvention, grant-in-aid, auxiliary, subsidiary"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛人",
    "answer": "あいじん",
    "meaning": "lover, mistress"
  },
  {
    "question": "流行",
    "answer": "りゅうこう,はやり",
    "meaning": "fashion, trend, vogue, craze, fad, popularity, prevalence (of a disease), epidemic, prevalence (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "更新",
    "answer": "こうしん",
    "meaning": "renewal, update, innovation, improvement"
  },
  {
    "question": "多め",
    "answer": "おおめ",
    "meaning": "somewhat larger (amount), quite a lot, a little more (than usual), a little extra"
  },
  {
    "question": "通",
    "answer": "つう",
    "meaning": "authority, expert, connoisseur, well-informed person, counter for messages, letters, notes, document"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕様",
    "answer": "しよう",
    "meaning": "way, method, means, resource, remedy, (technical) specification"
  },
  {
    "question": "主義",
    "answer": "しゅぎ",
    "meaning": "doctrine, rule, principle, -ism"
  },
  {
    "question": "律儀",
    "answer": "りちぎ",
    "meaning": "upright, honest, faithful, conscientious, sincere"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿屋",
    "answer": "やどや",
    "meaning": "inn"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗黒",
    "answer": "あんこく",
    "meaning": "darkness"
  },
  {
    "question": "案件",
    "answer": "あんけん",
    "meaning": "matter (to discuss), item (on the agenda), issue, topic, (court) case"
  },
  {
    "question": "混沌",
    "answer": "こんとん",
    "meaning": "chaos, confusion, disorder, chaotic, confused, uncertain, disarrayed"
  },
  {
    "question": "真摯",
    "answer": "しんし",
    "meaning": "sincere, earnest, serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "名目",
    "answer": "めいもく,みょうもく",
    "meaning": "name, title, appellation, (something) nominal, (under the) pretext (of), pretense"
  },
  {
    "question": "口の端",
    "answer": "くちのは",
    "meaning": "gossip, corner of the mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶暴",
    "answer": "きょうぼう",
    "meaning": "ferocious, brutal, atrocious, savage, barbarous"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚空",
    "answer": "こくう",
    "meaning": "empty space, empty sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "一際",
    "answer": "ひときわ",
    "meaning": "conspicuously, noticeably, remarkably, especially, particularly"
  },
  {
    "question": "募集",
    "answer": "ぼしゅう",
    "meaning": "recruitment, invitation, selection, advertisement, taking applications, raising (funds, donations, e"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕暮れ",
    "answer": "ゆうぐれ",
    "meaning": "evening, dusk, twilight"
  },
  {
    "question": "漠然",
    "answer": "ばくぜん",
    "meaning": "vague, obscure, indistinct, hazy, ambiguous"
  },
  {
    "question": "御者",
    "answer": "ぎょしゃ",
    "meaning": "coachman, driver, cabman, postilion"
  },
  {
    "question": "派閥",
    "answer": "はばつ",
    "meaning": "clique, faction"
  },
  {
    "question": "群がる",
    "answer": "むらがる",
    "meaning": "to swarm, to gather"
  },
  {
    "question": "通り越す",
    "answer": "とおりこす",
    "meaning": "to go past (a place or thing), to go beyond"
  },
  {
    "question": "賢者",
    "answer": "けんじゃ,けんしゃ",
    "meaning": "wise person, sage"
  },
  {
    "question": "腕前",
    "answer": "うでまえ",
    "meaning": "ability, skill, facility"
  },
  {
    "question": "建つ",
    "answer": "たつ",
    "meaning": "to be erected, to be built"
  },
  {
    "question": "様になる",
    "answer": "ようになる,さまになる",
    "meaning": "to reach the point that, to come to be that, to turn into, to become good-looking, to start looking"
  },
  {
    "question": "指し示す",
    "answer": "さししめす",
    "meaning": "to indicate, to show, to point to"
  },
  {
    "question": "連れ戻す",
    "answer": "つれもどす",
    "meaning": "to bring back"
  },
  {
    "question": "貫通",
    "answer": "かんつう",
    "meaning": "piercing, penetrating, perforating, passing through, being well versed (in something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "休暇",
    "answer": "きゅうか",
    "meaning": "holiday, day off, furlough, absence (from work)"
  },
  {
    "question": "揉める",
    "answer": "もめる",
    "meaning": "to disagree, to dispute, to fight (over)"
  },
  {
    "question": "創造",
    "answer": "そうぞう",
    "meaning": "creation"
  },
  {
    "question": "遮断",
    "answer": "しゃだん",
    "meaning": "isolation, cut off, blockade, quarantine, interception, deprivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "瓦礫",
    "answer": "がれき,がりゃく",
    "meaning": "rubble, debris, wreckage"
  },
  {
    "question": "元通り",
    "answer": "もとどおり",
    "meaning": "as before, as ever, as it was originally"
  },
  {
    "question": "暁",
    "answer": "あかつき,あかとき",
    "meaning": "dawn, daybreak, event (e.g. 'in the event of ...'), occasion, occurrence"
  },
  {
    "question": "短時間",
    "answer": "たんじかん",
    "meaning": "short time"
  },
  {
    "question": "書物",
    "answer": "しょもつ",
    "meaning": "book, volume"
  },
  {
    "question": "消し去る",
    "answer": "けしさる",
    "meaning": "to get rid of, to erase, to dispel, to eradicate, to wipe away"
  },
  {
    "question": "音声",
    "answer": "おんせい,おんじょう",
    "meaning": "voice, speech, sound of a voice, sound (e.g. of a TV)"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き換え",
    "answer": "ひきかえ",
    "meaning": "exchange, conversion"
  },
  {
    "question": "破壊力",
    "answer": "はかいりょく",
    "meaning": "destructive power, destructive energy, destructive force"
  },
  {
    "question": "植える",
    "answer": "うえる",
    "meaning": "to plant, to grow, to raise, to insert, to transplant, to implant, to set (type), to inoculate (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "男らしい",
    "answer": "おとこらしい",
    "meaning": "manly, masculine, like a man"
  },
  {
    "question": "窮屈",
    "answer": "きゅうくつ",
    "meaning": "narrow, tight, cramped, formal, stiff, strict, ceremonious, rigid, constrained, uncomfortable, tight"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り",
    "answer": "うり",
    "meaning": "sale, selling, selling point, gimmick, seller, vendor, prostitution"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛撫",
    "answer": "あいぶ",
    "meaning": "caressing, loving dearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "爺",
    "answer": "じじ,じじい,じい",
    "meaning": "old man, old geezer"
  },
  {
    "question": "儂",
    "answer": "わし",
    "meaning": "I, me"
  },
  {
    "question": "灯る",
    "answer": "ともる,とぼる",
    "meaning": "to be lit (e.g. candle, lamp, light bulb), to be lighted, to be burning"
  },
  {
    "question": "沼",
    "answer": "ぬま",
    "meaning": "marsh, swamp, wetland, bog, pond, being hooked (on a video game, TV show, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "注ぎ込む",
    "answer": "そそぎこむ,つぎこむ",
    "meaning": "to pour into (liquids), to pump into, to invest in, to sink money into, to put into, to lay out (fun"
  },
  {
    "question": "髭",
    "answer": "ひげ",
    "meaning": "moustache, beard, whiskers, whiskers (on a cat, etc.), feelers (on an insect, etc.), (chin) tuft, ex"
  },
  {
    "question": "早急",
    "answer": "そうきゅう,さっきゅう",
    "meaning": "immediate, prompt, quick, rapid, urgent, pressing"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊い",
    "answer": "とうとい,たっとい",
    "meaning": "precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred"
  },
  {
    "question": "星空",
    "answer": "ほしぞら",
    "meaning": "starry sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "双",
    "answer": "そう,もろ",
    "meaning": "pair, both"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬意",
    "answer": "けいい",
    "meaning": "respect, honour, honor"
  },
  {
    "question": "学習",
    "answer": "がくしゅう",
    "meaning": "study, learning, tutorial"
  },
  {
    "question": "束ねる",
    "answer": "たばねる,つかねる",
    "meaning": "to tie up in a bundle (e.g. straw, hair, bills, letters), to bundle, to sheathe, to govern, to manag"
  },
  {
    "question": "革",
    "answer": "かわ,つくりかわ,つくりがわ",
    "meaning": "leather, tanned animal hide, kanji 'leather' radical (radical 177)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手招き",
    "answer": "てまねき",
    "meaning": "beckoning"
  },
  {
    "question": "関節",
    "answer": "かんせつ",
    "meaning": "joint (knee, elbow, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一夜",
    "answer": "いちや,ひとや,ひとよ",
    "meaning": "one night, all night, overnight, one evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "花が咲く",
    "answer": "はながさく",
    "meaning": "to bloom, to blossom, to become lively (esp. of conversation), to become animated, to experience a g"
  },
  {
    "question": "大分",
    "answer": "だいぶ,だいぶん,おおいた",
    "meaning": "considerably, greatly, a lot, Ōita (city, prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "素手",
    "answer": "すで",
    "meaning": "bare hand, empty hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "毎晩",
    "answer": "まいばん",
    "meaning": "every night"
  },
  {
    "question": "第四",
    "answer": "だいよん",
    "meaning": "fourth"
  },
  {
    "question": "心細い",
    "answer": "こころぼそい",
    "meaning": "helpless, forlorn, hopeless, unpromising, lonely, discouraging, disheartening"
  },
  {
    "question": "面影",
    "answer": "おもかげ",
    "meaning": "face, looks, vestiges, trace"
  },
  {
    "question": "嬢ちゃん",
    "answer": "じょうちゃん",
    "meaning": "young girl"
  },
  {
    "question": "勧誘",
    "answer": "かんゆう",
    "meaning": "invitation, solicitation, canvassing, canvasing, inducement, persuasion, encouragement"
  },
  {
    "question": "旗",
    "answer": "はた",
    "meaning": "flag, banner (administrative division of Inner Mongolia)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幹",
    "answer": "みき,かん,から",
    "meaning": "(tree) trunk, (arrow) shaft, (tool) handle, backbone, base, trunk, stem, stalk, shaft (of an arrow),"
  },
  {
    "question": "莫大",
    "answer": "ばくだい",
    "meaning": "vast, huge, immense, enormous, colossal, malva nut (Sterculia lychnophora)"
  },
  {
    "question": "書き込む",
    "answer": "かきこむ",
    "meaning": "to fill in (field, entry, etc.), to fill out (form), to post a message (e.g. on a bulletin-board), t"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗脳",
    "answer": "せんのう",
    "meaning": "brainwashing"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝る",
    "answer": "まさる",
    "meaning": "to excel, to surpass, to exceed, to have an edge, to be superior, to outrival, to outweigh, to prepo"
  },
  {
    "question": "色合い",
    "answer": "いろあい,いろあわい",
    "meaning": "colouring, coloring, shade (of colour), hue, tone, tinge, tint, flavour, nuance, feel, sense, look"
  },
  {
    "question": "徒歩",
    "answer": "とほ,かち",
    "meaning": "walking, going on foot, foot soldier (Edo period), samurai on foot"
  },
  {
    "question": "業者",
    "answer": "ぎょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "trader, dealer, businessman, vendor, supplier, manufacturer, fellow trader, people in the same trade"
  },
  {
    "question": "撒く",
    "answer": "まく",
    "meaning": "to scatter, to sprinkle, to strew, to distribute (handbills, etc.), to spread (rumours, etc.), to gi"
  },
  {
    "question": "豆",
    "answer": "まめ",
    "meaning": "legume (esp. edible legumes or their seeds, such as beans, peas, pulses, etc.), beans, peas, soya be"
  },
  {
    "question": "祝い",
    "answer": "いわい,ゆわい",
    "meaning": "congratulation, congratulations, celebration, festival, congratulatory gift, present"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き",
    "answer": "つき,つつき",
    "meaning": "thrust, stab, lunge, pass (in fencing), tsuki, thrust to the throat (in kendo), thrust to the chest,"
  },
  {
    "question": "通称",
    "answer": "つうしょう",
    "meaning": "popular name, common name, nickname, alias"
  },
  {
    "question": "葛藤",
    "answer": "かっとう,つづらふじ",
    "meaning": "conflict, complication, troubles, discord, Chinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum), complex inter-relat"
  },
  {
    "question": "好都合",
    "answer": "こうつごう",
    "meaning": "convenient, favorable, favourable, expedient, expedience"
  },
  {
    "question": "融合",
    "answer": "ゆうごう",
    "meaning": "agglutination, adhesion, fusion, combination, blending, uniting"
  },
  {
    "question": "背伸び",
    "answer": "せのび",
    "meaning": "standing on tiptoe and stretching one's back to make oneself taller, stretching oneself, overreachin"
  },
  {
    "question": "高らか",
    "answer": "たからか",
    "meaning": "loud, sonorous, ringing"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽根",
    "answer": "はね",
    "meaning": "feather, plume, down, wing, blade (of a fan, propeller, etc.), shuttlecock (in badminton), shuttleco"
  },
  {
    "question": "純白",
    "answer": "じゅんぱく",
    "meaning": "pure white, snow white"
  },
  {
    "question": "口走る",
    "answer": "くちばしる",
    "meaning": "to blurt out, to let slip, to say inadvertently, to come out with (e.g. nonsense)"
  },
  {
    "question": "正論",
    "answer": "せいろん",
    "meaning": "sound argument, fair argument, just reasoning"
  },
  {
    "question": "支持",
    "answer": "しじ",
    "meaning": "support, backing, endorsement, approval, holding up, propping"
  },
  {
    "question": "大袈裟",
    "answer": "おおげさ",
    "meaning": "grandiose, exaggerated"
  },
  {
    "question": "膨れる",
    "answer": "ふくれる",
    "meaning": "to swell (out), to expand, to be inflated, to distend, to bulge, to get cross, to get sulky, to pout"
  },
  {
    "question": "危険性",
    "answer": "きけんせい",
    "meaning": "riskiness, (level of) danger"
  },
  {
    "question": "断じて",
    "answer": "だんじて",
    "meaning": "absolutely, positively, decidedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒らす",
    "answer": "あらす",
    "meaning": "to lay waste, to devastate, to damage, to invade, to break into, to troll (e.g. web forums), to spam"
  },
  {
    "question": "射撃",
    "answer": "しゃげき",
    "meaning": "firing, shooting, fire, gunshot, marksmanship"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち物",
    "answer": "もちもの",
    "meaning": "one's property, personal effects, one's belongings"
  },
  {
    "question": "拍子抜け",
    "answer": "ひょうしぬけ",
    "meaning": "anticlimax, let-down, disappointment, loss of interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "茂み",
    "answer": "しげみ",
    "meaning": "thicket, coppice, brushwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "一転",
    "answer": "いってん",
    "meaning": "one turn, spinning around, complete change, reversal, (an) about-face, sudden transformation"
  },
  {
    "question": "支障",
    "answer": "ししょう",
    "meaning": "obstacle, hindrance, impediment, difficulty"
  },
  {
    "question": "一昨日",
    "answer": "おととい,おとつい,いっさくじつ",
    "meaning": "day before yesterday"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅い",
    "answer": "あかい",
    "meaning": "red, crimson, scarlet, vermilion, vermillion, Red, communist, beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "貪る",
    "answer": "むさぼる",
    "meaning": "to covet, to crave, to lust insatiably for, to indulge in, to devour greedily"
  },
  {
    "question": "証人",
    "answer": "しょうにん",
    "meaning": "witness"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪郭",
    "answer": "りんかく",
    "meaning": "contour, outline, border, silhouette, summary, sketch, looks, features, appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "校門",
    "answer": "こうもん",
    "meaning": "school gate"
  },
  {
    "question": "作",
    "answer": "さく",
    "meaning": "work (e.g. of art), production, harvest, cultivation, farming, crop, yield, technique"
  },
  {
    "question": "造り",
    "answer": "つくり,づくり",
    "meaning": "making, producing, manufacturing, building, construction, make, structure, appearance (attire, make-"
  },
  {
    "question": "迷子",
    "answer": "まいご",
    "meaning": "lost child, lost person, stray child, missing child"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩恵",
    "answer": "おんけい",
    "meaning": "grace, favor, favour, blessing, benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "水色",
    "answer": "みずいろ,すいしょく",
    "meaning": "light blue, pale blue, aqua, colour of water (esp. in rivers, lakes, sea), scenery of rivers, lakes,"
  },
  {
    "question": "異形",
    "answer": "いぎょう,いけい",
    "meaning": "fantastic, grotesque, strange-looking, suspicious-looking, atypical appearance, atypicality, heterom"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽園",
    "answer": "らくえん",
    "meaning": "paradise, Eden, Elysium"
  },
  {
    "question": "憂鬱",
    "answer": "ゆううつ",
    "meaning": "depression, melancholy, dejection, gloom, despondency"
  },
  {
    "question": "秘書",
    "answer": "ひしょ",
    "meaning": "(private) secretary, treasured book, secret book"
  },
  {
    "question": "治める",
    "answer": "おさめる",
    "meaning": "to govern, to manage, to subdue"
  },
  {
    "question": "及び",
    "answer": "および",
    "meaning": "and, as well as"
  },
  {
    "question": "視察",
    "answer": "しさつ",
    "meaning": "inspection, observation"
  },
  {
    "question": "見物",
    "answer": "けんぶつ,みもの",
    "meaning": "sightseeing, watching, viewing, sightseer, watcher, spectator, sight, attraction, spectacle, somethi"
  },
  {
    "question": "社員",
    "answer": "しゃいん",
    "meaning": "company employee, member of a corporation, company stockholder (esp. in legal contexts)"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼光",
    "answer": "がんこう",
    "meaning": "glint in eye, discernment"
  },
  {
    "question": "惑わす",
    "answer": "まどわす",
    "meaning": "to bewilder, to perplex, to puzzle, to delude, to mislead, to deceive, to tempt, to seduce"
  },
  {
    "question": "獅子",
    "answer": "しし",
    "meaning": "lion, left-hand guardian dog at a Shinto shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "白銀",
    "answer": "しろがね,しろかね,はくぎん",
    "meaning": "silver (Ag), silver coin, money, silver medal, silver colour, silver color, silver, snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "噴く",
    "answer": "ふく",
    "meaning": "to emit, to spout, to spurt, to boil over"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽蔑",
    "answer": "けいべつ",
    "meaning": "scorn, disdain, contempt"
  },
  {
    "question": "為す",
    "answer": "なす",
    "meaning": "to build up, to establish, to form, to become (a state), to accomplish, to achieve, to succeed in, t"
  },
  {
    "question": "邸",
    "answer": "やしき,てい",
    "meaning": "residence, estate, grounds, premises, mansion"
  },
  {
    "question": "合計",
    "answer": "ごうけい",
    "meaning": "sum total, total amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "言葉遣い",
    "answer": "ことばづかい",
    "meaning": "speech, expression, wording, language"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝日",
    "answer": "あさひ",
    "meaning": "morning sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "効果的",
    "answer": "こうかてき",
    "meaning": "effective, successful"
  },
  {
    "question": "爵位",
    "answer": "しゃくい",
    "meaning": "peerage, court rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "手持ち",
    "answer": "てもち",
    "meaning": "in hand, on hand, on one, in stock, in store, handheld"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱力",
    "answer": "だつりょく",
    "meaning": "loss of strength, exhaustion, weakness"
  },
  {
    "question": "申し込む",
    "answer": "もうしこむ",
    "meaning": "to apply for, to make an application, to propose (marriage), to offer (mediation), to make an overtu"
  },
  {
    "question": "教官",
    "answer": "きょうかん",
    "meaning": "teacher, instructor, professor"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛々しい",
    "answer": "いたいたしい",
    "meaning": "pitiful, pathetic, painful to look at"
  },
  {
    "question": "連想",
    "answer": "れんそう",
    "meaning": "association (of ideas), being reminded (of something), suggestion"
  },
  {
    "question": "嗚咽",
    "answer": "おえつ",
    "meaning": "sobbing, weeping, fit of crying"
  },
  {
    "question": "稀",
    "answer": "まれ,き",
    "meaning": "rare, seldom, dilute"
  },
  {
    "question": "強がる",
    "answer": "つよがる",
    "meaning": "to pretend to be tough, to put on a brave front, to whistle in the dark, to bluff"
  },
  {
    "question": "皺",
    "answer": "しわ,しぼ,さび",
    "meaning": "wrinkle, crease, ripple, bumpy texture of a material (esp. woven fabric), creases in an eboshi hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "表紙",
    "answer": "ひょうし",
    "meaning": "cover (of a book, magazine, etc.), binding, appearing on the cover of a magazine"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗れる",
    "answer": "やぶれる",
    "meaning": "to be defeated, to be beaten, to be unsuccessful, to lose"
  },
  {
    "question": "決する",
    "answer": "けっする",
    "meaning": "to decide, to determine"
  },
  {
    "question": "門番",
    "answer": "もんばん",
    "meaning": "gatekeeper, door guard, doorman, concierge, janitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "屈する",
    "answer": "くっする",
    "meaning": "to yield, to give in, to be daunted, to shrink, to bend (knee, etc.), to subdue, to overpower, to fe"
  },
  {
    "question": "呆ける",
    "answer": "ぼける,ほうける",
    "meaning": "to grow senile, to be childish with age, to be mentally slow, to be befuddled, to play stupid, to sa"
  },
  {
    "question": "神父",
    "answer": "しんぷ",
    "meaning": "Catholic priest, abbe, reverend father, minister, padre"
  },
  {
    "question": "火力",
    "answer": "かりょく",
    "meaning": "heating power, thermal power, firepower"
  },
  {
    "question": "左側",
    "answer": "ひだりがわ,さそく",
    "meaning": "left side, left-hand side"
  },
  {
    "question": "事項",
    "answer": "じこう",
    "meaning": "matter, item, facts"
  },
  {
    "question": "局",
    "answer": "きょく,つぼね",
    "meaning": "bureau, department, office (e.g. post, telephone), broadcasting station (e.g. television, radio), ch"
  },
  {
    "question": "即死",
    "answer": "そくし",
    "meaning": "instant death"
  },
  {
    "question": "率直",
    "answer": "そっちょく",
    "meaning": "frank, candid, straightforward, openhearted, direct, outspoken"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝不足",
    "answer": "ねぶそく",
    "meaning": "lack of sleep, insufficient sleep"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚か者",
    "answer": "おろかもの",
    "meaning": "fool"
  },
  {
    "question": "口説く",
    "answer": "くどく",
    "meaning": "to persuade, to coax, to solicit, to seduce, to make advances, to make a play, to make a pass, to pu"
  },
  {
    "question": "出掛ける",
    "answer": "でかける",
    "meaning": "to go out (e.g. on an excursion or outing), to leave, to depart, to start, to set out, to be about t"
  },
  {
    "question": "首都",
    "answer": "しゅと",
    "meaning": "capital city, metropolis"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗がり",
    "answer": "くらがり",
    "meaning": "darkness"
  },
  {
    "question": "健気",
    "answer": "けなげ",
    "meaning": "admirable, commendable, praiseworthy, laudable, brave, heroic, noble, courageous"
  },
  {
    "question": "志",
    "answer": "こころざし",
    "meaning": "will, resolution, intention, ambition, aim, goal, kindness, goodwill, kind offer, gift (as a token o"
  },
  {
    "question": "費用",
    "answer": "ひよう",
    "meaning": "cost, expense"
  },
  {
    "question": "考え直す",
    "answer": "かんがえなおす",
    "meaning": "to reconsider, to rethink, to reassess"
  },
  {
    "question": "凝る",
    "answer": "こごる,こる,しこる",
    "meaning": "to congeal, to freeze, to become stiff (of muscles), to get absorbed in, to develop a passion for, t"
  },
  {
    "question": "網",
    "answer": "あみ,もう",
    "meaning": "net, netting, web, network"
  },
  {
    "question": "必然",
    "answer": "ひつぜん",
    "meaning": "inevitable, necessary, certain, sure, inevitability, necessity"
  },
  {
    "question": "工事",
    "answer": "こうじ",
    "meaning": "construction work"
  },
  {
    "question": "出",
    "answer": "で,しゅつ",
    "meaning": "coming out, going out, outflow, efflux, rising (of the Sun or the Moon), attending (work), appearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "滴る",
    "answer": "したたる",
    "meaning": "to drip, to drop, to trickle, to overflow (with freshness, beauty, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "興味津々",
    "answer": "きょうみしんしん",
    "meaning": "very interesting, of absorbing interest, having a keen interest (in), being immensely curious (about"
  },
  {
    "question": "供給",
    "answer": "きょうきゅう",
    "meaning": "supply, provision"
  },
  {
    "question": "噴水",
    "answer": "ふんすい",
    "meaning": "water fountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "人口",
    "answer": "じんこう",
    "meaning": "population, common talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "突っ立つ",
    "answer": "つったつ",
    "meaning": "to stick up (hair, etc.), to stand up straight, to stand up abruptly, to jump to one's feet, to stan"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶好",
    "answer": "ぜっこう",
    "meaning": "best, ideal, perfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "不正",
    "answer": "ふせい",
    "meaning": "injustice, unfairness, wrongdoing, iniquity, impropriety, irregularity, dishonesty, illegality, frau"
  },
  {
    "question": "一変",
    "answer": "いっぺん",
    "meaning": "complete change, about-face"
  },
  {
    "question": "極力",
    "answer": "きょくりょく",
    "meaning": "to the utmost, to the best of one's ability"
  },
  {
    "question": "伊達",
    "answer": "だて",
    "meaning": "elegance, dandyism, sophistication, having style, affectation, showing off, putting on an air, appea"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠距離",
    "answer": "えんきょり",
    "meaning": "long distance, tele-"
  },
  {
    "question": "足首",
    "answer": "あしくび",
    "meaning": "ankle"
  },
  {
    "question": "隊員",
    "answer": "たいいん",
    "meaning": "troops, group members, team members"
  },
  {
    "question": "形式",
    "answer": "けいしき",
    "meaning": "form (as opposed to substance), formality, method, system, style, format, mode, appearance, form (so"
  },
  {
    "question": "惑星",
    "answer": "わくせい",
    "meaning": "planet"
  },
  {
    "question": "応用",
    "answer": "おうよう",
    "meaning": "(practical) application, putting to practical use, applied"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し黙る",
    "answer": "おしだまる",
    "meaning": "to keep silent"
  },
  {
    "question": "観測",
    "answer": "かんそく",
    "meaning": "observation, survey, measurement"
  },
  {
    "question": "銃弾",
    "answer": "じゅうだん",
    "meaning": "bullet (from a rifle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "素性",
    "answer": "すじょう,そせい",
    "meaning": "birth, lineage, parentage, origin, identity, background, history, past, provenance"
  },
  {
    "question": "図",
    "answer": "ず",
    "meaning": "drawing, picture, diagram, figure, illustration, chart, graph, sight, scene"
  },
  {
    "question": "銃声",
    "answer": "じゅうせい",
    "meaning": "(sound of a) gunshot, (gun) report"
  },
  {
    "question": "裁判",
    "answer": "さいばん",
    "meaning": "trial, judgement, judgment"
  },
  {
    "question": "孕む",
    "answer": "はらむ",
    "meaning": "to conceive, to become pregnant, to get filled with (e.g. sails filled with wind), to be swollen wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "溶け込む",
    "answer": "とけこむ",
    "meaning": "to melt into, to dissolve into, to merge into, to blend into (surroundings), to fit in, to adapt to,"
  },
  {
    "question": "脆い",
    "answer": "もろい",
    "meaning": "brittle, fragile, weak, frail, tender-hearted, sentimental, easily moved"
  },
  {
    "question": "火照る",
    "answer": "ほてる",
    "meaning": "to feel hot, to flush, to burn"
  },
  {
    "question": "看病",
    "answer": "かんびょう",
    "meaning": "nursing (a patient)"
  },
  {
    "question": "首輪",
    "answer": "くびわ",
    "meaning": "(animal) collar, necklace, choker"
  },
  {
    "question": "狐",
    "answer": "きつね,けつね,きつ",
    "meaning": "fox (esp. the red fox, Vulpes vulpes), fox (i.e. a sly person), soba or udon topped with deep-fried"
  },
  {
    "question": "同志",
    "answer": "どうし",
    "meaning": "like-mindedness, (being of the) same mind, shared sentiment, comrade, fellow, kindred soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "補佐",
    "answer": "ほさ",
    "meaning": "aid, help, assistance, assistant, counselor, counsellor, adviser, advisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "粉砕",
    "answer": "ふんさい",
    "meaning": "pulverization, pulverisation, smashing, demolishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "高貴",
    "answer": "こうき",
    "meaning": "high class, noble"
  },
  {
    "question": "出入り口",
    "answer": "でいりぐち",
    "meaning": "exit and entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き込む",
    "answer": "ひきこむ",
    "meaning": "to pull into, to draw in, to bring in, to win over"
  },
  {
    "question": "見込む",
    "answer": "みこむ",
    "meaning": "to anticipate, to expect, to estimate, to count on, to allow for, to take into account, to place con"
  },
  {
    "question": "何処か",
    "answer": "どこか,どっか",
    "meaning": "somewhere, anywhere, in some respects"
  },
  {
    "question": "危機感",
    "answer": "ききかん",
    "meaning": "sense of impending crisis, sense of danger"
  },
  {
    "question": "降参",
    "answer": "こうさん",
    "meaning": "surrender, submission, capitulation, being defeated (e.g. by a problem), giving up, giving in"
  },
  {
    "question": "降伏",
    "answer": "こうふく",
    "meaning": "capitulation, surrender, submission, yield"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦慄",
    "answer": "せんりつ",
    "meaning": "shudder, shiver, trembling with fear"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽勝",
    "answer": "らくしょう",
    "meaning": "easy victory, walkover, easy peasy, child's play, cakewalk, walk in the park"
  },
  {
    "question": "異国",
    "answer": "いこく",
    "meaning": "foreign country"
  },
  {
    "question": "処女",
    "answer": "しょじょ",
    "meaning": "virgin, maiden"
  },
  {
    "question": "真上",
    "answer": "まうえ",
    "meaning": "just above, right overhead"
  },
  {
    "question": "水分",
    "answer": "すいぶん",
    "meaning": "water, liquid, fluid, moisture, humidity, sap, juice"
  },
  {
    "question": "特製",
    "answer": "とくせい",
    "meaning": "special make, deluxe"
  },
  {
    "question": "罵倒",
    "answer": "ばとう",
    "meaning": "(verbal) abuse, denunciation, disparagement, vilification, scathing criticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "解",
    "answer": "かい",
    "meaning": "solution (of an equation, inequality, etc.), root (e.g. of a polynomial), solution (to a given probl"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝む",
    "answer": "おがむ",
    "meaning": "to assume the posture of praying, to press the palms and fingers of both hands together, to do rever"
  },
  {
    "question": "堪る",
    "answer": "たまる",
    "meaning": "to bear, to endure"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち位置",
    "answer": "たちいち",
    "meaning": "position (where one is standing), place where one stands, position, stance, standpoint, status, role"
  },
  {
    "question": "開き直る",
    "answer": "ひらきなおる",
    "meaning": "to become defiant, to fight back, to turn upon, to take the offensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "体型",
    "answer": "たいけい",
    "meaning": "figure, body shape, build, physique, form, somatotype, biotype, habitus, (type of) physique"
  },
  {
    "question": "過ち",
    "answer": "あやまち",
    "meaning": "fault, error, indiscretion, faux pas"
  },
  {
    "question": "爺さん",
    "answer": "じいさん",
    "meaning": "grandfather (may be used after name as honorific), male senior-citizen (may be used after name as ho"
  },
  {
    "question": "警護",
    "answer": "けいご",
    "meaning": "bodyguard, escort"
  },
  {
    "question": "崎",
    "answer": "さき,みさき",
    "meaning": "small peninsula, cape, promontory, headland, cape (on coast)"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃げ切る",
    "answer": "にげきる",
    "meaning": "to make good one's escape, to get away, to outrun, to hold on (and win), to win narrowly"
  },
  {
    "question": "亀頭",
    "answer": "きとう",
    "meaning": "glans (esp. glans penis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "先祖",
    "answer": "せんぞ",
    "meaning": "ancestor"
  },
  {
    "question": "芸術",
    "answer": "げいじゅつ",
    "meaning": "(fine) art, the arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "替える",
    "answer": "かえる",
    "meaning": "to replace, to exchange, to interchange, to substitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "至極",
    "answer": "しごく",
    "meaning": "very, extremely, exceedingly, quite, most, top, highest, best"
  },
  {
    "question": "失せる",
    "answer": "うせる",
    "meaning": "to disappear, to vanish, to fade away, to go, to leave, to die"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い描く",
    "answer": "おもいえがく",
    "meaning": "to imagine, to picture, to figure, to see"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍団",
    "answer": "ぐんだん",
    "meaning": "army corps"
  },
  {
    "question": "噓",
    "answer": "うそ",
    "meaning": "lie, fib, falsehood, untruth, mistake, error, unwise move, bad decision, no way!, unbelievable!, rea"
  },
  {
    "question": "秩序",
    "answer": "ちつじょ",
    "meaning": "order, discipline, regularity, system, method"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪口",
    "answer": "わるぐち,わるくち,あっこう",
    "meaning": "slander, bad-mouthing, abuse, insult, speaking ill (of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い通り",
    "answer": "おもいどおり",
    "meaning": "as one expects, as one wants, to one's satisfaction, as one sees fit"
  },
  {
    "question": "口内",
    "answer": "こうない",
    "meaning": "oral, in the mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "死角",
    "answer": "しかく",
    "meaning": "blind spot (e.g. of a driver), dead angle, dead ground, dead space, sector without fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪人",
    "answer": "あくにん",
    "meaning": "bad person, villain, scoundrel, wrongdoer, wicked person"
  },
  {
    "question": "玩具",
    "answer": "おもちゃ,がんぐ",
    "meaning": "toy, plaything"
  },
  {
    "question": "生成",
    "answer": "せいせい,きなり",
    "meaning": "creation, generation, formation, derivation, unbleached cloth, unbleached colour (color), unbleached"
  },
  {
    "question": "実践",
    "answer": "じっせん",
    "meaning": "practice, putting into practice, implementation, praxis (philosophy)"
  },
  {
    "question": "缶",
    "answer": "かん,かま,ほとぎ",
    "meaning": "can, tin, canned food, boiler, fat-bodied, small-mouthed earthenware jar for carrying water, water v"
  },
  {
    "question": "封鎖",
    "answer": "ふうさ",
    "meaning": "blockade, lockdown, sealing off (an area), freezing (funds)"
  },
  {
    "question": "週末",
    "answer": "しゅうまつ",
    "meaning": "weekend"
  },
  {
    "question": "子息",
    "answer": "しそく",
    "meaning": "son"
  },
  {
    "question": "四肢",
    "answer": "しし",
    "meaning": "the (four) limbs, arms and legs"
  },
  {
    "question": "着物",
    "answer": "きもの,きるもの",
    "meaning": "kimono, Japanese traditional clothing (esp. full-length), clothing, clothes, something to wear"
  },
  {
    "question": "平均",
    "answer": "へいきん,へいぎん",
    "meaning": "average, mean, balance, equilibrium"
  },
  {
    "question": "囲う",
    "answer": "かこう",
    "meaning": "to enclose, to surround, to encircle, to fence, to wall in, to shelter (e.g. a criminal), to shield,"
  },
  {
    "question": "正座",
    "answer": "しょうざ,せいざ",
    "meaning": "seat of honor, seat of honour, seiza, kneeling with the tops of the feet flat on the floor, and sitt"
  },
  {
    "question": "包み",
    "answer": "つつみ",
    "meaning": "bundle, package, parcel, counter for wrapped objects"
  },
  {
    "question": "付き添う",
    "answer": "つきそう",
    "meaning": "to attend on, to wait on, to accompany, to escort, to chaperone"
  },
  {
    "question": "心情",
    "answer": "しんじょう",
    "meaning": "sentiment, emotions, one's feelings, one's heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "相対",
    "answer": "あいたい,そうたい",
    "meaning": "involving only the parties concerned, tete-a-tete, relativity, relative"
  },
  {
    "question": "持て余す",
    "answer": "もてあます",
    "meaning": "to be too much for one, to find unmanageable, to be beyond one's control, to not know what to do wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼下",
    "answer": "がんか",
    "meaning": "under one's eyes, below"
  },
  {
    "question": "銃口",
    "answer": "じゅうこう",
    "meaning": "gun point, muzzle"
  },
  {
    "question": "一手",
    "answer": "いって,ひとて",
    "meaning": "one move (in go, shogi, etc.), only way, only means, doing alone, doing single-handed, monopoly, one"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩人",
    "answer": "おんじん",
    "meaning": "benefactor, patron"
  },
  {
    "question": "血管",
    "answer": "けっかん",
    "meaning": "blood vessel, vein"
  },
  {
    "question": "細身",
    "answer": "ほそみ",
    "meaning": "narrow, thin (sized), slender"
  },
  {
    "question": "声色",
    "answer": "こわいろ,せいしょく",
    "meaning": "tone of voice, mimicry, imitative voice, voice and countenance, song and women"
  },
  {
    "question": "好ましい",
    "answer": "このましい",
    "meaning": "nice, likeable, desirable"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱",
    "answer": "じゃく",
    "meaning": "little less than, slightly fewer than, just under, weakness, the weak"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍勢",
    "answer": "ぐんぜい",
    "meaning": "military forces, hosts, troops"
  },
  {
    "question": "更なる",
    "answer": "さらなる",
    "meaning": "even more, still more, further"
  },
  {
    "question": "執拗",
    "answer": "しつよう,しつおう",
    "meaning": "persistent, obstinate, tenacious, relentless, insistent, importunate, persevering, stubborn"
  },
  {
    "question": "祭壇",
    "answer": "さいだん",
    "meaning": "altar"
  },
  {
    "question": "正当",
    "answer": "せいとう",
    "meaning": "just, justifiable, right, due, proper, equitable, reasonable, legitimate, legal, lawful"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝起き",
    "answer": "ねおき",
    "meaning": "lying down and getting up, waking, getting up, living (with), staying (with)"
  },
  {
    "question": "感激",
    "answer": "かんげき",
    "meaning": "deep emotion, impression, inspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "母ちゃん",
    "answer": "かあちゃん",
    "meaning": "mum, mom, mummy, mommy, the missus"
  },
  {
    "question": "香水",
    "answer": "こうすい,こうずい",
    "meaning": "perfume, scented water used for purification, water offering to Buddha"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥歯",
    "answer": "おくば",
    "meaning": "molars, back teeth"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び交う",
    "answer": "とびかう",
    "meaning": "to fly about, to flutter about, to flit about, to fly past each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "脅し",
    "answer": "おどし",
    "meaning": "threat, bird-scaring device (scarecrow, gun, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘲笑",
    "answer": "ちょうしょう",
    "meaning": "scornful laughter, ridicule, derision, sneer"
  },
  {
    "question": "強度",
    "answer": "きょうど",
    "meaning": "strength, intensity, strong (e.g. glasses), powerful (e.g. lens), intense (e.g. fear), extreme"
  },
  {
    "question": "図星",
    "answer": "ずぼし",
    "meaning": "bull's-eye, the mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "詐欺",
    "answer": "さぎ",
    "meaning": "fraud, swindle, graft, cheating, trick, scam"
  },
  {
    "question": "動向",
    "answer": "どうこう",
    "meaning": "trend, tendency, movement, attitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "検証",
    "answer": "けんしょう",
    "meaning": "verification, inspection"
  },
  {
    "question": "代金",
    "answer": "だいきん",
    "meaning": "price, cost, charge, payment, bill, fee"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆使",
    "answer": "くし",
    "meaning": "using freely, making full use of, having a good command of, working (someone) hard, driving (someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "所持",
    "answer": "しょじ",
    "meaning": "possession, owning"
  },
  {
    "question": "得",
    "answer": "とく,う",
    "meaning": "profit, advantage, benefit, gain, rebirth in paradise, entering nirvana, to get, to acquire, to obta"
  },
  {
    "question": "出場",
    "answer": "しゅつじょう,でば",
    "meaning": "(stage) appearance, performance, participation (e.g. in a tournament), one's time (e.g. to go on sta"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾行",
    "answer": "びこう",
    "meaning": "shadow, tail, following"
  },
  {
    "question": "何時",
    "answer": "いつ,なんじ,なんどき",
    "meaning": "when, at what time, how soon, normal times, ordinary days, what time, which hour, at what moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "家出",
    "answer": "いえで",
    "meaning": "running away from home, elopement, outing, going out, becoming a Buddhist monk, entering the priesth"
  },
  {
    "question": "難い",
    "answer": "かたい,にくい,がたい",
    "meaning": "difficult, hard, difficult to ..., hard to ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "慈悲",
    "answer": "じひ",
    "meaning": "mercy, compassion, clemency, pity, charity, benevolence, Hodgson's hawk-cuckoo (Cuculus fugax), Hors"
  },
  {
    "question": "距離感",
    "answer": "きょりかん",
    "meaning": "sense of distance (physical or emotional), feeling of distance"
  },
  {
    "question": "成分",
    "answer": "せいぶん",
    "meaning": "ingredient, component, composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆け巡る",
    "answer": "かけめぐる",
    "meaning": "to run about, to rush about"
  },
  {
    "question": "麗しい",
    "answer": "うるわしい",
    "meaning": "beautiful, lovely, heartwarming"
  },
  {
    "question": "取得",
    "answer": "とりえ,しゅとく",
    "meaning": "worth, merit, value, good point, redeeming feature, saving grace, acquisition, obtaining, gaining po"
  },
  {
    "question": "転送",
    "answer": "てんそう",
    "meaning": "transfer, redirection, transmission, forwarding (telephone call, e-mail, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "損ねる",
    "answer": "そこねる",
    "meaning": "to harm, to hurt, to injure, to wreck, to miss one's chance to (do something), to fail to (do what o"
  },
  {
    "question": "返し",
    "answer": "かえし",
    "meaning": "reversal, return, return gift, return favour (favor), barb (on a fishing hook), mixture of soy sauce"
  },
  {
    "question": "古",
    "answer": "いにしえ,ふる",
    "meaning": "antiquity, ancient times, used item, secondhand item, old, used, previous"
  },
  {
    "question": "不能",
    "answer": "ふのう",
    "meaning": "impossible, incapable (of doing), unable (to do), incompetence, inability, impotence, having no solu"
  },
  {
    "question": "早口",
    "answer": "はやくち,はやぐち",
    "meaning": "fast-talking, rapid talking"
  },
  {
    "question": "切っ先",
    "answer": "きっさき",
    "meaning": "point (of a sword, etc.), pointed verbal attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "根本",
    "answer": "ねもと,こんぽん,ねほん",
    "meaning": "root, source, origin, foundation, base, principle, kabuki script, illustrated kabuki script"
  },
  {
    "question": "乏しい",
    "answer": "とぼしい,ともしい",
    "meaning": "meagre, meager, scarce, limited, destitute, hard up, lacking, scanty, poor"
  },
  {
    "question": "異論",
    "answer": "いろん",
    "meaning": "different opinion, objection"
  },
  {
    "question": "現役",
    "answer": "げんえき",
    "meaning": "active duty, active service, student taking (university) entrance exams while still enrolled in scho"
  },
  {
    "question": "余程",
    "answer": "よほど",
    "meaning": "very, greatly, much, to a large extent, quite, just about to, almost, very nearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮廷",
    "answer": "きゅうてい",
    "meaning": "imperial court, royal court"
  },
  {
    "question": "認定",
    "answer": "にんてい",
    "meaning": "authorization, authorisation, acknowledgment, acknowledgement, certification, recognition"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮殿",
    "answer": "きゅうでん",
    "meaning": "palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄積",
    "answer": "ちくせき",
    "meaning": "accumulation, accumulate, store"
  },
  {
    "question": "一人一人",
    "answer": "ひとりひとり,ひとりびとり",
    "meaning": "each (person), individually, one by one, one at a time, in turn"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊園地",
    "answer": "ゆうえんち",
    "meaning": "amusement park"
  },
  {
    "question": "制度",
    "answer": "せいど",
    "meaning": "system, institution, organization, organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "大人びる",
    "answer": "おとなびる",
    "meaning": "to look (sound, behave) grown-up, to be adult-like, to mature"
  },
  {
    "question": "組み込む",
    "answer": "くみこむ",
    "meaning": "to insert, to include, to incorporate, to cut in (printing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "素質",
    "answer": "そしつ",
    "meaning": "makings (of), aptitude, talent, qualities, nature, character, temperament"
  },
  {
    "question": "不服",
    "answer": "ふふく",
    "meaning": "dissatisfaction, discontent, disapproval, objection, complaint, protest, disagreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "生身",
    "answer": "なまみ,しょうじん",
    "meaning": "living flesh, flesh and blood, physical body of Buddha or a bodhisattva"
  },
  {
    "question": "部位",
    "answer": "ぶい",
    "meaning": "part (esp. of the body), region, site, cut (of meat)"
  },
  {
    "question": "二重",
    "answer": "にじゅう,ふたえ",
    "meaning": "double, two-fold, two layers, duplex, diplo-, dipl-, double-edged eyelid, double eyelid, creased eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "継承",
    "answer": "けいしょう",
    "meaning": "inheritance, succession, accession, share-alike"
  },
  {
    "question": "分野",
    "answer": "ぶんや",
    "meaning": "field, sphere, realm, division, branch"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び回る",
    "answer": "とびまわる",
    "meaning": "to fly about, to skip about, to bustle about"
  },
  {
    "question": "監禁",
    "answer": "かんきん",
    "meaning": "confinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち目",
    "answer": "かちめ",
    "meaning": "chance (of success), odds"
  },
  {
    "question": "疑念",
    "answer": "ぎねん",
    "meaning": "doubt, suspicion, misgivings, scruples"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧しい",
    "answer": "まずしい",
    "meaning": "poor, needy, lacking (quantity and quality-wise), scanty, skimpy, slight, inadequate"
  },
  {
    "question": "反乱",
    "answer": "はんらん",
    "meaning": "insurrection, mutiny, rebellion, revolt, uprising"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕返し",
    "answer": "しかえし",
    "meaning": "payback, tit for tat, retaliation, revenge, doing over again, redoing"
  },
  {
    "question": "二枚",
    "answer": "にまい",
    "meaning": "two sheets (pieces) (of paper)"
  },
  {
    "question": "諦め",
    "answer": "あきらめ",
    "meaning": "resignation, acceptance, consolation"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦げる",
    "answer": "こげる",
    "meaning": "to burn, to scorch, to char, to singe"
  },
  {
    "question": "委ねる",
    "answer": "ゆだねる",
    "meaning": "to entrust (a matter) to, to leave to, to abandon oneself to (e.g. pleasure), to yield to (e.g. ange"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い至る",
    "answer": "おもいいたる",
    "meaning": "to realize, to realise, to hit upon something"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷気",
    "answer": "れいき",
    "meaning": "cold, chill, cold weather, cold wave, cold air"
  },
  {
    "question": "顔見知り",
    "answer": "かおみしり",
    "meaning": "acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び出し",
    "answer": "よびだし",
    "meaning": "call, summons, paging, curtain call, usher who calls the names of wrestlers, sweeps the ring, etc.,"
  },
  {
    "question": "私服",
    "answer": "しふく",
    "meaning": "civilian clothes, plain clothes, mufti, plainclothes police officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝統",
    "answer": "でんとう",
    "meaning": "tradition, convention"
  },
  {
    "question": "年月",
    "answer": "としつき,ねんげつ",
    "meaning": "months and years"
  },
  {
    "question": "身を引く",
    "answer": "みをひく",
    "meaning": "to resign, to abandon, to step aside, to back out of, to retire, to get away, to lean back, to back"
  },
  {
    "question": "援助",
    "answer": "えんじょ",
    "meaning": "assistance, aid, support"
  },
  {
    "question": "犠牲者",
    "answer": "ぎせいしゃ",
    "meaning": "victim"
  },
  {
    "question": "無念",
    "answer": "むねん",
    "meaning": "regret, chagrin, mortification, freedom from obstructive thoughts"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄り道",
    "answer": "よりみち",
    "meaning": "dropping in on the way, stopping off at, making a side trip, going the long way round, making a deto"
  },
  {
    "question": "強固",
    "answer": "きょうこ",
    "meaning": "firm, strong, solid, stable"
  },
  {
    "question": "晴らす",
    "answer": "はらす",
    "meaning": "to dispel, to clear away, to refresh (oneself), to accomplish a goal, to make it sunny, to make clou"
  },
  {
    "question": "来客",
    "answer": "らいきゃく,らいかく",
    "meaning": "visitor, caller"
  },
  {
    "question": "正真正銘",
    "answer": "しょうしんしょうめい",
    "meaning": "genuine, authentic, true, real"
  },
  {
    "question": "一心",
    "answer": "いっしん",
    "meaning": "one mind, wholeheartedness, one's whole heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "逝く",
    "answer": "いく,ゆく",
    "meaning": "to go, to move (in a direction or towards a specific location), to head (towards), to be transported"
  },
  {
    "question": "水音",
    "answer": "みずおと",
    "meaning": "sound of water"
  },
  {
    "question": "窓際",
    "answer": "まどぎわ",
    "meaning": "(at the) window"
  },
  {
    "question": "花弁",
    "answer": "はなびら,かべん",
    "meaning": "(flower) petal"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち消す",
    "answer": "うちけす",
    "meaning": "to deny, to contradict, to negate (esp. a sound), to drown out"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い合う",
    "answer": "いいあう",
    "meaning": "to say to each other, to exchange (jokes, comments, etc.), to quarrel, to dispute"
  },
  {
    "question": "客観的",
    "answer": "きゃっかんてき",
    "meaning": "objective"
  },
  {
    "question": "魔神",
    "answer": "まじん,ましん",
    "meaning": "devil, evil spirit, genie"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦々しい",
    "answer": "にがにがしい",
    "meaning": "unpleasant, disgusting, loathsome, shameful, scandalous"
  },
  {
    "question": "吉",
    "answer": "きち,きつ",
    "meaning": "good fortune (esp. omikuji fortune-telling result), good luck, auspiciousness, unspecified day of th"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝承",
    "answer": "でんしょう",
    "meaning": "handing down (information), legend, tradition, folklore, transmission"
  },
  {
    "question": "味見",
    "answer": "あじみ",
    "meaning": "tasting, sampling"
  },
  {
    "question": "離れ",
    "answer": "はなれ",
    "meaning": "detached building, solitary house, room detached from main house, separation from, loss of interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "締まる",
    "answer": "しまる",
    "meaning": "to be shut, to close, to be closed, to be firm (of a body, face, etc.), to be well-knit, to be locke"
  },
  {
    "question": "三階",
    "answer": "さんがい,さんかい",
    "meaning": "third floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "専属",
    "answer": "せんぞく",
    "meaning": "exclusive, attached to, specialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "罪人",
    "answer": "ざいにん,つみびと",
    "meaning": "criminal, lawbreaker, wrongdoer, offender, sinner, evildoer"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦闘力",
    "answer": "せんとうりょく",
    "meaning": "fighting strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱まる",
    "answer": "よわまる",
    "meaning": "to abate, to weaken, to be emaciated, to be dejected, to be perplexed"
  },
  {
    "question": "自動的",
    "answer": "じどうてき",
    "meaning": "automatic"
  },
  {
    "question": "分解",
    "answer": "ぶんかい",
    "meaning": "disassembly, dismantling, disaggregating, analysis, disintegrating, decomposing, degrading, factoriz"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き放す",
    "answer": "つきはなす",
    "meaning": "to push away, to thrust aside, to detach oneself from, to keep away from, to forsake, to abandon, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "交差",
    "answer": "こうさ",
    "meaning": "crossing, intersection, (genetic) crossing over"
  },
  {
    "question": "慰め",
    "answer": "なぐさめ",
    "meaning": "comfort, consolation, diversion"
  },
  {
    "question": "棘",
    "answer": "いばら,おどろ,とげ",
    "meaning": "thorny shrub, wild rose, briar, thorn, cusp, briars, thicket, the bush, spine, prickle, splinter (es"
  },
  {
    "question": "無料",
    "answer": "むりょう",
    "meaning": "free (of charge), gratuitous"
  },
  {
    "question": "敢えて",
    "answer": "あえて",
    "meaning": "purposely (of something needless, unexpected or seemingly counterproductive, etc.), daringly (doing"
  },
  {
    "question": "休息",
    "answer": "きゅうそく",
    "meaning": "rest, relief, relaxation"
  },
  {
    "question": "見受ける",
    "answer": "みうける",
    "meaning": "to catch sight of, to see, to suppose, to assume from appearances"
  },
  {
    "question": "撃破",
    "answer": "げきは",
    "meaning": "crushing"
  },
  {
    "question": "交わる",
    "answer": "まじわる",
    "meaning": "to cross, to intersect, to join, to meet, to associate with, to mingle with, to consort with, to hav"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し潰す",
    "answer": "おしつぶす",
    "meaning": "to squash, to crush, to flatten"
  },
  {
    "question": "制作",
    "answer": "せいさく",
    "meaning": "work (film, book), production, creation, turning (something) out, development"
  },
  {
    "question": "毛皮",
    "answer": "けがわ,もうひ",
    "meaning": "fur, skin, pelt, kanji 'fur' radical"
  },
  {
    "question": "返り討ち",
    "answer": "かえりうち",
    "meaning": "killing a would-be avenger, having the tables turned on someone (e.g. by a challenger), being beaten"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽る",
    "answer": "いつわる",
    "meaning": "to lie, to cheat, to pretend, to feign, to falsify, to trick, to deceive"
  },
  {
    "question": "小物",
    "answer": "こもの",
    "meaning": "accessories, small articles, minor character, small fry, weak one"
  },
  {
    "question": "健在",
    "answer": "けんざい",
    "meaning": "in good health, alive and well, going strong"
  },
  {
    "question": "逡巡",
    "answer": "しゅんじゅん",
    "meaning": "hesitation, indecision"
  },
  {
    "question": "連れ込む",
    "answer": "つれこむ",
    "meaning": "to bring (somebody into a place)"
  },
  {
    "question": "退院",
    "answer": "たいいん",
    "meaning": "leaving hospital, discharge from hospital"
  },
  {
    "question": "地形",
    "answer": "ちけい,じぎょう",
    "meaning": "terrain, geographical features, topography"
  },
  {
    "question": "建設",
    "answer": "けんせつ",
    "meaning": "construction, establishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "由来",
    "answer": "ゆらい",
    "meaning": "origin, source, history, derivation, originally, from the start, by nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "見苦しい",
    "answer": "みぐるしい",
    "meaning": "unsightly, ugly, unseemly, indecent, deplorable, disgraceful, shameful"
  },
  {
    "question": "民衆",
    "answer": "みんしゅう",
    "meaning": "people, populace, masses"
  },
  {
    "question": "直接的",
    "answer": "ちょくせつてき",
    "meaning": "direct"
  },
  {
    "question": "か細い",
    "answer": "かぼそい",
    "meaning": "thin, skinny, delicate, fragile, feeble"
  },
  {
    "question": "十六",
    "answer": "じゅうろく",
    "meaning": "16, sixteen"
  },
  {
    "question": "頃合い",
    "answer": "ころあい",
    "meaning": "suitable time, good time, propriety, moderation"
  },
  {
    "question": "支え",
    "answer": "ささえ,つかえ",
    "meaning": "support, stay, prop, load on one's chest, obstacle, hindrance, impediment, difficulty"
  },
  {
    "question": "生存",
    "answer": "せいぞん",
    "meaning": "existence, being, survival, to exist, to live, to survive"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び立つ",
    "answer": "とびたつ",
    "meaning": "to jump up, to start up, to leap to one's feet, to fly away, to take off"
  },
  {
    "question": "三本",
    "answer": "さんぼん",
    "meaning": "three (long cylindrical things), three-of-a-kind (in a dealt hand)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻影",
    "answer": "げんえい",
    "meaning": "phantom, vision, illusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "長ける",
    "answer": "たける",
    "meaning": "to excel at, to be proficient at, to grow old, to ripen, to rise high (e.g. the sun)"
  },
  {
    "question": "悲惨",
    "answer": "ひさん",
    "meaning": "disastrous, tragic, miserable, wretched, pitiful, woeful"
  },
  {
    "question": "懲りる",
    "answer": "こりる",
    "meaning": "to learn by experience, to learn one's lesson, to learn the hard way, to be discouraged (by), to hav"
  },
  {
    "question": "明ける",
    "answer": "あける",
    "meaning": "to empty, to remove, to make space, to make room, to move out, to clear out, to be away from (e.g. o"
  },
  {
    "question": "詮索",
    "answer": "せんさく",
    "meaning": "inquiry into, enquiry into, prying (into), investigation, search, exploration"
  },
  {
    "question": "京",
    "answer": "きょう,けい,みやこ",
    "meaning": "imperial capital (esp. Kyoto), final word of an iroha poem, 10^16, 10,000,000,000,000,000, ten quadr"
  },
  {
    "question": "返信",
    "answer": "へんしん",
    "meaning": "reply (e.g. email, fax, letter), answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "開閉",
    "answer": "かいへい",
    "meaning": "opening and shutting"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘆息",
    "answer": "たんそく",
    "meaning": "sigh (of grief, disappointment, etc.), grieving, lamenting, deploring"
  },
  {
    "question": "生々しい",
    "answer": "なまなましい",
    "meaning": "vivid (memory, description, etc.), fresh, graphic, raw, true-to-life, first-hand (experience), fresh"
  },
  {
    "question": "徹する",
    "answer": "てっする",
    "meaning": "to penetrate, to sink in, to devote oneself (to), to do intently and exclusively, to do throughout ("
  },
  {
    "question": "対戦",
    "answer": "たいせん",
    "meaning": "fighting (against), taking on (an opponent), facing, confronting, competing (with), battle, fight, c"
  },
  {
    "question": "一人前",
    "answer": "いちにんまえ,ひとりまえ",
    "meaning": "one portion, one serving, one person, adult, grown-up, person who has come of age, fully fledged, es"
  },
  {
    "question": "書斎",
    "answer": "しょさい",
    "meaning": "study, library, den, home office, reading room"
  },
  {
    "question": "休める",
    "answer": "やすめる",
    "meaning": "to rest, to suspend, to give relief"
  },
  {
    "question": "女子高生",
    "answer": "じょしこうせい",
    "meaning": "female high-school student"
  },
  {
    "question": "血筋",
    "answer": "ちすじ",
    "meaning": "lineage, stock, strain, blood relationship"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸ごと",
    "answer": "まるごと",
    "meaning": "in its entirety, whole, wholly"
  },
  {
    "question": "場違い",
    "answer": "ばちがい",
    "meaning": "out-of-place, inappropriate, sticking out like a sore thumb"
  },
  {
    "question": "成る",
    "answer": "なる",
    "meaning": "to become, to get, to grow, to be, to reach, to attain, to result in, to prove to be, to consist of,"
  },
  {
    "question": "某",
    "answer": "それがし,ぼう,なにがし",
    "meaning": "someone, unknown person, I, me, certain, one, certain amount, some, certain person, Mr So-and-so, a"
  },
  {
    "question": "土曜日",
    "answer": "どようび",
    "meaning": "Saturday"
  },
  {
    "question": "滑り込む",
    "answer": "すべりこむ",
    "meaning": "to slide into, to slip into"
  },
  {
    "question": "百年",
    "answer": "ひゃくねん,ももとせ",
    "meaning": "century, hundred years, a long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "援軍",
    "answer": "えんぐん",
    "meaning": "reinforcement"
  },
  {
    "question": "猶予",
    "answer": "ゆうよ",
    "meaning": "postponement, deferment, extension (of time)"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝見",
    "answer": "はいけん",
    "meaning": "seeing, looking at"
  },
  {
    "question": "特権",
    "answer": "とっけん",
    "meaning": "privilege, special right"
  },
  {
    "question": "委員会",
    "answer": "いいんかい",
    "meaning": "committee, commission, board, panel, committee meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き渡す",
    "answer": "ひきわたす",
    "meaning": "to deliver, to extradite, to stretch across, to hand over"
  },
  {
    "question": "洋服",
    "answer": "ようふく",
    "meaning": "Western-style clothes (cf. traditional Japanese clothes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "将",
    "answer": "しょう,はた",
    "meaning": "commander, general, leader, or, otherwise, furthermore, also, perhaps, by some chance, possibly, tha"
  },
  {
    "question": "思いきや",
    "answer": "おもいきや",
    "meaning": "contrary to expectations, or so we thought, but ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "斧",
    "answer": "おの,よき",
    "meaning": "axe, hatchet"
  },
  {
    "question": "形態",
    "answer": "けいたい",
    "meaning": "form, shape, figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "退散",
    "answer": "たいさん",
    "meaning": "dispersing, breaking up, running away"
  },
  {
    "question": "関与",
    "answer": "かんよ",
    "meaning": "participation, taking part in, participating in, being concerned in"
  },
  {
    "question": "人混み",
    "answer": "ひとごみ",
    "meaning": "crowd of people"
  },
  {
    "question": "大臣",
    "answer": "だいじん,おとど",
    "meaning": "cabinet minister, minister (of government), noble, nobleman's residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "授かる",
    "answer": "さずかる",
    "meaning": "to be awarded (e.g. a prize), to be given an award, to receive (e.g. a title), to be gifted or endow"
  },
  {
    "question": "見破る",
    "answer": "みやぶる",
    "meaning": "to see through (a plot, lie, etc.), to penetrate into, to discover, to find out"
  },
  {
    "question": "威圧",
    "answer": "いあつ",
    "meaning": "coercion, overpowering, to overpower, to overawe, to daunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "最小限",
    "answer": "さいしょうげん",
    "meaning": "minimum, lowest, minimal, least"
  },
  {
    "question": "鈍感",
    "answer": "どんかん",
    "meaning": "thickheaded, insensitive, dull, thick-skinned"
  },
  {
    "question": "恐らくは",
    "answer": "おそらくは",
    "meaning": "I fear that it's likely that, with all due respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "初期",
    "answer": "しょき",
    "meaning": "early (days), initial stage, initial"
  },
  {
    "question": "要する",
    "answer": "ようする",
    "meaning": "to need, to demand, to take, to require"
  },
  {
    "question": "水中",
    "answer": "すいちゅう",
    "meaning": "underwater"
  },
  {
    "question": "正門",
    "answer": "せいもん",
    "meaning": "main gate, main entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙遜",
    "answer": "けんそん",
    "meaning": "modesty, humility, being humble"
  },
  {
    "question": "無性に",
    "answer": "むしょうに",
    "meaning": "very much, intensely, overwhelmingly, excessively, irresistibly, without any obvious reason"
  },
  {
    "question": "適度",
    "answer": "てきど",
    "meaning": "moderate (degree), proper (amount), temperate, suitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "救急車",
    "answer": "きゅうきゅうしゃ",
    "meaning": "ambulance"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽装",
    "answer": "ぎそう",
    "meaning": "camouflage, disguise, pretense, feigning, masquerade"
  },
  {
    "question": "給仕",
    "answer": "きゅうじ",
    "meaning": "waiting on a table, serving (at dinner), waiter, waitress, waitperson, server, cabin boy, bellboy, p"
  },
  {
    "question": "早足",
    "answer": "はやあし",
    "meaning": "quick pace, quick steps, quick march, trot (horse gait)"
  },
  {
    "question": "艦隊",
    "answer": "かんたい",
    "meaning": "(naval) fleet, armada"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち入る",
    "answer": "たちいる",
    "meaning": "to enter, to trespass, to interfere, to meddle, to pry into"
  },
  {
    "question": "害",
    "answer": "がい",
    "meaning": "injury, harm, evil influence, damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "安易",
    "answer": "あんい",
    "meaning": "easy, simple, easygoing, lighthearted, simplistic, irresponsible, careless, quick (to do)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹴散らす",
    "answer": "けちらす",
    "meaning": "to kick about, to kick around, to scatter (a crowd, the enemy, etc.), to rout"
  },
  {
    "question": "異質",
    "answer": "いしつ",
    "meaning": "different (quality, nature), heterogeneous"
  },
  {
    "question": "今月",
    "answer": "こんげつ",
    "meaning": "this month"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り合う",
    "answer": "とりあう",
    "meaning": "to join (hands), to take (each other's hands), to scramble for, to struggle for, to fight for, to pa"
  },
  {
    "question": "採る",
    "answer": "とる",
    "meaning": "to adopt (method, proposal, etc.), to take (measure, course of action, etc.), to decide on, to pick"
  },
  {
    "question": "車両",
    "answer": "しゃりょう",
    "meaning": "rolling stock, railroad cars, wheeled vehicles"
  },
  {
    "question": "球体",
    "answer": "きゅうたい",
    "meaning": "sphere, globe, orb"
  },
  {
    "question": "雄叫び",
    "answer": "おたけび,おさけび",
    "meaning": "war cry, roar"
  },
  {
    "question": "粒子",
    "answer": "りゅうし",
    "meaning": "particle, grain"
  },
  {
    "question": "人通り",
    "answer": "ひとどおり",
    "meaning": "pedestrian traffic"
  },
  {
    "question": "面識",
    "answer": "めんしき",
    "meaning": "acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "喚く",
    "answer": "わめく",
    "meaning": "to shout, to cry, to scream, to clamour"
  },
  {
    "question": "味付け",
    "answer": "あじつけ",
    "meaning": "seasoning, flavour, flavor"
  },
  {
    "question": "格闘",
    "answer": "かくとう",
    "meaning": "hand-to-hand fighting, grappling, scuffling"
  },
  {
    "question": "毎度",
    "answer": "まいど",
    "meaning": "each time, always, often, thank you for your continued patronage"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺る",
    "answer": "ゆる",
    "meaning": "to shake, to jolt, to rock (cradle), to swing"
  },
  {
    "question": "多",
    "answer": "た",
    "meaning": "multi-"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶大",
    "answer": "ぜつだい",
    "meaning": "tremendous, immense"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮説",
    "answer": "かせつ",
    "meaning": "hypothesis, supposition, assumption, tentative theory"
  },
  {
    "question": "端末",
    "answer": "たんまつ",
    "meaning": "terminal, computer terminal, information access device (smartphone, tablet, book-reader, etc.), end"
  },
  {
    "question": "尚",
    "answer": "なお",
    "meaning": "still, yet, more, still more, greater, further, as ..., like ..., furthermore, in addition, moreover"
  },
  {
    "question": "見舞う",
    "answer": "みまう",
    "meaning": "to ask after (someone's health), to visit, to attack, to strike, to meet with misfortune, to suffer"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒幕",
    "answer": "くろまく",
    "meaning": "black curtain, wirepuller, mastermind, backroom manipulator, éminence grise, power broker"
  },
  {
    "question": "久しい",
    "answer": "ひさしい",
    "meaning": "long (time that has passed), old (story)"
  },
  {
    "question": "伯",
    "answer": "はく",
    "meaning": "count, earl, chief official of the Department of Worship, eldest brother, Brazil, Brazilian"
  },
  {
    "question": "嚙む",
    "answer": "かむ",
    "meaning": "to bite, to chew, to gnaw, to masticate, to fumble one's words (esp. during a play, broadcast, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "失踪",
    "answer": "しっそう",
    "meaning": "disappearance, running away, going missing, absconding"
  },
  {
    "question": "体当たり",
    "answer": "たいあたり",
    "meaning": "ramming attack, hurling oneself (at), throwing oneself into (e.g. a role), going all out"
  },
  {
    "question": "刀身",
    "answer": "とうしん",
    "meaning": "knife blade, sword blade"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻息",
    "answer": "はないき,びそく",
    "meaning": "nasal breathing, breathing through one's nose, person's pleasure, excitement"
  },
  {
    "question": "座席",
    "answer": "ざせき",
    "meaning": "seat"
  },
  {
    "question": "原稿",
    "answer": "げんこう",
    "meaning": "manuscript, copy, draft, notes, contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "子猫",
    "answer": "こねこ",
    "meaning": "kitten, small cat"
  },
  {
    "question": "沿い",
    "answer": "ぞい",
    "meaning": "along"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗り気",
    "answer": "のりき",
    "meaning": "interest, eagerness, enthusiasm"
  },
  {
    "question": "閃く",
    "answer": "ひらめく,ひろめく",
    "meaning": "to flash (e.g. lightning), to flicker, to glitter, to sparkle, to gleam, to flutter (e.g. flag), to"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤らめる",
    "answer": "あからめる",
    "meaning": "to blush, to redden"
  },
  {
    "question": "点数",
    "answer": "てんすう",
    "meaning": "marks, points, score, grade, runs (baseball), number of items, number of articles"
  },
  {
    "question": "射程",
    "answer": "しゃてい",
    "meaning": "range (of a rifle, missile, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "州",
    "answer": "しゅう,す",
    "meaning": "state (US, Australia, India, Germany, etc.), province (e.g. Canada), canton (e.g. Switzerland), obla"
  },
  {
    "question": "孤立",
    "answer": "こりつ",
    "meaning": "isolation, being alone, being friendless"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊急事態",
    "answer": "きんきゅうじたい",
    "meaning": "state of emergency, emergency, crisis"
  },
  {
    "question": "周",
    "answer": "しゅう",
    "meaning": "Zhou dynasty (China, approx. 1046-256 BCE), Chou dynasty, perimeter, counter for laps or circuits"
  },
  {
    "question": "蕩ける",
    "answer": "とろける",
    "meaning": "to melt (and become soft or liquid), to be enchanted (by), to be charmed, to be bewitched"
  },
  {
    "question": "木製",
    "answer": "もくせい",
    "meaning": "wooden, made of wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬礼",
    "answer": "けいれい",
    "meaning": "salute, bow"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉱山",
    "answer": "こうざん",
    "meaning": "mine (ore)"
  },
  {
    "question": "演説",
    "answer": "えんぜつ",
    "meaning": "speech, address"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪気",
    "answer": "わるぎ,あっき,わるげ",
    "meaning": "ill will, malice, evil intent, nasty smelling air, noxious gas, evil 'ki', seeming bad"
  },
  {
    "question": "判別",
    "answer": "はんべつ",
    "meaning": "distinction, discrimination, distinguishing, discernment"
  },
  {
    "question": "不本意",
    "answer": "ふほんい",
    "meaning": "reluctant, unwilling, involuntary, unintentional, unintended, unlooked-for, disappointing"
  },
  {
    "question": "数値",
    "answer": "すうち",
    "meaning": "numerical value, numerics, reading (on a meter, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "分身",
    "answer": "ぶんしん,ぶんじん",
    "meaning": "other self, alter ego, part of oneself (in someone or something else), representation of oneself, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "現金",
    "answer": "げんきん",
    "meaning": "cash, ready money, money on hand, currency, mercenary, self-interested, calculating"
  },
  {
    "question": "第三者",
    "answer": "だいさんしゃ",
    "meaning": "third party, third person, outsider, disinterested person"
  },
  {
    "question": "運び込む",
    "answer": "はこびこむ",
    "meaning": "to carry in, to bring in"
  },
  {
    "question": "今週",
    "answer": "こんしゅう",
    "meaning": "this week"
  },
  {
    "question": "良好",
    "answer": "りょうこう",
    "meaning": "good, fine, excellent, favorable, favourable, satisfactory"
  },
  {
    "question": "部品",
    "answer": "ぶひん",
    "meaning": "parts, accessories, components"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り巻く",
    "answer": "とりまく",
    "meaning": "to surround, to encircle, to enclose"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗をかく",
    "answer": "あせをかく",
    "meaning": "to perspire, to sweat"
  },
  {
    "question": "生き残り",
    "answer": "いきのこり",
    "meaning": "survival, survivor, relic"
  },
  {
    "question": "因縁",
    "answer": "いんねん,いんえん",
    "meaning": "fate, destiny, connection, tie, bond, origin, pretext, justification, hetu and prataya (direct cause"
  },
  {
    "question": "編む",
    "answer": "あむ",
    "meaning": "to knit, to plait, to braid, to compile (anthology, dictionary, etc.), to edit"
  },
  {
    "question": "連なる",
    "answer": "つらなる",
    "meaning": "to extend, to stretch out, to stand in a row, to attend, to participate in, to enrol, to enroll, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "談笑",
    "answer": "だんしょう",
    "meaning": "friendly chat, pleasant chat, lighthearted talk, friendly conversation"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤子",
    "answer": "あかご,せきし",
    "meaning": "baby, subject, people"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭が痛い",
    "answer": "あたまがいたい",
    "meaning": "having a headache, racking one's brains, troubling over something"
  },
  {
    "question": "遡る",
    "answer": "さかのぼる",
    "meaning": "to go upstream, to go back (in time, to origin), to date back to, to trace back to, to make retroact"
  },
  {
    "question": "躊躇い",
    "answer": "ためらい",
    "meaning": "faltering, hesitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "本能的",
    "answer": "ほんのうてき",
    "meaning": "instinctive, instinctual"
  },
  {
    "question": "富",
    "answer": "とみ",
    "meaning": "riches, wealth, fortune, resources, lottery"
  },
  {
    "question": "憂い",
    "answer": "うい,うれい",
    "meaning": "unhappy, sad, gloomy, sorrow, grief, anguish, distress, trouble, affliction, anxiety, fear, misgivin"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙袋",
    "answer": "かみぶくろ,かんぶくろ",
    "meaning": "paper bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠巻き",
    "answer": "とおまき",
    "meaning": "surrounding at a distance"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡霊",
    "answer": "ぼうれい",
    "meaning": "departed spirit, soul of the dead, ghost, apparition"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼球",
    "answer": "がんきゅう",
    "meaning": "eyeball"
  },
  {
    "question": "前半",
    "answer": "ぜんはん,ぜんぱん",
    "meaning": "first half"
  },
  {
    "question": "奢る",
    "answer": "おごる",
    "meaning": "to give (someone) a treat, to be extravagant, to live luxuriously, to be proud, to be haughty"
  },
  {
    "question": "影響力",
    "answer": "えいきょうりょく",
    "meaning": "influence, clout, leverage"
  },
  {
    "question": "片腕",
    "answer": "かたうで",
    "meaning": "one arm, one's right-hand man, one's right hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "化ける",
    "answer": "ばける,ふける",
    "meaning": "to take the form of (esp. in ref. to a spirit, fox, raccoon dog, etc.), to assume the shape of, to t"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞踏会",
    "answer": "ぶとうかい",
    "meaning": "ball, dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "割く",
    "answer": "さく",
    "meaning": "to cut up, to cleave, to cut open (esp. the abdomen), to spare (time, money, etc.), to use part of s"
  },
  {
    "question": "事業",
    "answer": "じぎょう,ことわざ",
    "meaning": "project, enterprise, business, industry, operations, venture, service, act, deed, conduct"
  },
  {
    "question": "留学",
    "answer": "りゅうがく",
    "meaning": "studying abroad"
  },
  {
    "question": "怒声",
    "answer": "どせい",
    "meaning": "angry voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "云々",
    "answer": "うんぬん",
    "meaning": "and so on, and so forth, et cetera, and such, and the like, comment, criticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "見送り",
    "answer": "みおくり",
    "meaning": "seeing one off, farewell, escort"
  },
  {
    "question": "歪み",
    "answer": "ひずみ,ゆがみ,いがみ",
    "meaning": "strain, deformation, warp, distortion, harmful effects, stress, imbalance, contortion, bend, skew, k"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り上げ",
    "answer": "うりあげ",
    "meaning": "amount sold, sales, proceeds, takings, turnover"
  },
  {
    "question": "収入",
    "answer": "しゅうにゅう",
    "meaning": "income, receipts, revenue"
  },
  {
    "question": "生前",
    "answer": "せいぜん",
    "meaning": "while alive, during one's lifetime"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾つも",
    "answer": "いくつも",
    "meaning": "many, much, plenty, hardly"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り取る",
    "answer": "きりとる",
    "meaning": "to cut off, to excise, to tear off, to cut out, to whittle down, to tear out, to cut down, to amputa"
  },
  {
    "question": "苛む",
    "answer": "さいなむ",
    "meaning": "to torment, to torture, to harass"
  },
  {
    "question": "手綱",
    "answer": "たづな",
    "meaning": "reins, bridle, control, the reins (on)"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し入れ",
    "answer": "さしいれ",
    "meaning": "insertion, letter drop, things sent to a prisoner, supply of provisions, refreshments, etc. to someo"
  },
  {
    "question": "差別",
    "answer": "さべつ,しゃべつ,しゃべち",
    "meaning": "distinction, differentiation, discrimination, discrimination (against people)"
  },
  {
    "question": "元凶",
    "answer": "げんきょう,がんきょう",
    "meaning": "ringleader, main culprit, main cause, source"
  },
  {
    "question": "石畳",
    "answer": "いしだたみ",
    "meaning": "stone paving, cobble paving, sett, flagstone, stone steps, check (pattern), pavé, rectangular desser"
  },
  {
    "question": "足す",
    "answer": "たす",
    "meaning": "to add (numbers), to add (something), to top up (with something), to take care of (e.g. one's busine"
  },
  {
    "question": "直々",
    "answer": "じきじき,なおなお",
    "meaning": "in person, personally, directly, straight, ordinary, common, obedient, meek, gentle, calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "吐き気",
    "answer": "はきけ",
    "meaning": "nausea, sickness in the stomach"
  },
  {
    "question": "塀",
    "answer": "へい",
    "meaning": "wall, fence"
  },
  {
    "question": "娯楽",
    "answer": "ごらく",
    "meaning": "pleasure, amusement"
  },
  {
    "question": "近隣",
    "answer": "きんりん",
    "meaning": "neighbourhood, neighborhood, vicinity"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り巻き",
    "answer": "とりまき",
    "meaning": "followers, hangers-on"
  },
  {
    "question": "目配せ",
    "answer": "めくばせ",
    "meaning": "signalling with the eyes, exchanging looks, winking"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝敗",
    "answer": "しょうはい",
    "meaning": "victory or defeat, issue (of battle), outcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪",
    "answer": "よこしま,じゃ",
    "meaning": "wicked, evil, wickedness, wicked person"
  },
  {
    "question": "物陰",
    "answer": "ものかげ",
    "meaning": "place hidden from view, cover, shelter, hiding place"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧迫",
    "answer": "あっぱく",
    "meaning": "pressure, oppression, suppression"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾燥",
    "answer": "かんそう",
    "meaning": "dryness, aridity, drying (e.g. clothes), dehydration, desiccation, insipidity"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち誇る",
    "answer": "かちほこる",
    "meaning": "to triumph, to be elated with success"
  },
  {
    "question": "接点",
    "answer": "せってん",
    "meaning": "tangent point, point of contact, contact (electrical, etc.), point of agreement, common ground, inte"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し切る",
    "answer": "おしきる",
    "meaning": "to overcome (opposition), to push past, to force one's way, to press and cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "専門家",
    "answer": "せんもんか",
    "meaning": "specialist, expert, professional, authority, pundit"
  },
  {
    "question": "対価",
    "answer": "たいか",
    "meaning": "compensation, equivalent value, consideration"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻歌",
    "answer": "はなうた",
    "meaning": "humming, crooning"
  },
  {
    "question": "台無し",
    "answer": "だいなし",
    "meaning": "mess, spoiled, spoilt, (come to) nothing, ruin"
  },
  {
    "question": "絡まる",
    "answer": "からまる",
    "meaning": "to be entwined, to be involved"
  },
  {
    "question": "反抗",
    "answer": "はんこう",
    "meaning": "opposition, resistance, insubordination, defiance, hostility, rebellion"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦悶",
    "answer": "くもん",
    "meaning": "anguish"
  },
  {
    "question": "先走る",
    "answer": "さきばしる",
    "meaning": "to be forward, to be impertinent"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い返す",
    "answer": "おいかえす",
    "meaning": "to drive away, to turn away, to send away, to repel, to repulse"
  },
  {
    "question": "下級",
    "answer": "かきゅう",
    "meaning": "lower grade, low class, junior (officer)"
  },
  {
    "question": "単独",
    "answer": "たんどく",
    "meaning": "sole, single, solo, independence, singleness, singularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "狼狽",
    "answer": "ろうばい",
    "meaning": "confusion, dismay, consternation, panic"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪党",
    "answer": "あくとう",
    "meaning": "scoundrel, rascal, villain"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌声",
    "answer": "うたごえ,かせい",
    "meaning": "singing voice, (sound of) singing"
  },
  {
    "question": "思想",
    "answer": "しそう",
    "meaning": "thought, idea, ideology"
  },
  {
    "question": "競う",
    "answer": "きそう",
    "meaning": "to compete, to contend, to vie, to contest"
  },
  {
    "question": "変形",
    "answer": "へんけい",
    "meaning": "transformation, variation, metamorphosis, modification, deformation, variety, deformity, monster"
  },
  {
    "question": "擦れる",
    "answer": "かすれる,すれる,こすれる",
    "meaning": "to get blurred, to get hoarse, to get husky, to graze, to scrape, to touch, to rub, to chafe, to wea"
  },
  {
    "question": "不",
    "answer": "ふ,ぶ",
    "meaning": "un-, non-, negative prefix, bad ..., poor ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "人間関係",
    "answer": "にんげんかんけい",
    "meaning": "human relations, personal relationships"
  },
  {
    "question": "信者",
    "answer": "しんじゃ",
    "meaning": "believer, adherent, devotee"
  },
  {
    "question": "微動",
    "answer": "びどう",
    "meaning": "slight movement, slight tremor, quiver"
  },
  {
    "question": "運転手",
    "answer": "うんてんしゅ",
    "meaning": "driver, chauffeur"
  },
  {
    "question": "誠意",
    "answer": "せいい",
    "meaning": "sincerity, good faith"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒げる",
    "answer": "あらげる",
    "meaning": "to roughen (e.g. one's attitude), to raise (one's voice)"
  },
  {
    "question": "野生",
    "answer": "やせい",
    "meaning": "wild, growing wild, living in the wild, I"
  },
  {
    "question": "宙に浮く",
    "answer": "ちゅうにうく",
    "meaning": "to float in the air, to be unfinished, to be unsettled, to be undecided"
  },
  {
    "question": "権",
    "answer": "けん",
    "meaning": "right (to do something), authority, power"
  },
  {
    "question": "進歩",
    "answer": "しんぽ",
    "meaning": "progress, advance, improvement, development"
  },
  {
    "question": "海賊",
    "answer": "かいぞく",
    "meaning": "pirate, sea robber, buccaneer, freebooter"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き叫ぶ",
    "answer": "なきさけぶ",
    "meaning": "to cry and shout, to scream"
  },
  {
    "question": "家柄",
    "answer": "いえがら",
    "meaning": "social standing of a family, lineage, parentage, pedigree, good family"
  },
  {
    "question": "掲示板",
    "answer": "けいじばん",
    "meaning": "bulletin board, display board, notice board, electronic bulletin board, BBS"
  },
  {
    "question": "生命力",
    "answer": "せいめいりょく",
    "meaning": "vitality, (one's) life force"
  },
  {
    "question": "脈打つ",
    "answer": "みゃくうつ",
    "meaning": "to pound (e.g. heart), to pulse (e.g. vein), to pulsate"
  },
  {
    "question": "限度",
    "answer": "げんど",
    "meaning": "limit, bounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "主な",
    "answer": "おもな",
    "meaning": "chief, main, principal, important"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁忌",
    "answer": "きんき",
    "meaning": "taboo, day, time, direction, words, etc. that must be avoided, contraindication"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃墟",
    "answer": "はいきょ",
    "meaning": "ruins, abandoned building"
  },
  {
    "question": "手を抜く",
    "answer": "てをぬく",
    "meaning": "to cut corners, to be shoddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "行",
    "answer": "ぎょう,こう",
    "meaning": "line (of text), row, verse, carya (austerities), samskara (formations), semi-cursive style (of writi"
  },
  {
    "question": "波打つ",
    "answer": "なみうつ",
    "meaning": "to dash against (of waves), to billow, to roll, to wave (e.g. in the wind), to heave, to pound (of a"
  },
  {
    "question": "見込み",
    "answer": "みこみ",
    "meaning": "hope, promise, possibility, chance, probability, likelihood, expectation, anticipation, forecast, es"
  },
  {
    "question": "轟く",
    "answer": "とどろく",
    "meaning": "to roar, to reverberate, to be well-known, to be famous, to palpitate, to throb"
  },
  {
    "question": "読み",
    "answer": "よみ",
    "meaning": "reading, reading (of a kanji, esp. kun reading), reading (e.g. of a situation), insight, judgment, i"
  },
  {
    "question": "車内",
    "answer": "しゃない",
    "meaning": "inside a car (train, bus, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "使い道",
    "answer": "つかいみち",
    "meaning": "purpose, utility, objective, way to use something"
  },
  {
    "question": "就く",
    "answer": "つく",
    "meaning": "to take (seat, position, course, office, etc.), to assume, to be hired, to be employed, to ascend (t"
  },
  {
    "question": "上層部",
    "answer": "じょうそうぶ",
    "meaning": "top brass, upper echelon, higher-ups, top management, upper reaches, top of the pile"
  },
  {
    "question": "早まる",
    "answer": "はやまる",
    "meaning": "to be brought forward (e.g. by three hours), to be moved up, to be advanced, to be hasty, to be rash"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治家",
    "answer": "せいじか",
    "meaning": "politician, statesman"
  },
  {
    "question": "嵌める",
    "answer": "はめる",
    "meaning": "to insert, to put in (such that there is a snug fit), to button, to put on (something that envelops,"
  },
  {
    "question": "口を出す",
    "answer": "くちをだす",
    "meaning": "to interrupt, to interfere, to meddle, to intrude, to butt in, to poke one's nose into"
  },
  {
    "question": "義母",
    "answer": "ぎぼ",
    "meaning": "mother-in-law, foster mother, step mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "風呂場",
    "answer": "ふろば",
    "meaning": "bathroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "迎え撃つ",
    "answer": "むかえうつ",
    "meaning": "to meet (the enemy) and attack, to engage (the approaching enemy), to confront, to intercept"
  },
  {
    "question": "医療",
    "answer": "いりょう",
    "meaning": "medical care, medical treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "有力",
    "answer": "ゆうりょく",
    "meaning": "influential, prominent, strong, likely, plausible, potent"
  },
  {
    "question": "推す",
    "answer": "おす",
    "meaning": "to recommend, to endorse (e.g. a candidate), to nominate, to support, to back, to infer (from), to d"
  },
  {
    "question": "強",
    "answer": "きょう",
    "meaning": "a little over, a little more than, powerhouse, one of the biggest, one of the most powerful"
  },
  {
    "question": "週間",
    "answer": "しゅうかん",
    "meaning": "week"
  },
  {
    "question": "全い",
    "answer": "まったい,またい",
    "meaning": "complete, whole, perfect, entire, safe"
  },
  {
    "question": "大喜び",
    "answer": "おおよろこび",
    "meaning": "great joy"
  },
  {
    "question": "井戸",
    "answer": "いど",
    "meaning": "water well"
  },
  {
    "question": "自我",
    "answer": "じが",
    "meaning": "self, the ego"
  },
  {
    "question": "当面",
    "answer": "とうめん",
    "meaning": "current, urgent, pressing, impending, to confront (an issue), to face (up to something), for the mea"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い張る",
    "answer": "いいはる",
    "meaning": "to insist, to assert, to be obstinate in saying"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁る",
    "answer": "あさる,すなどる,いさる",
    "meaning": "to fish, to look for, to search for, to hunt for, to scavenge, to scrounge, to look through, to rumm"
  },
  {
    "question": "独身",
    "answer": "どくしん",
    "meaning": "bachelorhood, single, unmarried, celibate"
  },
  {
    "question": "食後",
    "answer": "しょくご",
    "meaning": "after a meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "拡散",
    "answer": "かくさん",
    "meaning": "scattering, diffusion, spread (e.g. signal across the spectrum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "健全",
    "answer": "けんぜん",
    "meaning": "healthy, sound, wholesome"
  },
  {
    "question": "笑い出す",
    "answer": "わらいだす",
    "meaning": "to burst into laughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "恨めしい",
    "answer": "うらめしい",
    "meaning": "reproachful, hateful, bitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "遂行",
    "answer": "すいこう",
    "meaning": "accomplishment, execution"
  },
  {
    "question": "領土",
    "answer": "りょうど",
    "meaning": "dominion, territory, possession"
  },
  {
    "question": "簡潔",
    "answer": "かんけつ",
    "meaning": "concise, brief, succinct, compact (style)"
  },
  {
    "question": "看護師",
    "answer": "かんごし",
    "meaning": "(hospital) nurse, registered nurse, RN"
  },
  {
    "question": "克服",
    "answer": "こくふく",
    "meaning": "conquest (of a difficulty, illness, handicap, etc.), overcoming, bringing under control, subjugation"
  },
  {
    "question": "情け",
    "answer": "なさけ",
    "meaning": "pity, sympathy, compassion, mercy, affection, love"
  },
  {
    "question": "慣れ",
    "answer": "なれ",
    "meaning": "practice, practising, experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "電源",
    "answer": "でんげん",
    "meaning": "source of electricity, electrical power, power (button on TV, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "適性",
    "answer": "てきせい",
    "meaning": "aptitude, aptness, suitability"
  },
  {
    "question": "互角",
    "answer": "ごかく",
    "meaning": "equal (in ability), even, evenly matched, well-matched, on par (with)"
  },
  {
    "question": "家庭教師",
    "answer": "かていきょうし",
    "meaning": "private tutor, coach, governess"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂",
    "answer": "きょう",
    "meaning": "(some type of) enthusiast, somebody possessed of a (certain kind of) mental abnormality"
  },
  {
    "question": "競争",
    "answer": "きょうそう",
    "meaning": "competition, contest, rivalry, race, competition (between organisms or species)"
  },
  {
    "question": "同席",
    "answer": "どうせき",
    "meaning": "presence, sitting with, being with"
  },
  {
    "question": "溢れ出る",
    "answer": "あふれでる",
    "meaning": "to overflow from something full"
  },
  {
    "question": "満喫",
    "answer": "まんきつ",
    "meaning": "having enough of (food, drink, etc.), having one's fill, fully enjoying"
  },
  {
    "question": "疑わしい",
    "answer": "うたがわしい",
    "meaning": "doubtful, questionable, uncertain, disputable, suspicious"
  },
  {
    "question": "ど真ん中",
    "answer": "どまんなか",
    "meaning": "right in the center (centre)"
  },
  {
    "question": "殺到",
    "answer": "さっとう",
    "meaning": "rush, flood, deluge"
  },
  {
    "question": "応答",
    "answer": "おうとう",
    "meaning": "reply, answer, response"
  },
  {
    "question": "腕力",
    "answer": "わんりょく",
    "meaning": "physical strength, brute strength, arm strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "挙句",
    "answer": "あげく",
    "meaning": "after (a long process), at the end of, last line (of a renga)"
  },
  {
    "question": "同胞",
    "answer": "どうほう,どうぼう,はらから",
    "meaning": "brethren, brothers, fellow countrymen, fellowman, compatriot"
  },
  {
    "question": "精鋭",
    "answer": "せいえい",
    "meaning": "elite, best, pick, cream of the crop"
  },
  {
    "question": "遂に",
    "answer": "ついに",
    "meaning": "finally, at last, in the end, after all, never (happened)"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦悩",
    "answer": "くのう",
    "meaning": "(mental) agony, anguish, suffering, distress"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆破",
    "answer": "ばくは",
    "meaning": "destructive blast, blowing up, explosion"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻",
    "answer": "まき,かん",
    "meaning": "roll (e.g. of cloth), winding (e.g. watch), volume (of book), speeding up, heel (of a Japanese sanda"
  },
  {
    "question": "断罪",
    "answer": "だんざい",
    "meaning": "judgment (of a crime), conviction, condemnation, beheading, decapitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "殿方",
    "answer": "とのがた,とのかた",
    "meaning": "gentlemen, men, the men's (sign on toilet, bathroom, etc. doors)"
  },
  {
    "question": "記者",
    "answer": "きしゃ",
    "meaning": "reporter, journalist"
  },
  {
    "question": "反響",
    "answer": "はんきょう",
    "meaning": "echo, reverberation, response, reaction, repercussions, sensation, influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "逸れる",
    "answer": "それる,はぐれる",
    "meaning": "to turn away, to bear off, to veer away, to swerve from, to miss (e.g. a target), to deviate (e.g. o"
  },
  {
    "question": "恰好",
    "answer": "かっこう,かっこ",
    "meaning": "shape, form, figure, posture, pose, appearance, state, situation, suitable, fit, reasonable, about"
  },
  {
    "question": "尚更",
    "answer": "なおさら",
    "meaning": "still more, even more, all the more, still less, even less"
  },
  {
    "question": "恐るべき",
    "answer": "おそるべき",
    "meaning": "dreadful, terrible, horrible, deplorable, fearsome, formidable, awesome, redoubtable"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち砕く",
    "answer": "うちくだく,ぶちくだく",
    "meaning": "to smash, to crush"
  },
  {
    "question": "宥める",
    "answer": "なだめる",
    "meaning": "to soothe, to calm, to pacify"
  },
  {
    "question": "酸素",
    "answer": "さんそ",
    "meaning": "oxygen (O)"
  },
  {
    "question": "無残",
    "answer": "むざん",
    "meaning": "cruel, merciless, atrocious, ruthless, cold-blooded, pitiful, tragic, horrible, miserable"
  },
  {
    "question": "判定",
    "answer": "はんてい",
    "meaning": "judgement, judgment, decision, adjudication, award, verdict, determination"
  },
  {
    "question": "急所",
    "answer": "きゅうしょ,きゅうじょ",
    "meaning": "vital part (of the body), tender spot, weak point, vitals, key point, essential point, crux (of a pr"
  },
  {
    "question": "最奥",
    "answer": "さいおう",
    "meaning": "deep inside, innermost place"
  },
  {
    "question": "目尻",
    "answer": "めじり",
    "meaning": "outer canthus, outer corner of the eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "実質",
    "answer": "じっしつ",
    "meaning": "substance, essence, real (in economics, vs. nominal, e.g. real interest rate), substantive, substant"
  },
  {
    "question": "特徴的",
    "answer": "とくちょうてき",
    "meaning": "characteristic"
  },
  {
    "question": "子達",
    "answer": "こたち",
    "meaning": "children"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼女",
    "answer": "ようじょ",
    "meaning": "little girl"
  },
  {
    "question": "資質",
    "answer": "ししつ",
    "meaning": "nature, disposition, temperament, qualities, attributes, talents"
  },
  {
    "question": "間柄",
    "answer": "あいだがら",
    "meaning": "relationship, relation, terms (good, friendly, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "恍惚",
    "answer": "こうこつ",
    "meaning": "ecstasy, rapture, trance, senility"
  },
  {
    "question": "口角",
    "answer": "こうかく",
    "meaning": "corners of the mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "迅速",
    "answer": "じんそく",
    "meaning": "quick, fast, rapid, swift, prompt, streamlined, expedited, expeditious"
  },
  {
    "question": "適する",
    "answer": "てきする",
    "meaning": "to fit, to suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "親族",
    "answer": "しんぞく,うから",
    "meaning": "relative, relation, blood relative"
  },
  {
    "question": "極限",
    "answer": "きょくげん",
    "meaning": "utmost limits, extremity, limit"
  },
  {
    "question": "損傷",
    "answer": "そんしょう",
    "meaning": "damage, injury"
  },
  {
    "question": "退学",
    "answer": "たいがく",
    "meaning": "dropping out of school, withdrawing from school, expulsion from school, dismissal, leaving school (u"
  },
  {
    "question": "意向",
    "answer": "いこう",
    "meaning": "intention, idea, inclination, wish"
  },
  {
    "question": "立て続け",
    "answer": "たてつづけ",
    "meaning": "succession, continuation, series, sequence"
  },
  {
    "question": "世間話",
    "answer": "せけんばなし",
    "meaning": "small talk, chat, gossip"
  },
  {
    "question": "裁く",
    "answer": "さばく",
    "meaning": "to judge, to decide, to sit in judgement, to try"
  },
  {
    "question": "少数",
    "answer": "しょうすう",
    "meaning": "small number, few, minority"
  },
  {
    "question": "二十歳",
    "answer": "はたち,はたとせ",
    "meaning": "20 years old, twenty years"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝台",
    "answer": "しんだい,ねだい",
    "meaning": "bed, couch"
  },
  {
    "question": "摑む",
    "answer": "つかむ",
    "meaning": "to seize, to catch, to grasp, to grip, to grab, to clutch, to hold, to catch hold of, to lay one's h"
  },
  {
    "question": "禍々しい",
    "answer": "まがまがしい",
    "meaning": "ominous, sinister, unlucky, ill-omened, annoying, appearing to be true, plausible"
  },
  {
    "question": "万人",
    "answer": "ばんにん,ばんじん,まんにん",
    "meaning": "all people, everybody, ten thousand people"
  },
  {
    "question": "作動",
    "answer": "さどう",
    "meaning": "operation, functioning, running"
  },
  {
    "question": "清潔",
    "answer": "せいけつ",
    "meaning": "clean, hygienic, sanitary, pure, virtuous, immaculate"
  },
  {
    "question": "大男",
    "answer": "おおおとこ",
    "meaning": "big man, large man, tall man, giant"
  },
  {
    "question": "花束",
    "answer": "はなたば",
    "meaning": "bunch of flowers, bouquet"
  },
  {
    "question": "賊",
    "answer": "あだ,ぞく",
    "meaning": "foe, enemy, rival, resentment, enmity, grudge, harm, injury, thief, robber, burglar, rebel, insurgen"
  },
  {
    "question": "合宿",
    "answer": "がっしゅく",
    "meaning": "lodging together, training camp, boarding house"
  },
  {
    "question": "数多",
    "answer": "あまた,すうた",
    "meaning": "many, a lot, much, multitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "空白",
    "answer": "くうはく",
    "meaning": "blank space (in documents), vacuum, blank, void"
  },
  {
    "question": "詫びる",
    "answer": "わびる",
    "meaning": "to apologize, to apologise"
  },
  {
    "question": "出撃",
    "answer": "しゅつげき",
    "meaning": "sortie, sally, attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒々しい",
    "answer": "あらあらしい",
    "meaning": "rough, wild, rude, harsh, gruff, violent"
  },
  {
    "question": "巡回",
    "answer": "じゅんかい",
    "meaning": "going around, patrol, round, tour"
  },
  {
    "question": "永久",
    "answer": "えいきゅう,とこしえ,とわ",
    "meaning": "eternity, permanence, perpetuity, Eikyū era (1113.7.13-1118.4.3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "喜ばしい",
    "answer": "よろこばしい",
    "meaning": "delightful, joyous, joyful, happy, desirable, welcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "至急",
    "answer": "しきゅう",
    "meaning": "urgent, pressing, immediate, prompt, express, urgently, promptly, at once, right away, without delay"
  },
  {
    "question": "参考",
    "answer": "さんこう",
    "meaning": "reference, consultation"
  },
  {
    "question": "視覚",
    "answer": "しかく",
    "meaning": "sense of sight, vision"
  },
  {
    "question": "無茶苦茶",
    "answer": "むちゃくちゃ",
    "meaning": "nonsensical, unreasonable, absurd, unrealistic, awfully, extremely, to excess, senseless, reckless,"
  },
  {
    "question": "飼い主",
    "answer": "かいぬし",
    "meaning": "(pet) owner, keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿命",
    "answer": "しゅくめい",
    "meaning": "fate, destiny, predestination"
  },
  {
    "question": "先月",
    "answer": "せんげつ",
    "meaning": "last month"
  },
  {
    "question": "視力",
    "answer": "しりょく",
    "meaning": "eyesight, vision, visual acuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "上達",
    "answer": "じょうたつ",
    "meaning": "improvement (e.g. in skill, ability), advance, progress, communication of opinions of the general po"
  },
  {
    "question": "射る",
    "answer": "いる",
    "meaning": "to shoot (arrow, bolt, dart)"
  },
  {
    "question": "公表",
    "answer": "こうひょう",
    "meaning": "official announcement, proclamation"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃げ回る",
    "answer": "にげまわる",
    "meaning": "to run around trying to escape, to run from place to place"
  },
  {
    "question": "数回",
    "answer": "すうかい",
    "meaning": "several times, a few times"
  },
  {
    "question": "直視",
    "answer": "ちょくし",
    "meaning": "looking someone in the eyes, taking a straight look at something"
  },
  {
    "question": "折",
    "answer": "おり",
    "meaning": "opportunity, chance, occasion, time, folding, fold, pleat, crease, small food box (wooden or cardboa"
  },
  {
    "question": "釘付け",
    "answer": "くぎづけ",
    "meaning": "nailing on, nailing down, nailing shut, being glued (to), being unable to take one's eyes (from), be"
  },
  {
    "question": "交際",
    "answer": "こうさい",
    "meaning": "company, friendship, association, society, acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "細長い",
    "answer": "ほそながい",
    "meaning": "long and narrow"
  },
  {
    "question": "隔離",
    "answer": "かくり",
    "meaning": "isolation, segregation, separation, quarantine"
  },
  {
    "question": "一閃",
    "answer": "いっせん",
    "meaning": "flash, brandish"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀行",
    "answer": "ぎんこう",
    "meaning": "bank, banking institution"
  },
  {
    "question": "大学生",
    "answer": "だいがくせい",
    "meaning": "university student, college student"
  },
  {
    "question": "被せる",
    "answer": "かぶせる",
    "meaning": "to cover (with something), to put on (e.g. on someone else's head), to plate something (with a metal"
  },
  {
    "question": "来月",
    "answer": "らいげつ",
    "meaning": "next month"
  },
  {
    "question": "社交界",
    "answer": "しゃこうかい",
    "meaning": "high society"
  },
  {
    "question": "移行",
    "answer": "いこう",
    "meaning": "switching over to, migration, transition"
  },
  {
    "question": "熟練",
    "answer": "じゅくれん",
    "meaning": "skill, dexterity, proficiency"
  },
  {
    "question": "舌先",
    "answer": "したさき",
    "meaning": "tip of tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽口",
    "answer": "かるくち",
    "meaning": "talkative, loose-lipped, persiflage, frivolous talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "葬る",
    "answer": "ほうむる,ほうぶる",
    "meaning": "to bury, to inter, to entomb, to cover up, to hush up, to shelve"
  },
  {
    "question": "噂話",
    "answer": "うわさばなし",
    "meaning": "gossip"
  },
  {
    "question": "畳む",
    "answer": "たたむ",
    "meaning": "to fold (clothes, umbrella), to close (a shop, business), to vacate"
  },
  {
    "question": "多大",
    "answer": "ただい",
    "meaning": "great (quantity, amount, etc.), huge, enormous, serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕上げ",
    "answer": "しあげ",
    "meaning": "finish, finishing, finishing touches"
  },
  {
    "question": "っ子",
    "answer": "っこ",
    "meaning": "someone with a liking or characteristic, a true representative of (place)"
  },
  {
    "question": "知",
    "answer": "ち",
    "meaning": "wisdom, jnana (higher knowledge)"
  },
  {
    "question": "辛うじて",
    "answer": "かろうじて",
    "meaning": "barely, narrowly, only just, with difficulty"
  },
  {
    "question": "畜生",
    "answer": "ちくしょう,ちきしょう",
    "meaning": "beast (i.e. any animal other than man), person reborn into the animal realm, brute (i.e. a contempti"
  },
  {
    "question": "入室",
    "answer": "にゅうしつ,にっしつ",
    "meaning": "entering a room, studying under a Buddhist teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "前置き",
    "answer": "まえおき",
    "meaning": "preface, introduction, preamble"
  },
  {
    "question": "活気",
    "answer": "かっき",
    "meaning": "energy, liveliness"
  },
  {
    "question": "髪飾り",
    "answer": "かみかざり",
    "meaning": "hair ornaments"
  },
  {
    "question": "砲撃",
    "answer": "ほうげき",
    "meaning": "bombarding, shelling, bombardment"
  },
  {
    "question": "公平",
    "answer": "きんぴら,こうへい",
    "meaning": "chopped burdock root (and sometimes carrot) cooked in sugar and soy sauce, fairness, impartiality, j"
  },
  {
    "question": "三百",
    "answer": "さんびゃく",
    "meaning": "300, three hundred, 300 mon, trifling amount, two-bit item, shyster"
  },
  {
    "question": "糧",
    "answer": "かて,りょう,かりて",
    "meaning": "food, provisions, nourishment (mental, spiritual, etc.), sustenance (e.g. of one's life), source of"
  },
  {
    "question": "間際",
    "answer": "まぎわ",
    "meaning": "the point just before, the point of doing, the verge of happening"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔑む",
    "answer": "さげすむ",
    "meaning": "to scorn, to despise, to hold in contempt, to look down on, to disdain"
  },
  {
    "question": "首元",
    "answer": "くびもと",
    "meaning": "base of the throat, bottom of the neck"
  },
  {
    "question": "小指",
    "answer": "こゆび",
    "meaning": "little finger, pinky, little toe"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄える",
    "answer": "たくわえる",
    "meaning": "to store, to save up, to stock up on, to lay in stock, to set aside, to accumulate (e.g. knowledge),"
  },
  {
    "question": "一月",
    "answer": "いちがつ,ひとつき,いちげつ",
    "meaning": "January, first month of the lunar calendar, one month"
  },
  {
    "question": "温か",
    "answer": "あたたか,あったか",
    "meaning": "warm, mild, genial"
  },
  {
    "question": "変貌",
    "answer": "へんぼう",
    "meaning": "transfiguration, transformation, change of appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "予告",
    "answer": "よこく",
    "meaning": "advance notice, previous note, preliminary announcement, trailer (film, TV), preview"
  },
  {
    "question": "踊り",
    "answer": "おどり",
    "meaning": "dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "沸騰",
    "answer": "ふっとう",
    "meaning": "boiling, seething, becoming heated (e.g. debate), excitement, agitation, fermentation, soaring (pric"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕縛",
    "answer": "ほばく",
    "meaning": "arrest, apprehension, capture"
  },
  {
    "question": "過激",
    "answer": "かげき",
    "meaning": "extreme, radical"
  },
  {
    "question": "妥協",
    "answer": "だきょう",
    "meaning": "compromise, giving in"
  },
  {
    "question": "口出し",
    "answer": "くちだし",
    "meaning": "interference, meddling, butting in"
  },
  {
    "question": "分類",
    "answer": "ぶんるい",
    "meaning": "classification, categorization, sorting"
  },
  {
    "question": "坊や",
    "answer": "ぼうや",
    "meaning": "boy, son, child, mere boy, stripling, greenhorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "物語る",
    "answer": "ものがたる",
    "meaning": "to tell, to indicate"
  },
  {
    "question": "忍者",
    "answer": "にんじゃ",
    "meaning": "ninja, person trained in ninjutsu and employed for covert purposes in feudal Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "死後",
    "answer": "しご",
    "meaning": "after death"
  },
  {
    "question": "か弱い",
    "answer": "かよわい",
    "meaning": "weak, feeble, delicate, frail, helpless"
  },
  {
    "question": "業",
    "answer": "ごう,わざ,ぎょう",
    "meaning": "karma, result of one's karma, fate, destiny, uncontrollable temper, deed, act, work, performance, bu"
  },
  {
    "question": "計",
    "answer": "けい,はか",
    "meaning": "plan, meter, measuring device, (in) total, total (of), progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "疎い",
    "answer": "うとい",
    "meaning": "distant, estranged, disinterested, poorly informed, unfamiliar, ignorant"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏ん張る",
    "answer": "ふんばる",
    "meaning": "to brace one's legs, to straddle, to stand firm, to plant oneself (somewhere), to hold out, to persi"
  },
  {
    "question": "主催",
    "answer": "しゅさい",
    "meaning": "sponsorship (i.e. conducting under one's auspices), promotion, organizing, organising, hosting, stag"
  },
  {
    "question": "臨時",
    "answer": "りんじ",
    "meaning": "temporary, provisional, interim, special, extraordinary, extra"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉鎖",
    "answer": "へいさ",
    "meaning": "closing, closure, shutdown, lockout"
  },
  {
    "question": "自重",
    "answer": "じちょう,じじゅう",
    "meaning": "self-respect, prudence, not acting rashly, restraining oneself, taking care of oneself, being carefu"
  },
  {
    "question": "真逆",
    "answer": "まさか,まぎゃく",
    "meaning": "by no means, never!, well, I never!, you don't say!, certainly (not), something unexpected, emergenc"
  },
  {
    "question": "紛れ込む",
    "answer": "まぎれこむ",
    "meaning": "to disappear into, to slip into, to be lost in, to be mixed up with"
  },
  {
    "question": "量産",
    "answer": "りょうさん",
    "meaning": "mass production"
  },
  {
    "question": "青色",
    "answer": "あおいろ,せいしょく",
    "meaning": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "笛",
    "answer": "ふえ,ちゃく",
    "meaning": "flute, fife, pipe, recorder, flageolet, shakuhachi, clarinet, whistle"
  },
  {
    "question": "自負",
    "answer": "じふ",
    "meaning": "pride, self-confidence, thinking highly of oneself, being proud of one's abilities or achievements"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪我人",
    "answer": "けがにん",
    "meaning": "wounded person, injured person"
  },
  {
    "question": "闘う",
    "answer": "たたかう",
    "meaning": "to make war (on), to wage war (against), to go to war (with), to fight (with), to do battle (against"
  },
  {
    "question": "重傷",
    "answer": "じゅうしょう,おもで",
    "meaning": "serious wound, serious injury"
  },
  {
    "question": "着信",
    "answer": "ちゃくしん",
    "meaning": "arrival (of post, news, correspondence, etc.), receiving (a phone call, email, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "老",
    "answer": "ろう",
    "meaning": "old age, age, old people, the old, the aged, senior, elder, I, me, my humble self"
  },
  {
    "question": "人体",
    "answer": "じんたい,じんてい,にんてい",
    "meaning": "human body, personal appearance, looks"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩",
    "answer": "うた,し",
    "meaning": "modern poetry, poem, verse of poetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "日課",
    "answer": "にっか",
    "meaning": "daily lesson, daily work, daily routine"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦車",
    "answer": "せんしゃ",
    "meaning": "tank (military vehicle), chariot"
  },
  {
    "question": "和らぐ",
    "answer": "やわらぐ",
    "meaning": "to soften, to calm down, to be eased, to be mitigated, to subside, to abate"
  },
  {
    "question": "垣間見る",
    "answer": "かいまみる",
    "meaning": "to take a peep at, to catch a glimpse of"
  },
  {
    "question": "特技",
    "answer": "とくぎ",
    "meaning": "special skill"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇遇",
    "answer": "きぐう",
    "meaning": "unexpected meeting, coincidence"
  },
  {
    "question": "商業",
    "answer": "しょうぎょう",
    "meaning": "commerce, trade, business"
  },
  {
    "question": "重苦しい",
    "answer": "おもくるしい",
    "meaning": "heavy, gloomy, awkward, cumbrous, oppressive, leaden"
  },
  {
    "question": "所在",
    "answer": "しょざい",
    "meaning": "whereabouts, place where one is, position, location"
  },
  {
    "question": "桃",
    "answer": "もも",
    "meaning": "peach (Prunus persica)"
  },
  {
    "question": "白状",
    "answer": "はくじょう",
    "meaning": "confession"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘く見る",
    "answer": "あまくみる",
    "meaning": "to not take seriously, to take lightly"
  },
  {
    "question": "断定",
    "answer": "だんてい",
    "meaning": "conclusion, decision, judgement, declaration, affirmative"
  },
  {
    "question": "建前",
    "answer": "たてまえ",
    "meaning": "face, official stance, public position or attitude (as opposed to private thoughts), ceremony for th"
  },
  {
    "question": "質量",
    "answer": "しつりょう",
    "meaning": "mass"
  },
  {
    "question": "舌を出す",
    "answer": "したをだす",
    "meaning": "to put out one's tongue, to stick out one's tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "勃起",
    "answer": "ぼっき",
    "meaning": "erection (usu. penis), standing erect, stiffening"
  },
  {
    "question": "支部",
    "answer": "しぶ",
    "meaning": "branch, subdivision"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い込み",
    "answer": "おもいこみ",
    "meaning": "wrong impression, subjective impression, assumption, prejudice"
  },
  {
    "question": "賑わう",
    "answer": "にぎわう",
    "meaning": "to be crowded with people, to be bustling with, to prosper, to flourish, to do thriving business"
  },
  {
    "question": "念入り",
    "answer": "ねんいり",
    "meaning": "careful, scrupulous, thorough, conscientious, elaborate, deliberate, attentive"
  },
  {
    "question": "開け放つ",
    "answer": "あけはなつ",
    "meaning": "to throw open, to leave open"
  },
  {
    "question": "改良",
    "answer": "かいりょう",
    "meaning": "improvement, reform"
  },
  {
    "question": "葉っぱ",
    "answer": "はっぱ",
    "meaning": "leaf, blade (of grass), (pine) needle, marijuana, cannabis"
  },
  {
    "question": "団体",
    "answer": "だんたい",
    "meaning": "organization, organisation, association"
  },
  {
    "question": "滅茶苦茶",
    "answer": "めちゃくちゃ",
    "meaning": "absurd, unreasonable, nonsensical, preposterous, incoherent, extreme, senseless, reckless, wanton, d"
  },
  {
    "question": "城内",
    "answer": "じょうない",
    "meaning": "inside of a castle, area surrounded by castle walls"
  },
  {
    "question": "釘を刺す",
    "answer": "くぎをさす",
    "meaning": "to give a warning, to remind (a person) of"
  },
  {
    "question": "心外",
    "answer": "しんがい",
    "meaning": "regrettable, vexing, upsetting, unthinkable, wholly unexpected"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び名",
    "answer": "よびな",
    "meaning": "popular name, common name, given name"
  },
  {
    "question": "手帳",
    "answer": "てちょう",
    "meaning": "notebook, memo pad, (pocket) diary, certificate, identification card"
  },
  {
    "question": "に取って",
    "answer": "にとって",
    "meaning": "to, for, from the standpoint of, as far as ... is concerned"
  },
  {
    "question": "初め",
    "answer": "はじめ,ぞめ",
    "meaning": "beginning, start, outset, opening, first (in line, etc.), origin, such as ..., not to mention ..., f"
  },
  {
    "question": "疲弊",
    "answer": "ひへい",
    "meaning": "exhaustion, fatigue, impoverishment, (financial) exhaustion, ruin"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬鹿げる",
    "answer": "ばかげる",
    "meaning": "to look foolish"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮定",
    "answer": "かてい",
    "meaning": "assumption, supposition, hypothesis"
  },
  {
    "question": "製造",
    "answer": "せいぞう",
    "meaning": "manufacture, production"
  },
  {
    "question": "安らか",
    "answer": "やすらか",
    "meaning": "peaceful, tranquil, calm, restful"
  },
  {
    "question": "地帯",
    "answer": "ちたい",
    "meaning": "area, zone, belt (of land)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗っかる",
    "answer": "のっかる",
    "meaning": "to get on, to climb on"
  },
  {
    "question": "世紀",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "century, era, of the century (e.g. fight of the century)"
  },
  {
    "question": "驚くべき",
    "answer": "おどろくべき",
    "meaning": "astonishing, amazing, surprising, wonderful"
  },
  {
    "question": "危惧",
    "answer": "きぐ",
    "meaning": "apprehensions, misgivings, uneasiness, anxiety, fear"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い出し",
    "answer": "かいだし",
    "meaning": "going out to shop, going shopping, buying in quantity, buying wholesale, bulk purchasing"
  },
  {
    "question": "長居",
    "answer": "ながい",
    "meaning": "long visit, overstaying"
  },
  {
    "question": "真に",
    "answer": "まことに,しんに",
    "meaning": "indeed, really, absolutely, truly, actually, very, quite"
  },
  {
    "question": "用心",
    "answer": "ようじん",
    "meaning": "care, precaution, guarding, caution"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂浜",
    "answer": "すなはま",
    "meaning": "sandy beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝坊",
    "answer": "ねぼう",
    "meaning": "sleeping in late, oversleeping, late riser, sleepyhead"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯船",
    "answer": "ゆぶね",
    "meaning": "bathtub, boat with a bathtub rented to customers (Edo period)"
  },
  {
    "question": "進学",
    "answer": "しんがく",
    "meaning": "entering a higher-level school, esp. going on to university"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦況",
    "answer": "せんきょう",
    "meaning": "war situation, progress of a battle"
  },
  {
    "question": "技能",
    "answer": "ぎのう",
    "meaning": "technical skill, ability, capacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "大国",
    "answer": "たいこく",
    "meaning": "large country, major nation, great power, province of the highest rank (ritsuryo system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "染み",
    "answer": "しみ",
    "meaning": "stain, spot, smudge, blot, smear, blotch, spot (on one's skin, e.g. chloasma, liver spot), blemish,"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下",
    "answer": "てんか,てんが,てんげ",
    "meaning": "the whole world, the whole country, society, the public, supremacy over a nation, government of a co"
  },
  {
    "question": "賢明",
    "answer": "けんめい",
    "meaning": "wise, sensible, well-advised, intelligent, sagacious, prudent"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏口",
    "answer": "うらぐち",
    "meaning": "backdoor, rear entrance, unauthorized, illicit, illegal"
  },
  {
    "question": "独り占め",
    "answer": "ひとりじめ",
    "meaning": "monopolising, monopolizing, hogging, having all to oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "賞",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "prize, award"
  },
  {
    "question": "項目",
    "answer": "こうもく",
    "meaning": "item, heading, category, clause, headword (in a dictionary, encyclopedia, etc.), entry"
  },
  {
    "question": "武術",
    "answer": "ぶじゅつ",
    "meaning": "martial arts, military arts, wushu, modern sport derived from traditional Chinese martial arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰謀",
    "answer": "いんぼう",
    "meaning": "plot, intrigue, scheme, conspiracy, agreement between two or more people to commit an unlawful act"
  },
  {
    "question": "育ち",
    "answer": "そだち",
    "meaning": "growth, breeding, growing up (in, as), upbringing"
  },
  {
    "question": "迷路",
    "answer": "めいろ",
    "meaning": "maze, labyrinth, inner ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "高み",
    "answer": "たかみ",
    "meaning": "height, elevated place"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉱石",
    "answer": "こうせき",
    "meaning": "ore, mineral, crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "窮地",
    "answer": "きゅうち",
    "meaning": "dilemma, predicament"
  },
  {
    "question": "牢",
    "answer": "ろう",
    "meaning": "prison, jail, gaol, firm, solid, strong"
  },
  {
    "question": "五つ",
    "answer": "いつつ",
    "meaning": "five, five years of age, eight o'clock (old time system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "入力",
    "answer": "にゅうりょく",
    "meaning": "input, (data) entry"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮こまる",
    "answer": "ちぢこまる",
    "meaning": "to curl oneself up, to squeeze oneself in, to be huddled"
  },
  {
    "question": "常人",
    "answer": "じょうじん",
    "meaning": "ordinary person, run-of-the-mill people, John Doe, Jane Doe"
  },
  {
    "question": "運用",
    "answer": "うんよう",
    "meaning": "making use of, application, practical use, effective management (e.g. of funds), operation, handling"
  },
  {
    "question": "増加",
    "answer": "ぞうか",
    "meaning": "increase, rise, growth, addition, increment"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱み",
    "answer": "よわみ",
    "meaning": "(a) weakness, shortcoming, failing, sore point"
  },
  {
    "question": "賞賛",
    "answer": "しょうさん",
    "meaning": "praise, admiration, commendation, approbation"
  },
  {
    "question": "後々",
    "answer": "あとあと,のちのち",
    "meaning": "future, distant future"
  },
  {
    "question": "養う",
    "answer": "やしなう",
    "meaning": "to support, to maintain, to provide for, to bring up, to raise, to rear, to feed, to adopt (a child)"
  },
  {
    "question": "馴染み",
    "answer": "なじみ",
    "meaning": "intimacy, friendship, familiarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "半身",
    "answer": "はんしん,はんみ",
    "meaning": "half the body, half length, stance with legs in an L-shape, with one leg bent in front and other ext"
  },
  {
    "question": "連合",
    "answer": "れんごう",
    "meaning": "union, alliance, combination, RENGO (Japanese Trade Union Confederation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "依存",
    "answer": "いぞん,いそん",
    "meaning": "dependence, reliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "選挙",
    "answer": "せんきょ",
    "meaning": "election"
  },
  {
    "question": "好意的",
    "answer": "こういてき",
    "meaning": "favorable, favourable"
  },
  {
    "question": "語り合う",
    "answer": "かたりあう",
    "meaning": "to talk together"
  },
  {
    "question": "侵す",
    "answer": "おかす",
    "meaning": "to invade, to raid, to violate (airspace, etc.), to intrude, to trespass, to infringe, to encroach,"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏まえる",
    "answer": "ふまえる",
    "meaning": "to be based on, to take into account, to build upon, to have origin in, to have one's feet firmly pl"
  },
  {
    "question": "託す",
    "answer": "たくす",
    "meaning": "to entrust (someone) with, to leave (a matter) with someone, to place under someone's care, to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "延長",
    "answer": "えんちょう",
    "meaning": "extension, elongation, prolongation, lengthening, Enchō era (923.4.11-931.4.26)"
  },
  {
    "question": "階級",
    "answer": "かいきゅう",
    "meaning": "(social) class, rank, grade"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び出る",
    "answer": "とびでる",
    "meaning": "to project, to protrude, to pop out (e.g. eyes), to jump out, to rush out"
  },
  {
    "question": "昼飯",
    "answer": "ひるめし,ちゅうはん,ひるはん",
    "meaning": "lunch, midday meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "歪",
    "answer": "いびつ",
    "meaning": "distorted, crooked, irregular, warped, oval, elliptical shape, round, wooden container for cooked ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "続行",
    "answer": "ぞっこう",
    "meaning": "continuation, continuance, going on, resuming"
  },
  {
    "question": "発覚",
    "answer": "はっかく",
    "meaning": "detection (of a plot, fraud, etc.), discovery, coming to light, being uncovered"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕焼け",
    "answer": "ゆうやけ",
    "meaning": "evening glow, red sunset, afterglow (of sunset)"
  },
  {
    "question": "両目",
    "answer": "りょうめ",
    "meaning": "both eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "真下",
    "answer": "ました",
    "meaning": "right under, directly below"
  },
  {
    "question": "真横",
    "answer": "まよこ",
    "meaning": "directly horizontal, right beside"
  },
  {
    "question": "汲む",
    "answer": "くむ",
    "meaning": "to draw (water), to ladle, to dip up, to scoop up, to pump, to pour (into a cup), to drink (together"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝床",
    "answer": "ねどこ",
    "meaning": "bed, berth, crib, cot, kip, bedroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "井",
    "answer": "い,せい",
    "meaning": "well, well curb, Chinese 'Well' constellation (one of the 28 mansions)"
  },
  {
    "question": "彼等",
    "answer": "かれら,あれら",
    "meaning": "they, them, those (indicating something distant from both speaker and listener, or something underst"
  },
  {
    "question": "駐車場",
    "answer": "ちゅうしゃじょう",
    "meaning": "parking lot, car park, carpark, parking garage"
  },
  {
    "question": "輸送",
    "answer": "ゆそう",
    "meaning": "transport, transportation"
  },
  {
    "question": "技量",
    "answer": "ぎりょう",
    "meaning": "ability, competency, talent, skill, capacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "強要",
    "answer": "きょうよう",
    "meaning": "coercion, extortion, compulsion, force"
  },
  {
    "question": "据える",
    "answer": "すえる",
    "meaning": "to place (in position), to fix, to set (e.g. table), to lay (foundation), to install, to seat (someo"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し返す",
    "answer": "おしかえす",
    "meaning": "to force back, to jostle"
  },
  {
    "question": "褒美",
    "answer": "ほうび",
    "meaning": "reward, prize"
  },
  {
    "question": "役職",
    "answer": "やくしょく",
    "meaning": "post, official position, managerial position, executive position"
  },
  {
    "question": "操縦",
    "answer": "そうじゅう",
    "meaning": "steering, piloting, flying, control, operation, handling, management, manipulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "面する",
    "answer": "めんする",
    "meaning": "to face on, to look out on to"
  },
  {
    "question": "法則",
    "answer": "ほうそく",
    "meaning": "law, rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "模する",
    "answer": "もする",
    "meaning": "to imitate, to copy, to mock, to replace, to model after, to trace, to forge"
  },
  {
    "question": "粘膜",
    "answer": "ねんまく",
    "meaning": "mucous membrane"
  },
  {
    "question": "店舗",
    "answer": "てんぽ",
    "meaning": "shop, store"
  },
  {
    "question": "家系",
    "answer": "かけい",
    "meaning": "family lineage"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮まる",
    "answer": "ちぢまる",
    "meaning": "to shorten, to narrow, to close, to shrink"
  },
  {
    "question": "侵略",
    "answer": "しんりゃく",
    "meaning": "aggression, invasion, raid"
  },
  {
    "question": "義父",
    "answer": "ぎふ",
    "meaning": "father-in-law, foster father, stepfather"
  },
  {
    "question": "報復",
    "answer": "ほうふく",
    "meaning": "retaliation, revenge, reprisal, retribution, retorsion, retortion"
  },
  {
    "question": "助け出す",
    "answer": "たすけだす",
    "meaning": "to help out of (trouble), to extricate"
  },
  {
    "question": "害する",
    "answer": "がいする",
    "meaning": "to injure, to damage, to harm, to hurt, to kill, to hinder, to obstruct"
  },
  {
    "question": "狙撃",
    "answer": "そげき",
    "meaning": "shooting, sniping"
  },
  {
    "question": "甲斐",
    "answer": "かい,がい",
    "meaning": "effect, result, worth, use, avail, Kai (former province located in present-day Yamanashi Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一団",
    "answer": "いちだん",
    "meaning": "body, group, party, gang, troupe, troop"
  },
  {
    "question": "孤児",
    "answer": "こじ,みなしご",
    "meaning": "orphan, person without friends"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤黒い",
    "answer": "あかぐろい",
    "meaning": "dark red, dark brown, reddish brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "損なう",
    "answer": "そこなう",
    "meaning": "to harm, to hurt, to injure, to damage, to spoil, to mar, to fail to ..., to miss one's opportunity"
  },
  {
    "question": "一理",
    "answer": "いちり",
    "meaning": "(a) principle, (a) reason, (a) point, some truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "路地裏",
    "answer": "ろじうら",
    "meaning": "back street, back alley, off-street"
  },
  {
    "question": "燃料",
    "answer": "ねんりょう",
    "meaning": "fuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣取る",
    "answer": "じんどる",
    "meaning": "to encamp, to take up positions"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち会う",
    "answer": "たちあう",
    "meaning": "to be present (esp. during a birth), to be witness to"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済",
    "answer": "けいざい",
    "meaning": "economy, economics, finance, (one's) finances, financial circumstances, being economical, thrift"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち上る",
    "answer": "たちのぼる",
    "meaning": "to rise up (e.g. pillar of smoke), to go up"
  },
  {
    "question": "務まる",
    "answer": "つとまる",
    "meaning": "to be fit for, to be equal to, to function properly"
  },
  {
    "question": "保険",
    "answer": "ほけん",
    "meaning": "insurance, guarantee"
  },
  {
    "question": "今宵",
    "answer": "こよい",
    "meaning": "this evening, tonight"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺らめく",
    "answer": "ゆらめく",
    "meaning": "to flicker, to quiver, to waver, to sway"
  },
  {
    "question": "非常識",
    "answer": "ひじょうしき",
    "meaning": "lack of common sense, thoughtlessness, senselessness, irrationality, absurdity"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦点",
    "answer": "しょうてん",
    "meaning": "focus (e.g. photographic), focal point"
  },
  {
    "question": "満つ",
    "answer": "みつ",
    "meaning": "to be full, to wax (e.g. moon), to rise (e.g. tide), to mature, to expire"
  },
  {
    "question": "飴",
    "answer": "あめ,たがね",
    "meaning": "(hard) candy, toffee, rice-sugar, sugar made from the starch of rice, potatoes, etc., amber, yellowi"
  },
  {
    "question": "病人",
    "answer": "びょうにん",
    "meaning": "sick person, patient, invalid"
  },
  {
    "question": "見舞い",
    "answer": "みまい",
    "meaning": "visiting ill or distressed people, writing get-well letters, get-well gifts, get-well letters, expre"
  },
  {
    "question": "源",
    "answer": "みなもと,げん",
    "meaning": "source (of a river), fountainhead, source, origin, root"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕込み",
    "answer": "しこみ,じこみ",
    "meaning": "training, education, upbringing, stocking up, laying in, preparation (e.g. ingredients), girl studyi"
  },
  {
    "question": "朗らか",
    "answer": "ほがらか",
    "meaning": "cheerful, merry, sunny, melodious, bright (sky, day, etc.), fine, clear"
  },
  {
    "question": "各種",
    "answer": "かくしゅ",
    "meaning": "every kind, all sorts"
  },
  {
    "question": "胡散臭い",
    "answer": "うさんくさい",
    "meaning": "suspicious-looking, shady, questionable, dubious, fishy"
  },
  {
    "question": "辞退",
    "answer": "じたい",
    "meaning": "declining, refusal, nonacceptance, turning down, withdrawal (e.g. of candidacy), pulling out (e.g. o"
  },
  {
    "question": "纏める",
    "answer": "まとめる",
    "meaning": "to collect, to put (it all) together, to integrate, to consolidate, to unify, to summarize, to aggre"
  },
  {
    "question": "潔い",
    "answer": "いさぎよい",
    "meaning": "manly, sportsmanlike, gracious, gallant, resolute, brave, pure (heart, actions, etc.), upright, blam"
  },
  {
    "question": "自爆",
    "answer": "じばく",
    "meaning": "suicide bombing (e.g. crashing one's plane into a target), self-destruction, blowing oneself up"
  },
  {
    "question": "大概",
    "answer": "たいがい",
    "meaning": "generally, mainly, usually, normally, mostly, for the most part, nearly all, almost all, most, gist,"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪魔者",
    "answer": "じゃまもの",
    "meaning": "obstacle, hindrance, impediment, obstruction, nuisance, bore, burden"
  },
  {
    "question": "善意",
    "answer": "ぜんい",
    "meaning": "virtuous mind, good intentions, good will, positive mindset, bona fides, good faith"
  },
  {
    "question": "美形",
    "answer": "びけい,びぎょう",
    "meaning": "beautiful face, beautiful looks, beauty, belle, handsome man"
  },
  {
    "question": "短期間",
    "answer": "たんきかん",
    "meaning": "short term, short time"
  },
  {
    "question": "充満",
    "answer": "じゅうまん",
    "meaning": "being filled with, being full of, permeation"
  },
  {
    "question": "懸ける",
    "answer": "かける",
    "meaning": "to hang up (e.g. a coat, a picture on the wall), to let hang, to suspend (from), to hoist (e.g. sail"
  },
  {
    "question": "知人",
    "answer": "ちじん",
    "meaning": "friend, acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "牢獄",
    "answer": "ろうごく",
    "meaning": "prison, jail, gaol"
  },
  {
    "question": "簡易",
    "answer": "かんい",
    "meaning": "simplicity, convenience, easiness, quasi-"
  },
  {
    "question": "定か",
    "answer": "さだか",
    "meaning": "definite, sure"
  },
  {
    "question": "衰える",
    "answer": "おとろえる",
    "meaning": "to become weak, to decline, to wear, to abate, to decay, to wither, to waste away"
  },
  {
    "question": "出産",
    "answer": "しゅっさん",
    "meaning": "childbirth, (giving) birth, delivery, parturition, confinement, production (of goods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "増幅",
    "answer": "ぞうふく",
    "meaning": "amplification (elec.), magnification, amplification, making larger"
  },
  {
    "question": "見返り",
    "answer": "みかえり",
    "meaning": "reward, compensation, repayment, something done or given in return, collateral, security, turning to"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮上",
    "answer": "ふじょう",
    "meaning": "surfacing, rising to the surface, emerging, leaping into prominence, rising (of rank)"
  },
  {
    "question": "見当",
    "answer": "けんとう",
    "meaning": "estimate, guess, conjecture, aim, direction, bearings, registration mark (printing), approximately,"
  },
  {
    "question": "冴える",
    "answer": "さえる",
    "meaning": "to be clear (of a sight, sound, colour, etc.), to be bright, to be vivid, to be crisp, to be clear-h"
  },
  {
    "question": "要領",
    "answer": "ようりょう",
    "meaning": "point, gist, essentials, tenets, outline, knack, trick, the ropes"
  },
  {
    "question": "子孫",
    "answer": "しそん",
    "meaning": "descendant, posterity, offspring"
  },
  {
    "question": "行列",
    "answer": "ぎょうれつ",
    "meaning": "line, queue, procession, parade, matrix"
  },
  {
    "question": "形跡",
    "answer": "けいせき",
    "meaning": "traces, evidence"
  },
  {
    "question": "木箱",
    "answer": "きばこ",
    "meaning": "wooden box, wooden crate"
  },
  {
    "question": "郎",
    "answer": "ろう",
    "meaning": "nth son, lang, official title in ancient China, man, young man, my husband, my lover, nth child (mal"
  },
  {
    "question": "散策",
    "answer": "さんさく",
    "meaning": "walking, strolling, roaming, wandering, exploring"
  },
  {
    "question": "中枢",
    "answer": "ちゅうすう",
    "meaning": "centre, center, pivot, mainstay, nucleus, backbone, central figure, pillar, key man"
  },
  {
    "question": "批判",
    "answer": "ひはん",
    "meaning": "criticism, judgement, judgment, comment"
  },
  {
    "question": "治まる",
    "answer": "おさまる",
    "meaning": "to die down (storm, anger, conflict, etc.), to calm down, to cool off, to abate, to be settled, to b"
  },
  {
    "question": "速攻",
    "answer": "そっこう",
    "meaning": "swift attack, quick attack, fast break, right away, without delay, immediately"
  },
  {
    "question": "従順",
    "answer": "じゅうじゅん",
    "meaning": "obedient, gentle, meek, submissive, docile"
  },
  {
    "question": "手先",
    "answer": "てさき",
    "meaning": "fingers, fingertips, underling, stooge, tool, pawn, minion"
  },
  {
    "question": "野望",
    "answer": "やぼう",
    "meaning": "ambition, aspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "恋しい",
    "answer": "こいしい",
    "meaning": "yearned for, longed for, missed"
  },
  {
    "question": "必ずしも",
    "answer": "かならずしも",
    "meaning": "(not) always, (not) necessarily, (not) entirely, (not) all"
  },
  {
    "question": "海岸",
    "answer": "かいがん",
    "meaning": "coast, beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "霧散",
    "answer": "むさん",
    "meaning": "dispersing, vanishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "桃色",
    "answer": "ももいろ",
    "meaning": "pink (colour, color), colour of peach (flowers)"
  },
  {
    "question": "体液",
    "answer": "たいえき",
    "meaning": "body fluids"
  },
  {
    "question": "細か",
    "answer": "こまか",
    "meaning": "small, fine, detailed, stingy"
  },
  {
    "question": "心苦しい",
    "answer": "こころぐるしい",
    "meaning": "painful, being sorry, feeling sorry"
  },
  {
    "question": "地下室",
    "answer": "ちかしつ",
    "meaning": "cellar, basement"
  },
  {
    "question": "畳",
    "answer": "じょう,たたみ,たとう",
    "meaning": "tatami mat (esp. as a measure of room size, either 1.82 sqm or 1.54 sqm), tatami mat, Japanese straw"
  },
  {
    "question": "凌ぐ",
    "answer": "しのぐ",
    "meaning": "to endure, to keep out (e.g. rain), to stave off (e.g. starvation), to pull through, to get over, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "携える",
    "answer": "たずさえる",
    "meaning": "to carry in one's hand, to carry with one, to have on one's person, to bear, to take along (someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "清々しい",
    "answer": "すがすがしい",
    "meaning": "refreshing (e.g. feeling, scene, wind, morning air), brisk, bracing, fresh, refreshed"
  },
  {
    "question": "待ち伏せ",
    "answer": "まちぶせ",
    "meaning": "ambush, lying in wait for an ambush"
  },
  {
    "question": "不用意",
    "answer": "ふようい",
    "meaning": "unprepared, careless, imprudent, indiscreet, inadvertent"
  },
  {
    "question": "消化",
    "answer": "しょうか",
    "meaning": "digestion (of food), digestion (of information), assimilation, thorough understanding, consumption,"
  },
  {
    "question": "悠長",
    "answer": "ゆうちょう",
    "meaning": "leisurely, slow, deliberate, easygoing"
  },
  {
    "question": "人気者",
    "answer": "にんきもの",
    "meaning": "popular person, favorite, favourite"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒野",
    "answer": "こうや,あれの,あらの",
    "meaning": "wasteland, wilderness, deserted land, prairie, vast plain, wilds, desert, wild land"
  },
  {
    "question": "早",
    "answer": "はや,はよ",
    "meaning": "already, now, by this time, quick, early, fast, rapid, quickly, soon, early morning, early hour, ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "当",
    "answer": "とう,はた",
    "meaning": "this, our, the ... in question, the said ..., right, justice, fairness, or, otherwise, furthermore,"
  },
  {
    "question": "片足",
    "answer": "かたあし",
    "meaning": "one leg, one-legged"
  },
  {
    "question": "事象",
    "answer": "じしょう",
    "meaning": "event, phenomenon, matter"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷酷",
    "answer": "れいこく",
    "meaning": "cruelty, coldheartedness, relentless, ruthless"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄々",
    "answer": "うすうす",
    "meaning": "thinly, slightly, vaguely, a little"
  },
  {
    "question": "稼ぎ",
    "answer": "かせぎ",
    "meaning": "earnings"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き破る",
    "answer": "つきやぶる",
    "meaning": "to break through, to penetrate, to pierce"
  },
  {
    "question": "眷属",
    "answer": "けんぞく",
    "meaning": "(one's) family, dependents, household, follower, retainer, underling"
  },
  {
    "question": "杭",
    "answer": "くい,くいぜ,くいせ",
    "meaning": "stake, post, pile, picket, stump"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖域",
    "answer": "せいいき",
    "meaning": "sacred precincts, sanctuary, consecrated ground, holy ground, issue that is regarded as being off-li"
  },
  {
    "question": "士気",
    "answer": "しき",
    "meaning": "morale (of troops, team, etc.), esprit de corps"
  },
  {
    "question": "日曜",
    "answer": "にちよう",
    "meaning": "Sunday"
  },
  {
    "question": "片目",
    "answer": "かため,めっかち",
    "meaning": "one eye, one of one's eyes, blindness in one eye, having one eye much bigger than the other, someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "歯車",
    "answer": "はぐるま",
    "meaning": "gear, cogwheel"
  },
  {
    "question": "司祭",
    "answer": "しさい",
    "meaning": "priest, minister, pastor"
  },
  {
    "question": "収束",
    "answer": "しゅうそく",
    "meaning": "conclusion, resolution, firming up (plans, etc.), coming together, returning to normal, gathering an"
  },
  {
    "question": "解明",
    "answer": "かいめい",
    "meaning": "elucidation, explication, explaining, unravelling, clarification, understanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "喪失",
    "answer": "そうしつ",
    "meaning": "loss, forfeit"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕組む",
    "answer": "しくむ",
    "meaning": "to devise, to arrange, to plan, to plot"
  },
  {
    "question": "絡み合う",
    "answer": "からみあう",
    "meaning": "to be(come) intertwined, to be entangled"
  },
  {
    "question": "職務",
    "answer": "しょくむ",
    "meaning": "professional duties"
  },
  {
    "question": "保留",
    "answer": "ほりゅう",
    "meaning": "reservation, putting on hold, deferment"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠く",
    "answer": "かく",
    "meaning": "to chip, to nick, to break, to crack, to lack"
  },
  {
    "question": "早起き",
    "answer": "はやおき",
    "meaning": "early rising"
  },
  {
    "question": "隅々",
    "answer": "すみずみ,くまぐま",
    "meaning": "every corner, every nook and cranny, all the ins and outs"
  },
  {
    "question": "探知",
    "answer": "たんち",
    "meaning": "detection"
  },
  {
    "question": "外壁",
    "answer": "がいへき,そとかべ",
    "meaning": "outer wall"
  },
  {
    "question": "活発",
    "answer": "かっぱつ",
    "meaning": "lively, active, vigorous, animated, brisk"
  },
  {
    "question": "入場",
    "answer": "にゅうじょう",
    "meaning": "entrance, admission, entering"
  },
  {
    "question": "筋力",
    "answer": "きんりょく",
    "meaning": "physical strength, muscle strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "性欲",
    "answer": "せいよく",
    "meaning": "sexual desire"
  },
  {
    "question": "家畜",
    "answer": "かちく",
    "meaning": "domestic animals, livestock, cattle"
  },
  {
    "question": "隔てる",
    "answer": "へだてる",
    "meaning": "to separate (by distance, time, etc.), to isolate, to partition, to divide, to interpose, to have be"
  },
  {
    "question": "宇宙人",
    "answer": "うちゅうじん",
    "meaning": "space alien, alien, extraterrestrial being"
  },
  {
    "question": "外れ",
    "answer": "はずれ",
    "meaning": "end, verge, extremity, tip, outskirts, miss, failure, blank (e.g. lottery ticket)"
  },
  {
    "question": "規則",
    "answer": "きそく",
    "meaning": "rule, regulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "裕福",
    "answer": "ゆうふく",
    "meaning": "wealthy, rich, affluent, well-off"
  },
  {
    "question": "報いる",
    "answer": "むくいる",
    "meaning": "to reward, to recompense, to repay, to retaliate, to get revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び乗る",
    "answer": "とびのる",
    "meaning": "to jump upon (a moving object)"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕打ち",
    "answer": "しうち",
    "meaning": "(poor) treatment, (bad) behavior, behaviour, action, act"
  },
  {
    "question": "定まる",
    "answer": "さだまる",
    "meaning": "to become settled, to be fixed"
  },
  {
    "question": "思う存分",
    "answer": "おもうぞんぶん",
    "meaning": "to one's heart's content, to one's complete satisfaction, as much as one likes, heartily, thoroughly"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝込む",
    "answer": "ねこむ",
    "meaning": "to stay in bed, to sleep, to be laid up for a long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "見通す",
    "answer": "みとおす",
    "meaning": "to see without obstruction, to see through, to forecast, to predict, to anticipate"
  },
  {
    "question": "騎",
    "answer": "き",
    "meaning": "counter for horsemen"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗濯物",
    "answer": "せんたくもの",
    "meaning": "laundry, the washing"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠蔽",
    "answer": "いんぺい",
    "meaning": "concealment, suppression, hiding"
  },
  {
    "question": "一段落",
    "answer": "いちだんらく,ひとだんらく",
    "meaning": "reaching a stopping place, settling down (before the next stage), getting to a point where one can r"
  },
  {
    "question": "修羅場",
    "answer": "しゅらば,しゅらじょう",
    "meaning": "fighting scene, scene of carnage (bloodshed), difficulties (in a love relationship), crunch time (es"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き着く",
    "answer": "ゆきつく,いきつく",
    "meaning": "to arrive at, to end up"
  },
  {
    "question": "必ずや",
    "answer": "かならずや",
    "meaning": "certainly, surely, definitely"
  },
  {
    "question": "居座る",
    "answer": "いすわる",
    "meaning": "to remain, to stay (somewhere)"
  },
  {
    "question": "好物",
    "answer": "こうぶつ",
    "meaning": "favourite dish (favorite), favourite food"
  },
  {
    "question": "地道",
    "answer": "じみち",
    "meaning": "steady, honest, sober, straightforward"
  },
  {
    "question": "面接",
    "answer": "めんせつ",
    "meaning": "interview (e.g. for a job)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮮血",
    "answer": "せんけつ",
    "meaning": "fresh blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "霞む",
    "answer": "かすむ",
    "meaning": "to become misty, to become hazy, to get blurry, to grow dim, to be overshadowed, to be upstaged, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "長生き",
    "answer": "ながいき",
    "meaning": "longevity, long life"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻防",
    "answer": "こうぼう",
    "meaning": "offense and defense, offence and defence"
  },
  {
    "question": "子宮",
    "answer": "しきゅう",
    "meaning": "womb, uterus"
  },
  {
    "question": "切れ",
    "answer": "きれ,ぎれ",
    "meaning": "piece, slice, strip, scrap, cloth, sharpness, agility, counter for scraps, pieces, etc., completely"
  },
  {
    "question": "手が届く",
    "answer": "てがとどく",
    "meaning": "to be able to reach, to be within one's reach, to be able to afford, to have the means to buy, to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "記載",
    "answer": "きさい",
    "meaning": "mention (in a document), record, entry, statement, listing"
  },
  {
    "question": "女優",
    "answer": "じょゆう",
    "meaning": "actress"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀貨",
    "answer": "ぎんか",
    "meaning": "silver coin"
  },
  {
    "question": "初代",
    "answer": "しょだい",
    "meaning": "first generation, founder"
  },
  {
    "question": "別荘",
    "answer": "べっそう",
    "meaning": "holiday house, vacation home, villa, prison, jail"
  },
  {
    "question": "生憎",
    "answer": "あいにく",
    "meaning": "unfortunately, sorry, but ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "腕組み",
    "answer": "うでぐみ",
    "meaning": "folding one's arms"
  },
  {
    "question": "定義",
    "answer": "ていぎ",
    "meaning": "definition"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋼鉄",
    "answer": "こうてつ",
    "meaning": "steel"
  },
  {
    "question": "陥れる",
    "answer": "おとしいれる",
    "meaning": "to trap (into a difficult situation), to put (in a fix), to throw (e.g. into turmoil), to trick (int"
  },
  {
    "question": "灼熱",
    "answer": "しゃくねつ",
    "meaning": "becoming red hot, red heat, scorching heat, incandescence, running high (of emotions), burning (with"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘲笑う",
    "answer": "あざわらう,せせらわらう",
    "meaning": "to laugh at, to ridicule, to mock, to make fun of, to sneer at, to laugh mockingly, to smile with co"
  },
  {
    "question": "恥をかく",
    "answer": "はじをかく",
    "meaning": "to be embarrassed, to lose face"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰国",
    "answer": "きこく",
    "meaning": "return to one's country"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠征",
    "answer": "えんせい",
    "meaning": "expedition, (military) campaign, tour (by a sports team, performer, etc.), visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "婦人",
    "answer": "ふじん",
    "meaning": "woman, lady, adult female"
  },
  {
    "question": "革命",
    "answer": "かくめい",
    "meaning": "revolution, 58th year of the sexagenary cycle (in Onmyōdō)"
  },
  {
    "question": "颯爽",
    "answer": "さっそう",
    "meaning": "gallant, dashing, jaunty"
  },
  {
    "question": "効率的",
    "answer": "こうりつてき",
    "meaning": "efficient"
  },
  {
    "question": "お互い様",
    "answer": "おたがいさま",
    "meaning": "we are of equal status in this regard, we are in the same boat, the same to you, the feeling is mutu"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き交う",
    "answer": "ゆきかう,いきかう",
    "meaning": "to come and go, to go back and forth"
  },
  {
    "question": "見間違う",
    "answer": "みまちがう",
    "meaning": "to misperceive visually, to misread, to mistake for something or somebody else"
  },
  {
    "question": "実体",
    "answer": "じったい,じってい",
    "meaning": "substance, essence, entity, subject, content, reality, true form, honest, trustworthy, upright, sinc"
  },
  {
    "question": "四角い",
    "answer": "しかくい",
    "meaning": "square, rectangular"
  },
  {
    "question": "発進",
    "answer": "はっしん",
    "meaning": "departure, takeoff"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮む",
    "answer": "ちぢむ,ちじむ",
    "meaning": "to shrink, to contract, to diminish (in size)"
  },
  {
    "question": "昼過ぎ",
    "answer": "ひるすぎ",
    "meaning": "just past noon, afternoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶つ",
    "answer": "たつ",
    "meaning": "to sever, to cut off, to suppress, to eradicate, to exterminate, to abstain (from), to give up"
  },
  {
    "question": "浴衣",
    "answer": "ゆかた,よくい",
    "meaning": "yukata (light cotton kimono worn in the summer or used as a bathrobe)"
  },
  {
    "question": "部類",
    "answer": "ぶるい",
    "meaning": "class, heading, group, category"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼応",
    "answer": "こおう",
    "meaning": "hailing each other, acting in concert, responding (to), sympathizing (with), agreement, concord"
  },
  {
    "question": "近頃",
    "answer": "ちかごろ",
    "meaning": "lately, recently, nowadays"
  },
  {
    "question": "領民",
    "answer": "りょうみん",
    "meaning": "population of a fief"
  },
  {
    "question": "待遇",
    "answer": "たいぐう",
    "meaning": "treatment, reception, service, working conditions, salary, pay, remuneration"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦線",
    "answer": "せんせん",
    "meaning": "(war) front"
  },
  {
    "question": "無垢",
    "answer": "むく",
    "meaning": "pure, innocent, spotless, immaculate, unspoiled, unmixed, unadulterated, long kimono made from the s"
  },
  {
    "question": "利",
    "answer": "り",
    "meaning": "advantage, benefit, profit, interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "送信",
    "answer": "そうしん",
    "meaning": "transmission, sending"
  },
  {
    "question": "格段",
    "answer": "かくだん",
    "meaning": "dramatic (improvement), remarkable (difference), marked, noticeable, (far) better, exceptional"
  },
  {
    "question": "日中",
    "answer": "にっちゅう,ひなか",
    "meaning": "daytime, during the day, Japan and China"
  },
  {
    "question": "潮",
    "answer": "しお,うしお",
    "meaning": "tide, current, sea water, opportunity, chance, thin soup of fish or shellfish boiled in seawater"
  },
  {
    "question": "薪",
    "answer": "まき,たきぎ",
    "meaning": "piece(s) of firewood (esp. chopped or split from logs), kindling (twigs, branches, etc.), firewood"
  },
  {
    "question": "前衛",
    "answer": "ぜんえい",
    "meaning": "advance guard, vanguard, avant-garde (e.g. music)"
  },
  {
    "question": "演劇",
    "answer": "えんげき",
    "meaning": "drama, theatre, theater, play"
  },
  {
    "question": "目に映る",
    "answer": "めにうつる",
    "meaning": "to be visible to, to be seen by, to meet one's eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "誰一人",
    "answer": "だれひとり",
    "meaning": "(not) anyone, (not) a single person, no one, nobody"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺産",
    "answer": "いさん",
    "meaning": "inheritance, bequest, legacy, heritage"
  },
  {
    "question": "襟",
    "answer": "えり",
    "meaning": "collar, lapel, neckband, neck, nape of the neck, scruff of the neck"
  },
  {
    "question": "権威",
    "answer": "けんい",
    "meaning": "authority, power, influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "編成",
    "answer": "へんせい",
    "meaning": "composition, formation, organization, organisation, compilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "調味料",
    "answer": "ちょうみりょう",
    "meaning": "seasoning, flavoring, flavouring, condiment"
  },
  {
    "question": "刻印",
    "answer": "こくいん",
    "meaning": "carved seal, engraved stamp, to engrave (a seal), to carve, to make an impression (with a seal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "面子",
    "answer": "めんこ,メンツ",
    "meaning": "menko, children's game in which thick circular or rectangular cards are slapped down on the ground t"
  },
  {
    "question": "無口",
    "answer": "むくち,むこう",
    "meaning": "taciturn, reticent, quiet, silent, untalkative, astomatous"
  },
  {
    "question": "帯",
    "answer": "おび,たらし,たい",
    "meaning": "obi, kimono sash, paper wrapper on books, CDs, etc., band, belt, strip, cingulum, radio or televisio"
  },
  {
    "question": "月光",
    "answer": "げっこう",
    "meaning": "moonlight, moonbeam"
  },
  {
    "question": "手間取る",
    "answer": "てまどる",
    "meaning": "to take more time than expected, to take a long time, to be delayed"
  },
  {
    "question": "着信音",
    "answer": "ちゃくしんおん",
    "meaning": "ringtone"
  },
  {
    "question": "花壇",
    "answer": "かだん",
    "meaning": "flower bed"
  },
  {
    "question": "栄光",
    "answer": "えいこう",
    "meaning": "glory"
  },
  {
    "question": "大柄",
    "answer": "おおがら,おおへい",
    "meaning": "large build, large pattern, arrogance, haughtiness, insolence"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥底",
    "answer": "おくそこ,おうてい",
    "meaning": "depths, deep place, bottom (of one's heart)"
  },
  {
    "question": "無線",
    "answer": "むせん",
    "meaning": "radio (communication), wireless, not using wires"
  },
  {
    "question": "補足",
    "answer": "ほそく",
    "meaning": "supplement, complement"
  },
  {
    "question": "矢先",
    "answer": "やさき",
    "meaning": "arrowhead, target of a flying arrow, brunt (of an attack), the very moment (when), the point (of doi"
  },
  {
    "question": "朦朧",
    "answer": "もうろう",
    "meaning": "dim, hazy, vague, indistinct, faint, fuzzy, cloudy, obscure"
  },
  {
    "question": "童貞",
    "answer": "どうてい",
    "meaning": "virginity (of a male), virgin, (Catholic) nun, sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "穏便",
    "answer": "おんびん",
    "meaning": "gentle, peaceable, amicable, quiet, without fuss, simply"
  },
  {
    "question": "塞がる",
    "answer": "ふさがる,ふたがる",
    "meaning": "to be closed, to be blocked, to be healed (e.g. wound), to be shut up, to be clogged, to be plugged"
  },
  {
    "question": "細胞",
    "answer": "さいぼう,さいほう",
    "meaning": "cell, cell (in an organization, esp. a communist party)"
  },
  {
    "question": "合",
    "answer": "あい,ごう",
    "meaning": "between-season wear, spring and autumn clothing, spring and fall clothing, together, condition, situ"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠回り",
    "answer": "とおまわり",
    "meaning": "detour, roundabout way"
  },
  {
    "question": "感慨",
    "answer": "かんがい",
    "meaning": "deep emotion, strong feelings"
  },
  {
    "question": "恋心",
    "answer": "こいごころ",
    "meaning": "(feelings of) love"
  },
  {
    "question": "慈愛",
    "answer": "じあい",
    "meaning": "affection (esp. parental), love, fondness"
  },
  {
    "question": "背丈",
    "answer": "せたけ,せいたけ",
    "meaning": "stature, height"
  },
  {
    "question": "張本人",
    "answer": "ちょうほんにん",
    "meaning": "originator, ringleader, perpetrator, main culprit, person responsible"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び捨て",
    "answer": "よびすて",
    "meaning": "addressing (someone) without using a suffix such as '-san' or '-chan' (considered impolite)"
  },
  {
    "question": "連日",
    "answer": "れんじつ",
    "meaning": "day after day, every day"
  },
  {
    "question": "眩い",
    "answer": "まぶい,まばゆい",
    "meaning": "cute, pretty, dazzling, glaring, dazzlingly beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺伝子",
    "answer": "いでんし",
    "meaning": "gene, genetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "学者",
    "answer": "がくしゃ",
    "meaning": "scholar"
  },
  {
    "question": "簡素",
    "answer": "かんそ",
    "meaning": "simple, plain, modest"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗練",
    "answer": "せんれん",
    "meaning": "polish, refinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "大いなる",
    "answer": "おおいなる",
    "meaning": "big, large, great"
  },
  {
    "question": "大粒",
    "answer": "おおつぶ",
    "meaning": "large drop (rain, sweat, tears, etc.), large grain-like object (grape, cherry, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "単刀直入",
    "answer": "たんとうちょくにゅう",
    "meaning": "straight to the point, point-blank, frank, direct"
  },
  {
    "question": "着飾る",
    "answer": "きかざる",
    "meaning": "to dress up"
  },
  {
    "question": "反",
    "answer": "たん,はん",
    "meaning": "variable measure of fabric (28.8 cm in width), for kimonos: at least 10 m in length, for haori: at l"
  },
  {
    "question": "照れ隠し",
    "answer": "てれかくし",
    "meaning": "hiding one's embarrassment"
  },
  {
    "question": "司る",
    "answer": "つかさどる",
    "meaning": "to rule, to govern, to administer"
  },
  {
    "question": "大差",
    "answer": "たいさ",
    "meaning": "great difference, big difference, wide margin"
  },
  {
    "question": "独り",
    "answer": "ひとり",
    "meaning": "one person, being alone, being by oneself, being single, being unmarried, by oneself, alone, just, o"
  },
  {
    "question": "手下",
    "answer": "てした,てか",
    "meaning": "subordinate, underling, henchman, minion"
  },
  {
    "question": "死刑",
    "answer": "しけい",
    "meaning": "death penalty, capital punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "十日",
    "answer": "とおか",
    "meaning": "tenth day of the month, ten days"
  },
  {
    "question": "一周",
    "answer": "いっしゅう",
    "meaning": "one round, one circuit, one revolution, one lap, one turn"
  },
  {
    "question": "価格",
    "answer": "かかく",
    "meaning": "price, value, cost"
  },
  {
    "question": "蝕む",
    "answer": "むしばむ",
    "meaning": "to be worm-eaten, to be eaten by worms, to affect adversely, to spoil, to ruin, to undermine, to gna"
  },
  {
    "question": "優等生",
    "answer": "ゆうとうせい",
    "meaning": "honor student, honours student, model student, prize pupil"
  },
  {
    "question": "退場",
    "answer": "たいじょう",
    "meaning": "exit (from a stage), exeunt, leaving, exit"
  },
  {
    "question": "容疑者",
    "answer": "ようぎしゃ",
    "meaning": "suspect (person)"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵隊",
    "answer": "へいたい",
    "meaning": "soldier, sailor"
  },
  {
    "question": "原理",
    "answer": "げんり",
    "meaning": "principle, theory, fundamental truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝達",
    "answer": "でんたつ",
    "meaning": "transmission (e.g. news, chemical signals, electricity), communication, delivery, conveyance, transf"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑草",
    "answer": "ざっそう",
    "meaning": "weed"
  },
  {
    "question": "此処",
    "answer": "ここ",
    "meaning": "here, this place, this point, now, these past ... (e.g. three years), these last ..., the next ... ("
  },
  {
    "question": "五百",
    "answer": "ごひゃく,いお",
    "meaning": "500, five hundred, many"
  },
  {
    "question": "咳き込む",
    "answer": "せきこむ",
    "meaning": "to cough violently, to have a coughing fit"
  },
  {
    "question": "生気",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "life, vitality, verve, vigor, vigour, animation, spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "泊める",
    "answer": "とめる",
    "meaning": "to give shelter to, to lodge, to put up, to accommodate"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪寒",
    "answer": "おかん",
    "meaning": "chill, shakes, ague"
  },
  {
    "question": "虹",
    "answer": "にじ",
    "meaning": "rainbow"
  },
  {
    "question": "行く手",
    "answer": "ゆくて",
    "meaning": "one's way, one's path"
  },
  {
    "question": "見",
    "answer": "み,けん",
    "meaning": "looking, viewing, (please) try (to), view (of life, etc.), outlook"
  },
  {
    "question": "勇敢",
    "answer": "ゆうかん",
    "meaning": "brave, heroic, gallant"
  },
  {
    "question": "面食らう",
    "answer": "めんくらう",
    "meaning": "to be confused, to be bewildered, to be taken aback"
  },
  {
    "question": "渇く",
    "answer": "かわく",
    "meaning": "to be thirsty, to feel thirsty, to thirst for, to crave"
  },
  {
    "question": "生やす",
    "answer": "はやす",
    "meaning": "to grow, to cultivate, to wear a beard"
  },
  {
    "question": "過ぎ去る",
    "answer": "すぎさる",
    "meaning": "to pass, to pass by"
  },
  {
    "question": "頂上",
    "answer": "ちょうじょう",
    "meaning": "top, summit, peak"
  },
  {
    "question": "五日",
    "answer": "いつか",
    "meaning": "fifth day of the month, five days"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃げ道",
    "answer": "にげみち",
    "meaning": "way out, means to escape, escape route"
  },
  {
    "question": "念を押す",
    "answer": "ねんをおす",
    "meaning": "to remind (someone of something), to call attention to, to make sure of, to emphasize, to emphasise"
  },
  {
    "question": "投資",
    "answer": "とうし",
    "meaning": "investment"
  },
  {
    "question": "精度",
    "answer": "せいど",
    "meaning": "precision, accuracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "競技",
    "answer": "きょうぎ",
    "meaning": "game, match, contest"
  },
  {
    "question": "全面的",
    "answer": "ぜんめんてき",
    "meaning": "total, complete, all-out, general, extensive, full-scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "和らげる",
    "answer": "やわらげる",
    "meaning": "to soften, to moderate, to relieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧み",
    "answer": "たくみ",
    "meaning": "skillful, adroit, dexterous, masterful, clever, ingenious, cunning"
  },
  {
    "question": "製作",
    "answer": "せいさく",
    "meaning": "manufacture, production"
  },
  {
    "question": "項垂れる",
    "answer": "うなだれる",
    "meaning": "to hang one's head"
  },
  {
    "question": "達人",
    "answer": "たつじん",
    "meaning": "master, expert"
  },
  {
    "question": "無知",
    "answer": "むち",
    "meaning": "ignorance, innocence, stupidity"
  },
  {
    "question": "出回る",
    "answer": "でまわる",
    "meaning": "to appear on the market, to be in season (e.g. fruit), to circulate widely, to make the rounds, to g"
  },
  {
    "question": "最早",
    "answer": "もはや",
    "meaning": "already, now, no longer, not any more"
  },
  {
    "question": "着用",
    "answer": "ちゃくよう",
    "meaning": "wearing (e.g. uniform, seat belt), having on"
  },
  {
    "question": "総合",
    "answer": "そうごう",
    "meaning": "synthesis, coordination, putting together, integration, composite, comprehensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "後押し",
    "answer": "あとおし",
    "meaning": "pushing, backing, boosting, supporting, pushing from behind (a cart, etc.), pusher"
  },
  {
    "question": "中継",
    "answer": "ちゅうけい,なかつぎ",
    "meaning": "relay, hook-up, relay broadcasting, joining, joint, intermediation, acting as an intermediary, relay"
  },
  {
    "question": "料金",
    "answer": "りょうきん",
    "meaning": "fee, charge, fare"
  },
  {
    "question": "内装",
    "answer": "ないそう",
    "meaning": "interior design, interior, upholstery"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑用",
    "answer": "ざつよう,ぞうよう",
    "meaning": "chores, odd jobs, miscellaneous affairs, miscellaneous expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "惨状",
    "answer": "さんじょう",
    "meaning": "disastrous scene, terrible spectacle"
  },
  {
    "question": "咀嚼",
    "answer": "そしゃく",
    "meaning": "chewing, mastication, digestion (e.g. of words), assimilation, comprehension, appreciation"
  },
  {
    "question": "喉元",
    "answer": "のどもと",
    "meaning": "throat"
  },
  {
    "question": "実力者",
    "answer": "じつりょくしゃ",
    "meaning": "influential person, powerful person, big wheel, big gun, power behind the throne"
  },
  {
    "question": "指令",
    "answer": "しれい",
    "meaning": "orders, instructions, directive, command"
  },
  {
    "question": "不運",
    "answer": "ふうん",
    "meaning": "misfortune, bad luck, ill luck, ill fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕舞う",
    "answer": "しまう",
    "meaning": "to finish, to stop, to end, to put an end to, to bring to a close, to close (a business, etc.), to c"
  },
  {
    "question": "逞しい",
    "answer": "たくましい",
    "meaning": "burly, strong, sturdy, indomitable, indefatigable, strong-willed, resolute, bold, robust (vitality,"
  },
  {
    "question": "記述",
    "answer": "きじゅつ",
    "meaning": "description, account"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹",
    "answer": "たけ",
    "meaning": "bamboo (any grass of subfamily Bambusoideae), middle (of a three-tier ranking system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "作法",
    "answer": "さほう,さくほう",
    "meaning": "manners, etiquette, propriety, manner of production (esp. of prose, poetry, etc.), way of making"
  },
  {
    "question": "兜",
    "answer": "かぶと",
    "meaning": "helmet (of a warrior), headpiece"
  },
  {
    "question": "結合",
    "answer": "けつごう",
    "meaning": "combination, union, binding, catenation, coupling, joining, bond"
  },
  {
    "question": "見解",
    "answer": "けんかい",
    "meaning": "opinion, point of view"
  },
  {
    "question": "噴出",
    "answer": "ふんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "spewing, gushing, spouting, eruption, effusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "所長",
    "answer": "しょちょう",
    "meaning": "chief, head (of an office, of a laboratory)"
  },
  {
    "question": "容器",
    "answer": "ようき",
    "meaning": "container, receptacle, vessel, packaging"
  },
  {
    "question": "首を捻る",
    "answer": "くびをひねる",
    "meaning": "to cock one's head in puzzlement, to tilt one's head in contemplation, to wrack one's brain, to thin"
  },
  {
    "question": "審査",
    "answer": "しんさ",
    "meaning": "judging, inspection, examination, investigation, review"
  },
  {
    "question": "丁重",
    "answer": "ていちょう",
    "meaning": "polite, courteous, hospitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "灯す",
    "answer": "ともす,とぼす",
    "meaning": "to light (a candle, lamp, etc.), to turn on (a light)"
  },
  {
    "question": "嬉々",
    "answer": "きき",
    "meaning": "merry, joyful, gleeful"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち取る",
    "answer": "かちとる",
    "meaning": "to exert oneself and win, to gain (victory)"
  },
  {
    "question": "癒える",
    "answer": "いえる",
    "meaning": "to recover, to be healed"
  },
  {
    "question": "見入る",
    "answer": "みいる",
    "meaning": "to gaze at, to fix one's eyes upon"
  },
  {
    "question": "静止",
    "answer": "せいし",
    "meaning": "stillness, repose, standing still"
  },
  {
    "question": "審判",
    "answer": "しんぱん,しんばん",
    "meaning": "refereeing, trial, judgement, judgment, umpire, referee"
  },
  {
    "question": "進言",
    "answer": "しんげん",
    "meaning": "advice (to a superior), counsel, proposal, suggestion, recommendation"
  },
  {
    "question": "昔話",
    "answer": "むかしばなし",
    "meaning": "old tale, folk tale, legend, reminiscence"
  },
  {
    "question": "恭しい",
    "answer": "うやうやしい",
    "meaning": "polite, respectful, reverent"
  },
  {
    "question": "勤務",
    "answer": "きんむ",
    "meaning": "service, duty, work"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅苦しい",
    "answer": "かたくるしい,かたぐるしい",
    "meaning": "formal, strict, ceremonious, stiff"
  },
  {
    "question": "火炎",
    "answer": "かえん",
    "meaning": "flame, blaze"
  },
  {
    "question": "塾",
    "answer": "じゅく",
    "meaning": "cram school, private tutoring school, juku"
  },
  {
    "question": "間隔",
    "answer": "かんかく",
    "meaning": "space, interval, space character, whitespace"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち切る",
    "answer": "うちきる",
    "meaning": "to stop, to abort, to discontinue, to close"
  },
  {
    "question": "強まる",
    "answer": "つよまる",
    "meaning": "to get strong, to gain strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍛冶",
    "answer": "かじ,たんや,かぬち",
    "meaning": "smithing, blacksmith"
  },
  {
    "question": "時空",
    "answer": "じくう",
    "meaning": "space-time"
  },
  {
    "question": "常連",
    "answer": "じょうれん",
    "meaning": "regular customer, regular patron, frequenter, constant companion"
  },
  {
    "question": "分際",
    "answer": "ぶんざい",
    "meaning": "social standing"
  },
  {
    "question": "処罰",
    "answer": "しょばつ",
    "meaning": "punishment, penalty"
  },
  {
    "question": "名称",
    "answer": "めいしょう",
    "meaning": "name, title"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄",
    "answer": "き",
    "meaning": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "報道",
    "answer": "ほうどう",
    "meaning": "report (of news), reporting, news, information, (media) coverage"
  },
  {
    "question": "退避",
    "answer": "たいひ",
    "meaning": "taking refuge, evacuation, backup (of data)"
  },
  {
    "question": "役人",
    "answer": "やくにん",
    "meaning": "government official"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩返し",
    "answer": "おんがえし",
    "meaning": "requital of a favour (favor), repayment (of an obligation, kindness, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狭間",
    "answer": "はざま,はさま",
    "meaning": "interval, space, interstice, threshold, valley, gorge, ravine, loophole (in a wall), crenel, eyelet"
  },
  {
    "question": "竜巻",
    "answer": "たつまき",
    "meaning": "tornado, waterspout"
  },
  {
    "question": "若き",
    "answer": "わかき",
    "meaning": "young person, youth, young"
  },
  {
    "question": "宴会",
    "answer": "えんかい",
    "meaning": "party, banquet, reception, feast, dinner"
  },
  {
    "question": "車輪",
    "answer": "しゃりん",
    "meaning": "(vehicle) wheel"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾",
    "answer": "いく,ほとほと",
    "meaning": "some, several, many, how many?, how much?, quite (usu. negative connotation), utterly, really"
  },
  {
    "question": "申し訳",
    "answer": "もうしわけ",
    "meaning": "apology, excuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "無効",
    "answer": "むこう",
    "meaning": "invalid, void, ineffective, unavailable"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱れ",
    "answer": "みだれ",
    "meaning": "disorder, disturbance, unrest"
  },
  {
    "question": "満月",
    "answer": "まんげつ",
    "meaning": "full moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "鷹",
    "answer": "たか",
    "meaning": "falcon (Falconidae spp.), hawk"
  },
  {
    "question": "密室",
    "answer": "みっしつ",
    "meaning": "room that cannot be entered (e.g. because it's locked from the inside), secret room"
  },
  {
    "question": "酷",
    "answer": "こく",
    "meaning": "severe, harsh, stringent, rigorous, strict, unfair"
  },
  {
    "question": "意味合い",
    "answer": "いみあい",
    "meaning": "implication, nuance, shade of meaning, connotation"
  },
  {
    "question": "高揚",
    "answer": "こうよう",
    "meaning": "elevation (of spirits), raising (of morale), uplift, upsurge"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮める",
    "answer": "しずめる",
    "meaning": "to appease, to suppress, to calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸い取る",
    "answer": "すいとる",
    "meaning": "to suck up, to absorb, to squeeze (money)"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛でる",
    "answer": "めでる",
    "meaning": "to love, to cherish, to admire, to appreciate"
  },
  {
    "question": "喧騒",
    "answer": "けんそう",
    "meaning": "tumult, great noise, clatter, hustle and bustle"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅館",
    "answer": "りょかん",
    "meaning": "ryokan, traditional inn, Japanese-style lodging, usu. professionally-run"
  },
  {
    "question": "必然的",
    "answer": "ひつぜんてき",
    "meaning": "inevitable, necessary"
  },
  {
    "question": "次ぐ",
    "answer": "つぐ",
    "meaning": "to rank next to, to come after"
  },
  {
    "question": "山道",
    "answer": "やまみち,さんどう,せんどう",
    "meaning": "mountain road, mountain trail"
  },
  {
    "question": "旋回",
    "answer": "せんかい",
    "meaning": "revolution, rotation, turning, circling, swiveling, turning (an aircraft or ship)"
  },
  {
    "question": "養子",
    "answer": "ようし",
    "meaning": "adopted child (usu. male), son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question": "沿う",
    "answer": "そう",
    "meaning": "to run along, to run beside, to stick to (a line), to follow (a policy, plan, etc.), to act in accor"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧",
    "answer": "あつ",
    "meaning": "pressure, force"
  },
  {
    "question": "軒",
    "answer": "のき,けん",
    "meaning": "eaves, narrow aisle surrounding the core of a temple building, counter for buildings (esp. houses),"
  },
  {
    "question": "衝撃波",
    "answer": "しょうげきは",
    "meaning": "shock wave"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶色い",
    "answer": "ちゃいろい",
    "meaning": "light brown, tawny"
  },
  {
    "question": "淵",
    "answer": "ふち",
    "meaning": "deep pool, deep water, abyss, depths (e.g. of despair, etc.), grip (e.g. of death)"
  },
  {
    "question": "粘液",
    "answer": "ねんえき",
    "meaning": "mucus, mucilage, viscous liquid, phlegm"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い難い",
    "answer": "いいがたい,いいにくい",
    "meaning": "hard to say, inexpressible, hesitant to say, embarrassing, delicate"
  },
  {
    "question": "殺戮",
    "answer": "さつりく",
    "meaning": "slaughter, massacre"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛す",
    "answer": "あいす",
    "meaning": "to love"
  },
  {
    "question": "引っ越し",
    "answer": "ひっこし",
    "meaning": "moving (dwelling, office, etc.), changing residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪者",
    "answer": "わるもの",
    "meaning": "bad guy, villain, evildoer, scoundrel"
  },
  {
    "question": "削ぐ",
    "answer": "そぐ",
    "meaning": "to chip (off), to shave (off), to slice (off), to sharpen, to dampen (e.g. enthusiasm), to discourag"
  },
  {
    "question": "品物",
    "answer": "しなもの",
    "meaning": "goods, article, thing"
  },
  {
    "question": "装",
    "answer": "そう",
    "meaning": "clothing, dressing, binding (of a book)"
  },
  {
    "question": "精神力",
    "answer": "せいしんりょく",
    "meaning": "emotional strength, force of will"
  },
  {
    "question": "様子見",
    "answer": "ようすみ",
    "meaning": "wait-and-see"
  },
  {
    "question": "合理的",
    "answer": "ごうりてき",
    "meaning": "rational, reasonable, logical"
  },
  {
    "question": "突っ込み",
    "answer": "つっこみ",
    "meaning": "thrust, charge, penetration, digging into (a matter), depth, straight man (of a comedy duo), quip, j"
  },
  {
    "question": "逢う",
    "answer": "あう",
    "meaning": "to meet, to encounter, to see, to have an accident, to have a bad experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "貴殿",
    "answer": "きでん",
    "meaning": "you, your residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "粘る",
    "answer": "ねばる",
    "meaning": "to be sticky, to be adhesive, to persevere, to persist, to stick to, to hold out, to linger"
  },
  {
    "question": "救い出す",
    "answer": "すくいだす",
    "meaning": "to rescue, to free"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸出し",
    "answer": "まるだし",
    "meaning": "exposing fully, uncovering completely, being in full view, putting on display, not disguising"
  },
  {
    "question": "水滴",
    "answer": "すいてき",
    "meaning": "drop of water, vessel for replenishing inkstone water"
  },
  {
    "question": "山脈",
    "answer": "やまなみ,さんみゃく",
    "meaning": "mountain range, mountain belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "期限",
    "answer": "きげん",
    "meaning": "term, period, time frame, time limit, deadline, cutoff (date)"
  },
  {
    "question": "胴",
    "answer": "どう",
    "meaning": "trunk, torso, body, abdomen, waist, plastron (in kendo), touching the plastron (kimari-te in kendo),"
  },
  {
    "question": "建築",
    "answer": "けんちく",
    "meaning": "construction, architecture (of buildings)"
  },
  {
    "question": "中指",
    "answer": "なかゆび,ちゅうし",
    "meaning": "middle finger, long finger, second finger, tall finger, middle toe, third toe"
  },
  {
    "question": "出張",
    "answer": "しゅっちょう",
    "meaning": "business trip, official trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "工作",
    "answer": "こうさく",
    "meaning": "handicraft, work, construction, manufacturing, maneuvering, manoeuvering"
  },
  {
    "question": "真夜中",
    "answer": "まよなか",
    "meaning": "dead of night, midnight"
  },
  {
    "question": "協会",
    "answer": "きょうかい",
    "meaning": "association, society, organization, organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "風味",
    "answer": "ふうみ",
    "meaning": "taste, flavor, flavour"
  },
  {
    "question": "後始末",
    "answer": "あとしまつ",
    "meaning": "settlement (of affairs), remedial measures, cleaning up afterwards"
  },
  {
    "question": "疼く",
    "answer": "うずく",
    "meaning": "to throb, to ache"
  },
  {
    "question": "光り輝く",
    "answer": "ひかりかがやく",
    "meaning": "to shine, to glitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "武具",
    "answer": "ぶぐ",
    "meaning": "arms, weapons (of war), armor, armour"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い回し",
    "answer": "いいまわし",
    "meaning": "expression, phraseology"
  },
  {
    "question": "学期",
    "answer": "がっき",
    "meaning": "school term, semester"
  },
  {
    "question": "番目",
    "answer": "ばんめ,つがいめ",
    "meaning": "indicates position in a sequence, divisions of a kabuki performance, joint, hinge"
  },
  {
    "question": "相場",
    "answer": "そうば",
    "meaning": "market price, speculation (e.g. on stocks), reputation (according to conventional wisdom), estimatio"
  },
  {
    "question": "激怒",
    "answer": "げきど",
    "meaning": "rage, indignation, exasperation"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏手",
    "answer": "うらて",
    "meaning": "back (esp. of a building, etc.), rear, behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "救世主",
    "answer": "きゅうせいしゅ",
    "meaning": "saviour, savior, messiah"
  },
  {
    "question": "家臣",
    "answer": "かしん",
    "meaning": "vassal, retainer"
  },
  {
    "question": "調合",
    "answer": "ちょうごう",
    "meaning": "mixing, compounding, dispensing (e.g. prescription)"
  },
  {
    "question": "断固",
    "answer": "だんこ",
    "meaning": "firm, determined, resolute, conclusive"
  },
  {
    "question": "叩き潰す",
    "answer": "たたきつぶす",
    "meaning": "to smash up, to defeat crushingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "降下",
    "answer": "こうか",
    "meaning": "descent, fall, drop, (atmospheric) depression, passing down (of an order, decree, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "瘴気",
    "answer": "しょうき",
    "meaning": "miasma, noxious form of 'bad air' formerly believed to cause diseases"
  },
  {
    "question": "弾力",
    "answer": "だんりょく",
    "meaning": "elasticity, flexibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "音色",
    "answer": "ねいろ,おんしょく",
    "meaning": "tone color, tone colour, tone quality, timbre"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い直す",
    "answer": "おもいなおす",
    "meaning": "to re-think, to think back upon, to change one's mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "気が合う",
    "answer": "きがあう",
    "meaning": "to get along (with someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "際立つ",
    "answer": "きわだつ",
    "meaning": "to be prominent, to be conspicuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "一対一",
    "answer": "いちたいいち,いったいいち",
    "meaning": "one-to-one, one-on-one"
  },
  {
    "question": "疾走",
    "answer": "しっそう",
    "meaning": "sprint, dash, scampering"
  },
  {
    "question": "清楚",
    "answer": "せいそ",
    "meaning": "neat and clean, tidy, trim"
  },
  {
    "question": "静けさ",
    "answer": "しずけさ",
    "meaning": "stillness, silence, hush, calm, serenity"
  },
  {
    "question": "六十",
    "answer": "ろくじゅう,むそ",
    "meaning": "sixty, 60"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛想",
    "answer": "あいそ,あいそう",
    "meaning": "amiability, friendliness, affability, sociability, fondness (of someone), affection, liking, complim"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち破る",
    "answer": "うちやぶる",
    "meaning": "to break, to smash, to defeat, to destroy, to eliminate"
  },
  {
    "question": "収集",
    "answer": "しゅうしゅう",
    "meaning": "collecting, accumulating, gathering, collection (of art, stamps, insects, etc.), garbage collection,"
  },
  {
    "question": "因果",
    "answer": "いんが",
    "meaning": "cause and effect, causality, karma, fate, unfortunate, unlucky, ill-fated"
  },
  {
    "question": "溝",
    "answer": "こう,みぞ,どぶ",
    "meaning": "10^32, hundred nonillion, ditch, drain, gutter, trench, groove, tread, gap (between people, countrie"
  },
  {
    "question": "感情的",
    "answer": "かんじょうてき",
    "meaning": "emotional, sentimental"
  },
  {
    "question": "両脇",
    "answer": "りょうわき",
    "meaning": "both sides"
  },
  {
    "question": "参戦",
    "answer": "さんせん",
    "meaning": "participation in a war, going to war, taking part in a competition or contest"
  },
  {
    "question": "満々",
    "answer": "まんまん",
    "meaning": "full of, brimming with"
  },
  {
    "question": "寺",
    "answer": "てら,じ",
    "meaning": "temple (Buddhist), counter for temples"
  },
  {
    "question": "育成",
    "answer": "いくせい",
    "meaning": "rearing, training, nurture, cultivation, promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "動",
    "answer": "どう",
    "meaning": "motion"
  },
  {
    "question": "掌握",
    "answer": "しょうあく",
    "meaning": "grasping, seizing, holding, commanding, having control over"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り合う",
    "answer": "つりあう",
    "meaning": "to balance, to be in harmony, to be in equilibrium, to suit, to go well together, to be a good match"
  },
  {
    "question": "蘇生",
    "answer": "そせい",
    "meaning": "revival, resuscitation, revitalization, rejuvenation, regeneration"
  },
  {
    "question": "か否か",
    "answer": "かいなか",
    "meaning": "whether or not"
  },
  {
    "question": "重々しい",
    "answer": "おもおもしい",
    "meaning": "serious, grave, dignified, solemn"
  },
  {
    "question": "司令官",
    "answer": "しれいかん",
    "meaning": "commandant, commanding officer, general"
  },
  {
    "question": "発達",
    "answer": "はったつ",
    "meaning": "development, growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "犯",
    "answer": "はん",
    "meaning": "perpetrators of (some) crime, (some type of) crime"
  },
  {
    "question": "本屋",
    "answer": "ほんおく,ほんや",
    "meaning": "principal residence, bookstore, bookshop, publisher, main building"
  },
  {
    "question": "災厄",
    "answer": "さいやく",
    "meaning": "calamity, disaster, accident"
  },
  {
    "question": "悠然",
    "answer": "ゆうぜん",
    "meaning": "calm, composed, leisurely"
  },
  {
    "question": "交戦",
    "answer": "こうせん",
    "meaning": "war, battle, hostilities"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻め込む",
    "answer": "せめこむ",
    "meaning": "to invade, to attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "交じり",
    "answer": "まじり",
    "meaning": "mixed, mingled"
  },
  {
    "question": "視野",
    "answer": "しや",
    "meaning": "field of vision, view, one's outlook (e.g. on life), one's horizons"
  },
  {
    "question": "息抜き",
    "answer": "いきぬき",
    "meaning": "taking a breather, relaxation, vent hole"
  },
  {
    "question": "台本",
    "answer": "だいほん",
    "meaning": "script, libretto, scenario"
  },
  {
    "question": "双眸",
    "answer": "そうぼう",
    "meaning": "pair of eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "身支度",
    "answer": "みじたく",
    "meaning": "dress, outfit, getup, to dress oneself, to outfit oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "撤回",
    "answer": "てっかい",
    "meaning": "withdrawal, retraction, revocation, repeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕立てる",
    "answer": "したてる",
    "meaning": "to tailor, to make (clothing), to train, to bring up, to make it seem like, to pass off, to turn int"
  },
  {
    "question": "破綻",
    "answer": "はたん",
    "meaning": "failure, collapse, breakdown, break-up, bankruptcy"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛翔",
    "answer": "ひしょう",
    "meaning": "flight, flying, soaring"
  },
  {
    "question": "支払い",
    "answer": "しはらい",
    "meaning": "payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "通達",
    "answer": "つうたつ,つうだつ",
    "meaning": "notification, official notice, directive (e.g. from higher to lower levels of the administration), b"
  },
  {
    "question": "占領",
    "answer": "せんりょう",
    "meaning": "occupying, having (an area) all to oneself, military occupation, possession, capture, seizure"
  },
  {
    "question": "労働",
    "answer": "ろうどう",
    "meaning": "manual labor, manual labour, toil, work, Labour Party"
  },
  {
    "question": "四日",
    "answer": "よっか",
    "meaning": "fourth day of the month, four days"
  },
  {
    "question": "割合",
    "answer": "わりあい",
    "meaning": "rate, ratio, percentage, proportion, comparatively, contrary to expectations"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉体的",
    "answer": "にくたいてき",
    "meaning": "bodily, physical, corporeal, sexual, sensual, of the flesh"
  },
  {
    "question": "啜る",
    "answer": "すする",
    "meaning": "to sip, to slurp"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び戻す",
    "answer": "よびもどす",
    "meaning": "to call (someone) back, to recall, to call home, to bring back (memories, etc.), to revive"
  },
  {
    "question": "貶める",
    "answer": "おとしめる",
    "meaning": "to show contempt for, to look down upon, to have a low opinion of, to cause to fall, to make decline"
  },
  {
    "question": "復興",
    "answer": "ふっこう",
    "meaning": "revival, reconstruction, restoration, rebuilding, recovery, renaissance"
  },
  {
    "question": "必要性",
    "answer": "ひつようせい",
    "meaning": "necessity"
  },
  {
    "question": "救助",
    "answer": "きゅうじょ",
    "meaning": "relief, aid, rescue"
  },
  {
    "question": "生息",
    "answer": "せいそく",
    "meaning": "inhabiting, living"
  },
  {
    "question": "身柄",
    "answer": "みがら",
    "meaning": "one's person"
  },
  {
    "question": "期",
    "answer": "き,ご",
    "meaning": "period, time, opportunity, chance, occasion, age, term (e.g. in office), session (e.g. of parliament"
  },
  {
    "question": "制",
    "answer": "せい",
    "meaning": "system, organization, organisation, imperial command, laws, regulation, control, government, suppres"
  },
  {
    "question": "力任せ",
    "answer": "ちからまかせ",
    "meaning": "with all one's strength, with all one's might"
  },
  {
    "question": "衆",
    "answer": "しゅう,しゅ",
    "meaning": "great numbers (of people), numerical superiority, masses, people, folk, clique, bunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "古びる",
    "answer": "ふるびる",
    "meaning": "to look old, to get old"
  },
  {
    "question": "需要",
    "answer": "じゅよう",
    "meaning": "demand, request"
  },
  {
    "question": "虜",
    "answer": "とりこ,りょ",
    "meaning": "captive, prisoner, victim (of love, etc.), slave (to one's lust, etc.), foreigner, barbarian, slave"
  },
  {
    "question": "校長",
    "answer": "こうちょう",
    "meaning": "principal, headmaster"
  },
  {
    "question": "実る",
    "answer": "みのる",
    "meaning": "to bear fruit, to ripen"
  },
  {
    "question": "同期",
    "answer": "どうき",
    "meaning": "same period, corresponding period, same year (of graduation, entering a company, etc.), contemporary"
  },
  {
    "question": "満点",
    "answer": "まんてん",
    "meaning": "perfect score, full marks, extremely, very, quite"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り刻む",
    "answer": "きりきざむ",
    "meaning": "to hew, to chop up, to mangle, to mince"
  },
  {
    "question": "恐れ入る",
    "answer": "おそれいる",
    "meaning": "to be sorry, to beg pardon, to be much obliged, to feel small, to be grateful, to be amazed, to be f"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮込む",
    "answer": "にこむ",
    "meaning": "to boil well, to stew, to simmer (for a long time), to cook (various ingredients) together"
  },
  {
    "question": "広範囲",
    "answer": "こうはんい",
    "meaning": "extensive, vast range, wide scope"
  },
  {
    "question": "潜伏",
    "answer": "せんぷく",
    "meaning": "concealment, hiding, ambush, incubation, latency, dormancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰け反る",
    "answer": "のけぞる",
    "meaning": "to bend backwards, to bend oneself back, to be taken aback"
  },
  {
    "question": "人柄",
    "answer": "ひとがら",
    "meaning": "personality, character, personal appearance, gentility"
  },
  {
    "question": "真理",
    "answer": "しんり",
    "meaning": "truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "怒号",
    "answer": "どごう",
    "meaning": "angry roar, bellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "確立",
    "answer": "かくりつ",
    "meaning": "establishment, settlement"
  },
  {
    "question": "別物",
    "answer": "べつもの",
    "meaning": "another thing, exception, special case"
  },
  {
    "question": "哀しい",
    "answer": "かなしい",
    "meaning": "sad, miserable, unhappy, sorrowful, lamentable, deplorable, grievous"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤毛",
    "answer": "あかげ",
    "meaning": "red hair, ginger hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "不死",
    "answer": "ふし",
    "meaning": "immortality, eternal life, undeath, undead"
  },
  {
    "question": "経路",
    "answer": "けいろ",
    "meaning": "course, route, path, channel, process, means"
  },
  {
    "question": "同性",
    "answer": "どうせい",
    "meaning": "same sex"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅潮",
    "answer": "こうちょう",
    "meaning": "flush, blush"
  },
  {
    "question": "好機",
    "answer": "こうき",
    "meaning": "good opportunity, chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "食糧",
    "answer": "しょくりょう",
    "meaning": "food (esp. staple food such as rice or wheat), provisions, rations, food supply"
  },
  {
    "question": "有意義",
    "answer": "ゆういぎ",
    "meaning": "significant, useful, meaningful, worthwhile, valuable, of interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "温まる",
    "answer": "あたたまる,あったまる,ぬくまる",
    "meaning": "to warm oneself, to sun oneself, to warm up, to get warm"
  },
  {
    "question": "正規",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "regular, normal, formal, legal, established, legitimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "回路",
    "answer": "かいろ",
    "meaning": "circuit (electric), cycle (e.g. Krebs cycle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "二年生",
    "answer": "にねんせい",
    "meaning": "second-year student, biennial"
  },
  {
    "question": "校庭",
    "answer": "こうてい",
    "meaning": "schoolyard, playground, school grounds, campus"
  },
  {
    "question": "手分け",
    "answer": "てわけ",
    "meaning": "division of labour, division of labor, splitting into groups (e.g. to search)"
  },
  {
    "question": "素朴",
    "answer": "そぼく",
    "meaning": "simple, artless, naive, unsophisticated"
  },
  {
    "question": "獰猛",
    "answer": "どうもう,ねいもう",
    "meaning": "ferocious, fierce, truculent, savage"
  },
  {
    "question": "程遠い",
    "answer": "ほどとおい",
    "meaning": "far away, far off"
  },
  {
    "question": "嗅覚",
    "answer": "きゅうかく",
    "meaning": "sense of smell, olfaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き金",
    "answer": "ひきがね",
    "meaning": "trigger (of a gun, etc.), trigger (for something), immediate cause"
  },
  {
    "question": "汚染",
    "answer": "おせん",
    "meaning": "pollution, contamination"
  },
  {
    "question": "統治",
    "answer": "とうち,とうじ",
    "meaning": "rule, reign, government, governing"
  },
  {
    "question": "我が身",
    "answer": "わがみ",
    "meaning": "myself, oneself, I, me, you (referring to one's inferior)"
  },
  {
    "question": "診察",
    "answer": "しんさつ",
    "meaning": "medical examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "下腹部",
    "answer": "かふくぶ",
    "meaning": "abdomen"
  },
  {
    "question": "連",
    "answer": "れん,むらじ",
    "meaning": "two reams (of paper), 1000 sheets (of paper), stanza, verse, tribe (in taxonomy), forecast (bet), be"
  },
  {
    "question": "武力",
    "answer": "ぶりょく",
    "meaning": "armed might, military power, the sword, force"
  },
  {
    "question": "憤怒",
    "answer": "ふんぬ,ふんど",
    "meaning": "anger, rage, resentment, indignation, exasperation"
  },
  {
    "question": "占拠",
    "answer": "せんきょ",
    "meaning": "occupation (e.g. of territory), exclusive possession"
  },
  {
    "question": "誠に",
    "answer": "まことに",
    "meaning": "indeed, really, absolutely, truly, actually, very, quite"
  },
  {
    "question": "最前線",
    "answer": "さいぜんせん",
    "meaning": "front line, forefront"
  },
  {
    "question": "陽光",
    "answer": "ようこう",
    "meaning": "sunshine, sunlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "外国人",
    "answer": "がいこくじん",
    "meaning": "foreigner, foreign citizen, foreign national, alien, non-Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "前足",
    "answer": "まえあし",
    "meaning": "forefoot, forefeet, foreleg, forelimb"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾ら",
    "answer": "いくら",
    "meaning": "how much, something over, and something, -odd, however (much), no matter how"
  },
  {
    "question": "大方",
    "answer": "おおかた",
    "meaning": "large part, greater part, majority, people in general, general public, public at large, mostly, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "選定",
    "answer": "せんてい",
    "meaning": "selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽快",
    "answer": "けいかい",
    "meaning": "light (of movements), nimble, sprightly, springy, light-hearted, cheerful, buoyant, jaunty, casual ("
  },
  {
    "question": "王位",
    "answer": "おうい",
    "meaning": "the throne, the crown"
  },
  {
    "question": "束の間",
    "answer": "つかのま",
    "meaning": "moment, brief space of time"
  },
  {
    "question": "血の気",
    "answer": "ちのけ",
    "meaning": "blood (in one's face, cheeks, etc.), colour, color, hot-bloodedness, hotheadedness, impulsive temper"
  },
  {
    "question": "不公平",
    "answer": "ふこうへい",
    "meaning": "unfairness, injustice, partiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵力",
    "answer": "へいりょく",
    "meaning": "military force, force of arms, strength of an army"
  },
  {
    "question": "承認",
    "answer": "しょうにん",
    "meaning": "recognition, acknowledgement, acknowledgment, approval, consent, agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "醸し出す",
    "answer": "かもしだす",
    "meaning": "to create (an atmosphere, feeling, etc.), to produce, to engender"
  },
  {
    "question": "婿",
    "answer": "むこ",
    "meaning": "husband, groom, (one's) son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question": "上気",
    "answer": "じょうき,うわき",
    "meaning": "flushing (of one's cheeks), dizziness, rush of blood to the head, extramarital sex, affair, fooling"
  },
  {
    "question": "人前",
    "answer": "にんまえ,ひとまえ",
    "meaning": "portion of food, presence of other people, (in) public, (in) front of others"
  },
  {
    "question": "備わる",
    "answer": "そなわる",
    "meaning": "to be furnished with, to be provided with, to be equipped with, to be possessed of, to be endowed wi"
  },
  {
    "question": "上出来",
    "answer": "じょうでき",
    "meaning": "good performance, good work, great success"
  },
  {
    "question": "終始",
    "answer": "しゅうし",
    "meaning": "beginning and end, doing something from beginning to end, being unchanged from beginning to end, fro"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し方",
    "answer": "はなしかた",
    "meaning": "way of talking, speaking style"
  },
  {
    "question": "課長",
    "answer": "かちょう",
    "meaning": "section manager, section chief"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し声",
    "answer": "はなしごえ",
    "meaning": "speaking voice, talking voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "術者",
    "answer": "じゅつしゃ",
    "meaning": "practitioner (in medicine, art, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "石造り",
    "answer": "いしづくり",
    "meaning": "(made of) stone, stone-built"
  },
  {
    "question": "思春期",
    "answer": "ししゅんき",
    "meaning": "puberty, adolescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "警察官",
    "answer": "けいさつかん",
    "meaning": "police officer, policeman, policewoman"
  },
  {
    "question": "矛先",
    "answer": "ほこさき",
    "meaning": "point of spear, spearhead, brunt, aim of attack, force of argument"
  },
  {
    "question": "凍り付く",
    "answer": "こおりつく",
    "meaning": "to freeze to, to be frozen to, to freeze in place, to be still"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶番",
    "answer": "ちゃばん",
    "meaning": "farce, charade, person who serves tea, short and humorous improvised sketch (originating from Edo-er"
  },
  {
    "question": "災害",
    "answer": "さいがい",
    "meaning": "calamity, disaster, misfortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "に当たり",
    "answer": "にあたり",
    "meaning": "on the occasion of, at the time of"
  },
  {
    "question": "消去",
    "answer": "しょうきょ",
    "meaning": "elimination, erasure, clearing, dissipating, melting away, elimination (of variables)"
  },
  {
    "question": "回廊",
    "answer": "かいろう",
    "meaning": "corridor, gallery, hallway, cloister (i.e. covered walk typically circling a building or garden, esp"
  },
  {
    "question": "掠れる",
    "answer": "かすれる",
    "meaning": "to get blurred, to get hoarse, to get husky, to graze, to scrape, to touch"
  },
  {
    "question": "率先",
    "answer": "そっせん",
    "meaning": "taking the initiative"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼓膜",
    "answer": "こまく",
    "meaning": "eardrum, tympanic membrane"
  },
  {
    "question": "死骸",
    "answer": "しがい",
    "meaning": "(dead) body, corpse, carcass, remains"
  },
  {
    "question": "没収",
    "answer": "ぼっしゅう",
    "meaning": "forfeiture, seizure, confiscation, impounding"
  },
  {
    "question": "退出",
    "answer": "たいしゅつ",
    "meaning": "leaving (e.g. work at end of day), withdrawal (e.g. from a noble's or superior's presence), exit (e."
  },
  {
    "question": "儀",
    "answer": "ぎ",
    "meaning": "ceremony, matter, affair, with regard to, as for, as concerns"
  },
  {
    "question": "靴下",
    "answer": "くつした",
    "meaning": "socks, sock, stockings, stocking"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸中",
    "answer": "きょうちゅう",
    "meaning": "one's heart, one's mind, one's intentions"
  },
  {
    "question": "号令",
    "answer": "ごうれい",
    "meaning": "order (esp. to a number of people), command, ritual of bowing at start and end of school class"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾かす",
    "answer": "かわかす",
    "meaning": "to dry (clothes, etc.), to desiccate"
  },
  {
    "question": "新入生",
    "answer": "しんにゅうせい",
    "meaning": "new student, freshman, first-year student"
  },
  {
    "question": "君臨",
    "answer": "くんりん",
    "meaning": "reigning, controlling, to reign, to dictate, to control"
  },
  {
    "question": "大小",
    "answer": "だいしょう",
    "meaning": "size, large and small (sizes), various sizes, daishō (matched pair of long and short swords), large"
  },
  {
    "question": "血を引く",
    "answer": "ちをひく",
    "meaning": "to be descended from, to inherit (a disposition, etc.) from one's ancestors"
  },
  {
    "question": "連れ",
    "answer": "つれ,づれ",
    "meaning": "companion, company, tritagonist, in the company of, accompanied by ..., as a group comprising ..., l"
  },
  {
    "question": "警報",
    "answer": "けいほう",
    "meaning": "alarm, warning"
  },
  {
    "question": "大広間",
    "answer": "おおひろま",
    "meaning": "banquet or reception hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "味噌汁",
    "answer": "みそしる",
    "meaning": "miso soup"
  },
  {
    "question": "浜",
    "answer": "はま",
    "meaning": "beach, seashore, captured pieces (in the game of go), captured stones, Yokohama, riverbank, riversid"
  },
  {
    "question": "身代わり",
    "answer": "みがわり",
    "meaning": "substitution (for someone else), substitute, stand-in, scapegoat, sacrifice"
  },
  {
    "question": "聡明",
    "answer": "そうめい",
    "meaning": "wise, sagacious, intelligent, sensible"
  },
  {
    "question": "窓ガラス",
    "answer": "まどガラス",
    "meaning": "windowpane, window glass"
  },
  {
    "question": "着",
    "answer": "ちゃく,ぎ",
    "meaning": "counter for suits of clothing, arriving at ..., clothes, outfit, uniform"
  },
  {
    "question": "土産",
    "answer": "みやげ,どさん,とさん",
    "meaning": "local specialty or souvenir bought as a gift while travelling, present brought by a visitor, somethi"
  },
  {
    "question": "姫君",
    "answer": "ひめぎみ",
    "meaning": "daughter of a person of high rank (esp. eldest daughter)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一振り",
    "answer": "ひとふり",
    "meaning": "one swing, one shake (e.g. of pepper), one sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "希少",
    "answer": "きしょう",
    "meaning": "scarce, rare"
  },
  {
    "question": "役員",
    "answer": "やくいん",
    "meaning": "director, executive, officer, official, person in charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "遅れ",
    "answer": "おくれ",
    "meaning": "delay, lag, postponement, falling behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "大違い",
    "answer": "おおちがい",
    "meaning": "great difference, major mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "内面",
    "answer": "ないめん,うちづら",
    "meaning": "inside, interior, the face one presents at home"
  },
  {
    "question": "下校",
    "answer": "げこう",
    "meaning": "coming home from school"
  },
  {
    "question": "滅亡",
    "answer": "めつぼう",
    "meaning": "downfall, ruin, collapse, destruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣戦布告",
    "answer": "せんせんふこく",
    "meaning": "declaration of war, proclamation of war"
  },
  {
    "question": "十一",
    "answer": "じゅういち,といち,とおいち",
    "meaning": "eleven, 11, jack (playing card), Hodgson's hawk-cuckoo (Cuculus fugax), Horsfield's hawk cuckoo, typ"
  },
  {
    "question": "許容",
    "answer": "きょよう",
    "meaning": "permission, allowance, acceptance, tolerance, pardon"
  },
  {
    "question": "漢字",
    "answer": "かんじ",
    "meaning": "kanji, Chinese characters"
  },
  {
    "question": "振舞う",
    "answer": "ふるまう",
    "meaning": "to behave, to conduct oneself, to entertain, to treat someone (to a drink), to make tea for someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち並ぶ",
    "answer": "たちならぶ",
    "meaning": "to stand in a row (e.g. shops on a street), to line in a row, to line, to be equal to, to be on a pa"
  },
  {
    "question": "激昂",
    "answer": "げっこう,げきこう",
    "meaning": "excitement, exasperation, indignation, rage, fury"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧縮",
    "answer": "あっしゅく",
    "meaning": "compression, condensation, constriction, compaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽",
    "answer": "けい",
    "meaning": "light (e.g. aircraft, truck), light motor vehicle (up to 660cc and 64bhp), kei car"
  },
  {
    "question": "劇的",
    "answer": "げきてき",
    "meaning": "dramatic, exciting, touching, extreme"
  },
  {
    "question": "激情",
    "answer": "げきじょう",
    "meaning": "violent emotion, passion, fury"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆け引き",
    "answer": "かけひき",
    "meaning": "bargaining, haggling, tactics, strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "稲妻",
    "answer": "いなずま,いなづま",
    "meaning": "lightning, flash of lightning, lightning bolt"
  },
  {
    "question": "破く",
    "answer": "やぶく",
    "meaning": "to tear, to rip"
  },
  {
    "question": "半数",
    "answer": "はんすう",
    "meaning": "half the number, haploid"
  },
  {
    "question": "膜",
    "answer": "まく",
    "meaning": "membrane, film"
  },
  {
    "question": "壇上",
    "answer": "だんじょう",
    "meaning": "on a stage, on a platform, on an altar"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱者",
    "answer": "じゃくしゃ",
    "meaning": "weak person, the weak, vulnerable person, disadvantaged person"
  },
  {
    "question": "連鎖",
    "answer": "れんさ",
    "meaning": "chain, chaining, connection, (genetic) linkage"
  },
  {
    "question": "電撃",
    "answer": "でんげき",
    "meaning": "electric shock, blitz, lightning attack, sudden and without warning, shocking"
  },
  {
    "question": "順位",
    "answer": "じゅんい",
    "meaning": "order, rank, position (e.g. in a race), precedence"
  },
  {
    "question": "気が利く",
    "answer": "きがきく",
    "meaning": "to be sensible, to be smart, to be tasteful, to be thoughtful, to be tactful, to be sensitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "覇気",
    "answer": "はき",
    "meaning": "spirit, drive, vigour, vigor, ambition, aspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "顕現",
    "answer": "けんげん",
    "meaning": "manifestation"
  },
  {
    "question": "枕元",
    "answer": "まくらもと",
    "meaning": "bedside, near one's pillow"
  },
  {
    "question": "助力",
    "answer": "じょりょく",
    "meaning": "assistance, support"
  },
  {
    "question": "一様",
    "answer": "いちよう",
    "meaning": "uniform, equal, even, the same, identical, common, ordinary, usual"
  },
  {
    "question": "迂回",
    "answer": "うかい",
    "meaning": "detour, circumvention, turning movement"
  },
  {
    "question": "無粋",
    "answer": "ぶすい",
    "meaning": "boorish, inelegant, unpolished, unromantic, tactless"
  },
  {
    "question": "之",
    "answer": "これ,の",
    "meaning": "this, this one, this person, now, this point (in time), here, used to stress the subject of a senten"
  },
  {
    "question": "素顔",
    "answer": "すがお",
    "meaning": "face with no make-up, unpainted face, true face (of a country, celebrity, etc.), real face, true pic"
  },
  {
    "question": "染み込む",
    "answer": "しみこむ",
    "meaning": "to soak into, to permeate, to penetrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪趣味",
    "answer": "あくしゅみ",
    "meaning": "bad taste"
  },
  {
    "question": "畏怖",
    "answer": "いふ",
    "meaning": "awe, fear, dread, fright"
  },
  {
    "question": "筋合い",
    "answer": "すじあい",
    "meaning": "reason, right"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻想的",
    "answer": "げんそうてき",
    "meaning": "fantastic, magical, wondrous, whimsical, fairytale-like, romantic"
  },
  {
    "question": "抱擁",
    "answer": "ほうよう",
    "meaning": "embrace, hug, holding in one's arms"
  },
  {
    "question": "身じろぎ",
    "answer": "みじろぎ",
    "meaning": "stirring, slight movement"
  },
  {
    "question": "抱っこ",
    "answer": "だっこ",
    "meaning": "hug, carrying in one's arms (a baby, pet, doll, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治的",
    "answer": "せいじてき",
    "meaning": "political"
  },
  {
    "question": "強盗",
    "answer": "ごうとう",
    "meaning": "robber, mugger, robbery, burglary"
  },
  {
    "question": "前触れ",
    "answer": "まえぶれ",
    "meaning": "advance warning, previous notice, announcement, herald, harbinger, forerunner, portent, omen"
  },
  {
    "question": "搭載",
    "answer": "とうさい",
    "meaning": "loading (on board), equipping, equipped (with), built-in"
  },
  {
    "question": "瀕死",
    "answer": "ひんし",
    "meaning": "(on the) verge of death"
  },
  {
    "question": "意味深",
    "answer": "いみしん,いみぶか",
    "meaning": "with profound (often hidden) meaning, pregnant with significance, meaningful, suggestive, interestin"
  },
  {
    "question": "風紀",
    "answer": "ふうき",
    "meaning": "public morals, discipline, rules governing social behavior"
  },
  {
    "question": "流通",
    "answer": "りゅうつう",
    "meaning": "circulation (money, goods, etc.), distribution, circulation (air, water, etc.), ventilation, flow, n"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝息",
    "answer": "ねいき",
    "meaning": "breathing of a sleeping person"
  },
  {
    "question": "極上",
    "answer": "ごくじょう",
    "meaning": "first-rate, finest quality, the best"
  },
  {
    "question": "正々堂々",
    "answer": "せいせいどうどう",
    "meaning": "fair and square, open and aboveboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "気さく",
    "answer": "きさく",
    "meaning": "friendly, openhearted, sociable, amiable, good-humored, good-humoured, frank, candid, willing, ready"
  },
  {
    "question": "講師",
    "answer": "こうし",
    "meaning": "lecturer"
  },
  {
    "question": "白濁",
    "answer": "はくだく",
    "meaning": "cloudiness, turbidity, nebula (medical)"
  },
  {
    "question": "力尽きる",
    "answer": "ちからつきる",
    "meaning": "to use up all one's strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "感性",
    "answer": "かんせい",
    "meaning": "sensitivity, sensitiveness, sense (of ...)"
  },
  {
    "question": "外套",
    "answer": "がいとう",
    "meaning": "overcoat, greatcoat, cloak, wrap, mantle"
  },
  {
    "question": "墜落",
    "answer": "ついらく",
    "meaning": "fall, crash (e.g. aircraft)"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪神",
    "answer": "じゃしん",
    "meaning": "evil god"
  },
  {
    "question": "付着",
    "answer": "ふちゃく",
    "meaning": "sticking to, clinging to, adhesion, cohesion, agglutination"
  },
  {
    "question": "錬金術",
    "answer": "れんきんじゅつ",
    "meaning": "alchemy, way of making money, moneymaker, money-spinner"
  },
  {
    "question": "全速力",
    "answer": "ぜんそくりょく",
    "meaning": "full speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "知能",
    "answer": "ちのう",
    "meaning": "intelligence, intellect, brains"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛感",
    "answer": "つうかん",
    "meaning": "feeling keenly, fully realizing"
  },
  {
    "question": "二つ目",
    "answer": "ふたつめ",
    "meaning": "one after next, second"
  },
  {
    "question": "新型",
    "answer": "しんがた",
    "meaning": "new type, new style, new model, new strain (e.g. infectious disease)"
  },
  {
    "question": "臣下",
    "answer": "しんか",
    "meaning": "retainer, subject, vassal, servant"
  },
  {
    "question": "手近",
    "answer": "てぢか,てじか",
    "meaning": "near, close by, within reach, handy, familiar"
  },
  {
    "question": "力量",
    "answer": "りきりょう",
    "meaning": "ability, capacity, capability, talent, physical strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "各所",
    "answer": "かくしょ",
    "meaning": "each place, various places"
  },
  {
    "question": "布地",
    "answer": "ぬのじ,きれじ",
    "meaning": "cloth, fabric"
  },
  {
    "question": "顧問",
    "answer": "こもん",
    "meaning": "adviser, advisor, consultant"
  },
  {
    "question": "最愛",
    "answer": "さいあい",
    "meaning": "beloved, dearest"
  },
  {
    "question": "拉致",
    "answer": "らち,らっち",
    "meaning": "taking captive, carrying away, kidnapping, kidnaping, abduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛用",
    "answer": "あいよう",
    "meaning": "favorite, favourite, habitually used"
  },
  {
    "question": "糾弾",
    "answer": "きゅうだん",
    "meaning": "censure, denunciation, (verbal) attack, blaming"
  },
  {
    "question": "壮絶",
    "answer": "そうぜつ",
    "meaning": "grand, heroic, sublime, fierce"
  },
  {
    "question": "劇場",
    "answer": "げきじょう",
    "meaning": "theatre, theater, playhouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒸発",
    "answer": "じょうはつ",
    "meaning": "evaporation, disappearance (of people intentionally concealing their whereabouts), unexplained disap"
  },
  {
    "question": "理想的",
    "answer": "りそうてき",
    "meaning": "ideal"
  },
  {
    "question": "規定",
    "answer": "きてい",
    "meaning": "stipulation, prescription, provision, regulation, rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "旨",
    "answer": "むね",
    "meaning": "principle, aim, main purpose, central part, pillar, purport, gist, drift, meaning, instructions, ord"
  },
  {
    "question": "親密",
    "answer": "しんみつ",
    "meaning": "intimacy, friendship"
  },
  {
    "question": "斬",
    "answer": "ざん",
    "meaning": "beheading, decapitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜き取る",
    "answer": "ぬきとる",
    "meaning": "to pull out, to draw out, to disconnect, to steal contents of, to pilfer (from), to pickpocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "接客",
    "answer": "せっきゃく",
    "meaning": "serving customers, looking after visitors, reception"
  },
  {
    "question": "塵",
    "answer": "ごみ,ちり,じん",
    "meaning": "rubbish, trash, garbage, refuse, dust, dirt, defilement, impurity, affliction, object (perceived wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎌",
    "answer": "かま",
    "meaning": "sickle, leading question, trick question, sickle-and-chain (weapon), spear with curved cross-blades,"
  },
  {
    "question": "彫刻",
    "answer": "ちょうこく",
    "meaning": "carving, engraving, sculpture"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛める",
    "answer": "いためる,やめる",
    "meaning": "to hurt, to injure, to cause pain, to harm, to damage, to spoil, to worry, to bother, to be grieved"
  },
  {
    "question": "執務",
    "answer": "しつむ",
    "meaning": "performance of one's official duties"
  },
  {
    "question": "呻き声",
    "answer": "うめきごえ",
    "meaning": "groan, moan, moaning"
  },
  {
    "question": "常識的",
    "answer": "じょうしきてき",
    "meaning": "ordinary, sensible, commonplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "先回り",
    "answer": "さきまわり",
    "meaning": "going on ahead, forestalling, anticipating, arrival before another"
  },
  {
    "question": "目印",
    "answer": "めじるし",
    "meaning": "mark (for quick identification or recognition), sign, landmark, guide, trademark"
  },
  {
    "question": "不都合",
    "answer": "ふつごう",
    "meaning": "inconvenient, inexpedient, unfavourable, troublesome, difficult, wrong, improper, objectionable, unj"
  },
  {
    "question": "印象的",
    "answer": "いんしょうてき",
    "meaning": "impressive, striking, memorable, impactful"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖艶",
    "answer": "ようえん",
    "meaning": "fascinating, voluptuous, bewitching, captivating"
  },
  {
    "question": "転倒",
    "answer": "てんとう,てんどう",
    "meaning": "falling down, tumbling, overturning, turning over, reversing, inverting, inversion, getting upset, c"
  },
  {
    "question": "繁栄",
    "answer": "はんえい",
    "meaning": "prosperity, thriving, flourishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "経歴",
    "answer": "けいれき",
    "meaning": "personal history, career"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き届く",
    "answer": "いきとどく,ゆきとどく",
    "meaning": "to be scrupulous, to be attentive, to be prudent, to be complete, to be thorough"
  },
  {
    "question": "化身",
    "answer": "けしん",
    "meaning": "incarnation, impersonation, personification, avatar"
  },
  {
    "question": "発売",
    "answer": "はつばい",
    "meaning": "sale, offering for sale, release (for sale), launch (product)"
  },
  {
    "question": "真似る",
    "answer": "まねる",
    "meaning": "to mimic, to imitate"
  },
  {
    "question": "霞",
    "answer": "かすみ",
    "meaning": "haze (esp. in spring), mist, dimness (of sight)"
  },
  {
    "question": "語尾",
    "answer": "ごび",
    "meaning": "(inflected) end of a word, end of a sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "静まる",
    "answer": "しずまる",
    "meaning": "to become quiet, to quiet down, to quieten down, to calm down, to die down, to subside, to abate, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "入浴",
    "answer": "にゅうよく",
    "meaning": "bathing, to bathe, to take a bath, to enter a bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "血走る",
    "answer": "ちばしる",
    "meaning": "to become bloodshot"
  },
  {
    "question": "負荷",
    "answer": "ふか",
    "meaning": "burden, load (e.g. CPU time, electricity, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "産",
    "answer": "うぶ,さん",
    "meaning": "innocent, naive, unsophisticated, inexperienced, green, wet behind the ears, birth-, (giving) birth,"
  },
  {
    "question": "身震い",
    "answer": "みぶるい",
    "meaning": "shivering (with cold), trembling (with fear), shuddering"
  },
  {
    "question": "部署",
    "answer": "ぶしょ",
    "meaning": "one's post, one's station, department, bureau, section"
  },
  {
    "question": "心中",
    "answer": "しんじゅう,しんぢゅう,しんちゅう",
    "meaning": "double suicide, lovers' suicide, one's heart, the mind, inner feelings, inmost thoughts, true motive"
  },
  {
    "question": "刑",
    "answer": "けい",
    "meaning": "penalty, sentence, punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "感慨深い",
    "answer": "かんがいぶかい",
    "meaning": "deeply emotive, moving"
  },
  {
    "question": "落書き",
    "answer": "らくがき",
    "meaning": "scrawl, scribble, graffiti, doodle"
  },
  {
    "question": "本拠地",
    "answer": "ほんきょち",
    "meaning": "stronghold, inner citadel, base, headquarters"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け根",
    "answer": "つけね",
    "meaning": "root, joint, base, crotch"
  },
  {
    "question": "金銭",
    "answer": "きんせん",
    "meaning": "money, cash"
  },
  {
    "question": "所作",
    "answer": "しょさ,そさ",
    "meaning": "conduct, behaviour, movements, gesture, one's carriage, performance (on stage, etc.), dance, acting,"
  },
  {
    "question": "杞憂",
    "answer": "きゆう",
    "meaning": "needless fear, groundless apprehension, unfounded worry"
  },
  {
    "question": "校",
    "answer": "こう",
    "meaning": "school, proof (of a book, document, etc.), counter for proofs"
  },
  {
    "question": "真紅",
    "answer": "しんく",
    "meaning": "deep crimson"
  },
  {
    "question": "一色",
    "answer": "いっしょく,いっしき,ひといろ",
    "meaning": "one color, one colour, one article, monochrome, same tendency, everyone being caught up in the same"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁解",
    "answer": "べんかい",
    "meaning": "explanation (e.g. for one's actions), excuse, justification, defense, defence"
  },
  {
    "question": "人工",
    "answer": "じんこう",
    "meaning": "artificial, man-made, human work, human skill, artificiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "亀",
    "answer": "かめ",
    "meaning": "tortoise, turtle, heavy drinker, turtle crest, turtle mon"
  },
  {
    "question": "中国",
    "answer": "ちゅうごく,ちゅうこく",
    "meaning": "China, Chūgoku region of western Honshu (incl. Okayama, Hiroshima, Shimane, Tottori and Yamaguchi pr"
  },
  {
    "question": "分散",
    "answer": "ぶんさん",
    "meaning": "dispersion, breakup, scattering, decentralization, decentralisation, distribution, variance"
  },
  {
    "question": "文面",
    "answer": "ぶんめん",
    "meaning": "content of a letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "断末魔",
    "answer": "だんまつま",
    "meaning": "one's last moments, death throes, agony of death"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿泊",
    "answer": "しゅくはく",
    "meaning": "accommodation, lodging"
  },
  {
    "question": "中間",
    "answer": "ちゅうかん,ちゅうげん",
    "meaning": "middle, midway, halfway, centre, center, middle position, moderate position, neutral position, middl"
  },
  {
    "question": "辛抱",
    "answer": "しんぼう",
    "meaning": "patience, endurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "浸透",
    "answer": "しんとう",
    "meaning": "penetration (e.g. market), pervasion (e.g. thought, ideology), permeation, soaking, osmosis"
  },
  {
    "question": "該当",
    "answer": "がいとう",
    "meaning": "corresponding to, being applicable to, being relevant to, coming under, falling under, fulfilling (r"
  },
  {
    "question": "掠める",
    "answer": "かすめる",
    "meaning": "to steal, to rob, to snatch, to pocket, to plunder, to deceive, to trick, to cheat, to graze (in pas"
  },
  {
    "question": "無実",
    "answer": "むじつ",
    "meaning": "innocence, guiltlessness, false accusation, false charge, absence of the fact, insubstantiality, lac"
  },
  {
    "question": "実物",
    "answer": "じつぶつ,みもの",
    "meaning": "real thing, original, actual, ornamental plant used primarily for the visual effect of its fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "無関心",
    "answer": "むかんしん",
    "meaning": "apathetic, indifferent"
  },
  {
    "question": "偏る",
    "answer": "かたよる",
    "meaning": "to lean (to one side), to incline, to be unbalanced (e.g. diet), to be unduly weighted towards, to b"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇跡的",
    "answer": "きせきてき",
    "meaning": "miraculous"
  },
  {
    "question": "偏見",
    "answer": "へんけん",
    "meaning": "prejudice, bias, distorted view"
  },
  {
    "question": "業界",
    "answer": "ぎょうかい",
    "meaning": "business world, business circles, (the) industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "集結",
    "answer": "しゅうけつ",
    "meaning": "massing (of troops), gathering"
  },
  {
    "question": "合体",
    "answer": "がったい",
    "meaning": "union, coalescence, amalgamation, combination, alliance, annexation, incorporation, copulation, pene"
  },
  {
    "question": "注意深い",
    "answer": "ちゅういぶかい",
    "meaning": "attentive, cautious, careful, watchful"
  },
  {
    "question": "荷台",
    "answer": "にだい",
    "meaning": "(truck) load-carrying tray, (bicycle) luggage carrier, roof rack"
  },
  {
    "question": "二番目",
    "answer": "にばんめ",
    "meaning": "second (in a series)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾度も",
    "answer": "いくども",
    "meaning": "many times"
  },
  {
    "question": "煌めく",
    "answer": "きらめく",
    "meaning": "to glitter, to glisten, to sparkle, to twinkle, to glare, to gleam"
  },
  {
    "question": "収縮",
    "answer": "しゅうしゅく",
    "meaning": "deflation, contraction, shrinking, constriction"
  },
  {
    "question": "暖炉",
    "answer": "だんろ",
    "meaning": "fireplace, hearth, stove"
  },
  {
    "question": "任命",
    "answer": "にんめい",
    "meaning": "appointment, nomination, ordination, commission, designation"
  },
  {
    "question": "回想",
    "answer": "かいそう",
    "meaning": "recollection, retrospection, reflection, reminiscence"
  },
  {
    "question": "横暴",
    "answer": "おうぼう",
    "meaning": "violence, oppression, high-handedness, tyranny, despotism"
  },
  {
    "question": "形作る",
    "answer": "かたちづくる",
    "meaning": "to form, to shape, to make, to mold, to mould, to build up"
  },
  {
    "question": "和やか",
    "answer": "にこやか,なごやか",
    "meaning": "smiling, beaming, radiant, bright, cheerful, mild, calm, gentle, quiet, congenial, amicable, amiable"
  },
  {
    "question": "欄",
    "answer": "らん,おばしま",
    "meaning": "section (e.g. in a newspaper), column, page, field (in a form, web page, etc.), blank, handrail, rai"
  },
  {
    "question": "違法",
    "answer": "いほう",
    "meaning": "illegal, illicit, unlawful"
  },
  {
    "question": "念じる",
    "answer": "ねんじる",
    "meaning": "to wish (for), to pray (for), to hope (for), to pray silently, to recite (Buddha's name, sutras, etc"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱走",
    "answer": "だっそう",
    "meaning": "escape, flight, breakout, fleeing, desertion"
  },
  {
    "question": "沢",
    "answer": "さわ,たく",
    "meaning": "mountain stream, valley, dale, wetlands, swamp, marsh, blessing, grace, favour, favor, benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "機材",
    "answer": "きざい",
    "meaning": "machine parts, machinery, equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "当番",
    "answer": "とうばん",
    "meaning": "being on duty, person on duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛来",
    "answer": "ひらい",
    "meaning": "coming flying in (migratory birds, airborne sand, pollen, etc.), coming by airplane"
  },
  {
    "question": "後ろ盾",
    "answer": "うしろだて",
    "meaning": "backing, support, backer, supporter, patron, sponsor, shield that protects one's back"
  },
  {
    "question": "穿つ",
    "answer": "うがつ",
    "meaning": "to drill, to bore, to pierce, to pass through, to hit the mark, to get to the heart of (the matter),"
  },
  {
    "question": "客室",
    "answer": "きゃくしつ",
    "meaning": "guest room (at a hotel), guest cabin (on a boat), passenger cabin (on a plane), drawing room"
  },
  {
    "question": "登場人物",
    "answer": "とうじょうじんぶつ",
    "meaning": "character (in a play or novel), dramatis personae"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺るぐ",
    "answer": "ゆるぐ",
    "meaning": "to shake, to waver, to tremble"
  },
  {
    "question": "姉弟",
    "answer": "してい,きょうだい",
    "meaning": "older sister and younger brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "船長",
    "answer": "せんちょう,ふなおさ",
    "meaning": "ship's captain, skipper, length of a ship, boatman"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆け回る",
    "answer": "かけまわる",
    "meaning": "to run around, to bustle about"
  },
  {
    "question": "写す",
    "answer": "うつす",
    "meaning": "to transcribe, to duplicate, to reproduce, to imitate, to trace, to describe, to film, to picture, t"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い渡す",
    "answer": "いいわたす",
    "meaning": "to announce, to tell, to sentence, to order"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜かす",
    "answer": "ぬかす",
    "meaning": "to omit, to leave out, to skip, to overtake, to pass, to say, to speak"
  },
  {
    "question": "奪還",
    "answer": "だっかん",
    "meaning": "recovery, rescue, recapture"
  },
  {
    "question": "用途",
    "answer": "ようと",
    "meaning": "use, service, purpose"
  },
  {
    "question": "屈強",
    "answer": "くっきょう",
    "meaning": "robust, brawny, muscular, strong, sturdy"
  },
  {
    "question": "合わさる",
    "answer": "あわさる",
    "meaning": "to join, to be put together, to combine, to unite, to fit, to close (e.g. of a wound)"
  },
  {
    "question": "拙い",
    "answer": "つたない,まずい",
    "meaning": "poor-quality, shoddy, crude, unskillful, inexpert, maladroit, inept, foolish, clumsy, unlucky"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸見え",
    "answer": "まるみえ",
    "meaning": "full view, plain sight, completely visible"
  },
  {
    "question": "歴代",
    "answer": "れきだい",
    "meaning": "successive generations, successive emperors"
  },
  {
    "question": "綻ぶ",
    "answer": "ほころぶ",
    "meaning": "to begin to open, to come out, to smile broadly, to come apart at the seams (clothes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "長女",
    "answer": "ちょうじょ",
    "meaning": "eldest daughter, first-born daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "同類",
    "answer": "どうるい",
    "meaning": "the same kind, accomplice, partner"
  },
  {
    "question": "刺客",
    "answer": "しかく,しきゃく",
    "meaning": "assassin, to assassinate"
  },
  {
    "question": "損害",
    "answer": "そんがい",
    "meaning": "damage, injury, loss"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦法",
    "answer": "せんぽう",
    "meaning": "tactics, strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "癒やす",
    "answer": "いやす",
    "meaning": "to heal, to cure, to satisfy (e.g. hunger, thirst), to alleviate (e.g. sorrow, fatigue)"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠席",
    "answer": "けっせき",
    "meaning": "absence, non-attendance"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆効果",
    "answer": "ぎゃくこうか,ぎゃっこうか",
    "meaning": "opposite effect, adverse effect, backfiring"
  },
  {
    "question": "零",
    "answer": "れい,ゼロ",
    "meaning": "zero, nought, nil, nothing, zilch"
  },
  {
    "question": "合成",
    "answer": "ごうせい",
    "meaning": "composition, synthesis, composite, compound, synthetic, mixed, combined, (function) composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "作者",
    "answer": "さくしゃ",
    "meaning": "creator (of a work), author, writer, artist, composer, playwright, dramatist"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝そべる",
    "answer": "ねそべる",
    "meaning": "to sprawl, to lie sprawled, to stretch oneself out, to lie relaxed on one's side"
  },
  {
    "question": "見分ける",
    "answer": "みわける",
    "meaning": "to distinguish, to recognize, to recognise, to tell apart, to differentiate"
  },
  {
    "question": "割れ目",
    "answer": "われめ",
    "meaning": "chasm, interstice, crevice, crack, cleft, split, rift, fissure, vulva, slit, cunt, vagina, twat"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆",
    "answer": "ふで,ひつ",
    "meaning": "writing brush, paintbrush, pen, writing with a brush, drawing with a brush, penmanship, something dr"
  },
  {
    "question": "下心",
    "answer": "したごころ",
    "meaning": "secret intention, ulterior motive, kanji 'heart' radical at bottom"
  },
  {
    "question": "人見知り",
    "answer": "ひとみしり",
    "meaning": "shyness, fear of strangers, stranger anxiety"
  },
  {
    "question": "捌く",
    "answer": "さばく",
    "meaning": "to handle well, to handle deftly, to deal with, to manage, to settle, to sort, to process, to prepar"
  },
  {
    "question": "機動",
    "answer": "きどう",
    "meaning": "maneuver (usu. of military force), manoeuvre, mobile, nimble, agile, quick to respond"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣営",
    "answer": "じんえい",
    "meaning": "camp (supporters of a doctrine, party, etc.), faction (of a party), military camp, encampment, canto"
  },
  {
    "question": "著しい",
    "answer": "いちじるしい",
    "meaning": "striking, remarkable, considerable"
  },
  {
    "question": "京都",
    "answer": "きょうと",
    "meaning": "Kyoto (city, prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "凌駕",
    "answer": "りょうが",
    "meaning": "excelling, surpassing, outdoing"
  },
  {
    "question": "目覚め",
    "answer": "めざめ",
    "meaning": "waking"
  },
  {
    "question": "腫れる",
    "answer": "はれる",
    "meaning": "to swell (from inflammation), to become swollen"
  },
  {
    "question": "管理人",
    "answer": "かんりにん",
    "meaning": "administrator, janitor, manager, concierge, caretaker, superintendent, supervisor, custodian, execut"
  },
  {
    "question": "近しい",
    "answer": "ちかしい",
    "meaning": "intimate, close"
  },
  {
    "question": "両側",
    "answer": "りょうがわ,りょうそく",
    "meaning": "both sides"
  },
  {
    "question": "腕輪",
    "answer": "うでわ",
    "meaning": "bracelet, bangle"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬う",
    "answer": "うやまう",
    "meaning": "to show respect for, to revere, to honour, to honor, to worship, to hold in esteem"
  },
  {
    "question": "気迫",
    "answer": "きはく",
    "meaning": "spirit, soul, drive, vigor, vigour"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍事",
    "answer": "ぐんじ",
    "meaning": "military affairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "樽",
    "answer": "たる",
    "meaning": "cask, barrel"
  },
  {
    "question": "使役",
    "answer": "しえき",
    "meaning": "setting (someone) to work, employment, using, causative (verb, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "気を配る",
    "answer": "きをくばる",
    "meaning": "to pay attention, to be watchful"
  },
  {
    "question": "変人",
    "answer": "へんじん",
    "meaning": "eccentric, crank, oddball"
  },
  {
    "question": "注視",
    "answer": "ちゅうし",
    "meaning": "gazing steadily at, observing (a person) closely, maintain a watch over"
  },
  {
    "question": "貝",
    "answer": "かい,ばい",
    "meaning": "shellfish, seashell, shell, Japanese babylon (species of shelled mollusk, Babylonia japonica), Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "平日",
    "answer": "へいじつ,ひらび",
    "meaning": "weekday, ordinary days (i.e. non-holiday), kanji radical 73"
  },
  {
    "question": "反芻",
    "answer": "はんすう",
    "meaning": "rumination, regurgitation, chewing the cud, turning over in one's mind, thinking over something, pon"
  },
  {
    "question": "次男",
    "answer": "じなん",
    "meaning": "second son"
  },
  {
    "question": "坊ちゃん",
    "answer": "ぼっちゃん",
    "meaning": "son (of others), boy, young master, green young man from a well-to-do family, young man innocent of"
  },
  {
    "question": "美術",
    "answer": "びじゅつ",
    "meaning": "art, fine arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "大人気",
    "answer": "だいにんき,おとなげ",
    "meaning": "very popular, highly favoured, adultness, maturity"
  },
  {
    "question": "故障",
    "answer": "こしょう",
    "meaning": "breakdown, failure, fault, accident, out of order, damage, hurt, objection, protest"
  },
  {
    "question": "小突く",
    "answer": "こづく",
    "meaning": "to poke, to push"
  },
  {
    "question": "試し",
    "answer": "ためし",
    "meaning": "trial, test"
  },
  {
    "question": "道場",
    "answer": "どうじょう",
    "meaning": "dojo, hall used for martial arts training, manda (place of Buddhist practice or meditation, esp. the"
  },
  {
    "question": "咳",
    "answer": "せき,しわぶき",
    "meaning": "cough, coughing, tussis"
  },
  {
    "question": "躍る",
    "answer": "おどる",
    "meaning": "to jump up, to spring up, to leap, to move around, to bounce up and down, to pound (of one's heart,"
  },
  {
    "question": "芋",
    "answer": "いも",
    "meaning": "tuber, taro, potato, yam, yokel, bumpkin, dud, worthless thing"
  },
  {
    "question": "良き",
    "answer": "よき",
    "meaning": "goodness, good"
  },
  {
    "question": "段取り",
    "answer": "だんどり",
    "meaning": "programme, program, plans, arrangements"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝かす",
    "answer": "ねかす",
    "meaning": "to put to sleep, to lay (something) on its side"
  },
  {
    "question": "良し",
    "answer": "よし,えし",
    "meaning": "good, excellent, fine, nice, pleasant, agreeable"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦意",
    "answer": "せんい",
    "meaning": "fighting spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "感染",
    "answer": "かんせん",
    "meaning": "infection, contagion, becoming infected"
  },
  {
    "question": "芝生",
    "answer": "しばふ",
    "meaning": "lawn, grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "御用",
    "answer": "ごよう",
    "meaning": "(your) business, (your) concern, (your) need, (customer's) order, official business (of the governme"
  },
  {
    "question": "半径",
    "answer": "はんけい",
    "meaning": "radius"
  },
  {
    "question": "心身",
    "answer": "しんしん,しんじん",
    "meaning": "mind and body"
  },
  {
    "question": "着実",
    "answer": "ちゃくじつ",
    "meaning": "steady, sound, solid, reliable, trustworthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "神秘",
    "answer": "しんぴ",
    "meaning": "mystery, mysteriousness, secret"
  },
  {
    "question": "文官",
    "answer": "ぶんかん",
    "meaning": "civil official"
  },
  {
    "question": "事柄",
    "answer": "ことがら",
    "meaning": "matter, thing, affair, circumstance"
  },
  {
    "question": "倣う",
    "answer": "ならう",
    "meaning": "to imitate, to follow, to emulate"
  },
  {
    "question": "称賛",
    "answer": "しょうさん",
    "meaning": "praise, admiration, commendation, approbation"
  },
  {
    "question": "省く",
    "answer": "はぶく",
    "meaning": "to omit, to leave out, to exclude, to eliminate, to curtail, to save, to cut down, to economize, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "院長",
    "answer": "いんちょう",
    "meaning": "director"
  },
  {
    "question": "食い物",
    "answer": "くいもの",
    "meaning": "food, foodstuff, prey, victim"
  },
  {
    "question": "区域",
    "answer": "くいき",
    "meaning": "limits, boundary, domain, zone, sphere, territory, area (e.g. in programming languages)"
  },
  {
    "question": "階下",
    "answer": "かいか",
    "meaning": "lower floor, downstairs, bottom of the stairs, foot of the stairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "主要",
    "answer": "しゅよう",
    "meaning": "chief, main, principal, major"
  },
  {
    "question": "身軽",
    "answer": "みがる",
    "meaning": "agile, nimble, light (of foot), casual (clothing), light (e.g. luggage), carefree, with limited resp"
  },
  {
    "question": "芸",
    "answer": "げい",
    "meaning": "art, craft, accomplishment, artistic skill, technique, performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "流石は",
    "answer": "さすがは",
    "meaning": "as one would expect, just as you'd expect (from), just like (someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小石",
    "answer": "こいし",
    "meaning": "pebble"
  },
  {
    "question": "不完全",
    "answer": "ふかんぜん",
    "meaning": "imperfect, incomplete, faulty, defective"
  },
  {
    "question": "散らかる",
    "answer": "ちらかる",
    "meaning": "to be in disorder, to lie scattered around"
  },
  {
    "question": "決行",
    "answer": "けっこう",
    "meaning": "doing (with resolve), carrying out (e.g. a plan)"
  },
  {
    "question": "空港",
    "answer": "くうこう",
    "meaning": "airport"
  },
  {
    "question": "責務",
    "answer": "せきむ",
    "meaning": "duty, obligation"
  },
  {
    "question": "連発",
    "answer": "れんぱつ",
    "meaning": "running continuously, firing in rapid succession"
  },
  {
    "question": "股",
    "answer": "また,もも",
    "meaning": "crotch, crutch, groin, thigh, fork (in a tree, road, river, etc.), tines (of a fork), femoral"
  },
  {
    "question": "一回り",
    "answer": "ひとまわり",
    "meaning": "one turn, one round, (a) size, to go around, to make a circuit, to take a turn, twelve years, one cy"
  },
  {
    "question": "延びる",
    "answer": "のびる",
    "meaning": "to stretch, to extend, to lengthen, to grow (of hair, height, grass, etc.), to straighten out, to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "全うする",
    "answer": "まっとうする",
    "meaning": "to accomplish, to fulfill, to carry out"
  },
  {
    "question": "外道",
    "answer": "げどう",
    "meaning": "tirthika, non-Buddhist teachings, non-Buddhist, heterodoxy, unorthodoxy, heresy, heretic, demon, dev"
  },
  {
    "question": "光線",
    "answer": "こうせん",
    "meaning": "beam, light ray"
  },
  {
    "question": "一国",
    "answer": "いっこく",
    "meaning": "one country, whole country, hotheaded, stubborn"
  },
  {
    "question": "憶測",
    "answer": "おくそく",
    "meaning": "guess, speculation, supposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "所有者",
    "answer": "しょゆうしゃ",
    "meaning": "owner"
  },
  {
    "question": "直ちに",
    "answer": "ただちに",
    "meaning": "at once, immediately, right away, without delay, directly (face, lead to, etc.), automatically (mean"
  },
  {
    "question": "見殺し",
    "answer": "みごろし",
    "meaning": "letting (someone) die without helping"
  },
  {
    "question": "狩人",
    "answer": "かりゅうど,かりうど,かりびと",
    "meaning": "hunter"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶賛",
    "answer": "ぜっさん",
    "meaning": "high praise, great admiration, rave reviews"
  },
  {
    "question": "出動",
    "answer": "しゅつどう",
    "meaning": "sailing, marching, going out, dispatch"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻め",
    "answer": "せめ",
    "meaning": "attack, offence, offense, dominant partner of a homosexual relationship, a barrage of, a flood of"
  },
  {
    "question": "補正",
    "answer": "ほせい",
    "meaning": "correction, revision, compensation (e.g. to a pendulum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "着込む",
    "answer": "きこむ",
    "meaning": "to wear extra clothes, to dress formally"
  },
  {
    "question": "物心",
    "answer": "ものごころ,ぶっしん",
    "meaning": "awareness of things around one, ability to understand what is going on around oneself, judgment, jud"
  },
  {
    "question": "入",
    "answer": "いり,しお",
    "meaning": "entering, setting (of the Sun), containing, content, audience, income, beginning, counter for soakin"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻血",
    "answer": "はなぢ,はなじ",
    "meaning": "nosebleed"
  },
  {
    "question": "大昔",
    "answer": "おおむかし",
    "meaning": "great antiquity, old-fashioned, long ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "気丈",
    "answer": "きじょう",
    "meaning": "stout-hearted, firm, courageous, brave, tough"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒼白",
    "answer": "そうはく",
    "meaning": "pale, pallid"
  },
  {
    "question": "発音",
    "answer": "はつおん",
    "meaning": "pronunciation, production of sound"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸い付く",
    "answer": "すいつく",
    "meaning": "to stick to"
  },
  {
    "question": "存続",
    "answer": "そんぞく",
    "meaning": "duration, continuance, survival, persistence, retention"
  },
  {
    "question": "密度",
    "answer": "みつど",
    "meaning": "density"
  },
  {
    "question": "怯え",
    "answer": "おびえ",
    "meaning": "being startled, surprised or afraid, panic, trepidation"
  },
  {
    "question": "急遽",
    "answer": "きゅうきょ",
    "meaning": "hurriedly, in a hurry, in haste, sudden"
  },
  {
    "question": "表明",
    "answer": "ひょうめい",
    "meaning": "declaration, indication, representation, manifestation, demonstration, expression, announcement, ass"
  },
  {
    "question": "防壁",
    "answer": "ぼうへき",
    "meaning": "protective wall, bulwark"
  },
  {
    "question": "労力",
    "answer": "ろうりょく",
    "meaning": "labour, labor, effort, toil, trouble"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒼い",
    "answer": "あおい",
    "meaning": "blue, azure, green, pale, gray, grey, unripe, inexperienced"
  },
  {
    "question": "想像力",
    "answer": "そうぞうりょく",
    "meaning": "(power of) imagination"
  },
  {
    "question": "誰しも",
    "answer": "だれしも,たれしも",
    "meaning": "everyone, anyone, no one"
  },
  {
    "question": "反面",
    "answer": "はんめん",
    "meaning": "on the other hand, opposite side, reverse"
  },
  {
    "question": "裁き",
    "answer": "さばき",
    "meaning": "judgment, judgement, decision, verdict"
  },
  {
    "question": "近々",
    "answer": "ちかぢか,きんきん",
    "meaning": "soon, nearness, before long"
  },
  {
    "question": "生真面目",
    "answer": "きまじめ",
    "meaning": "overserious, deeply sincere, very earnest"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮る",
    "answer": "にる",
    "meaning": "to boil, to simmer, to stew, to seethe"
  },
  {
    "question": "適任",
    "answer": "てきにん",
    "meaning": "competent, suitable, qualified"
  },
  {
    "question": "追っ手",
    "answer": "おって",
    "meaning": "pursuer, pursuing party, posse"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗ばむ",
    "answer": "あせばむ",
    "meaning": "to be sweaty"
  },
  {
    "question": "河",
    "answer": "かわ,がわ,ホー",
    "meaning": "river, stream, River, the ... river, discarded tiles, discards"
  },
  {
    "question": "構図",
    "answer": "こうず",
    "meaning": "composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "境界",
    "answer": "きょうかい,けいかい",
    "meaning": "boundary, border, limit, bounds, frontier, land boundary, border (between properties)"
  },
  {
    "question": "発行",
    "answer": "はっこう",
    "meaning": "publication, issue (of journal, newspaper, etc.), issue (of banknotes, bonds, passport, etc.), raisi"
  },
  {
    "question": "対話",
    "answer": "たいわ",
    "meaning": "dialogue, discussion, conversation, interaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "暮れる",
    "answer": "くれる",
    "meaning": "to get dark, to grow dark, to end (of a day, year, season, etc.), to come to an end, to close, to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "筒",
    "answer": "つつ,ピン",
    "meaning": "pipe, tube, cylinder, gun barrel, gun, cannon, well lining, well curb, counter for dot tiles"
  },
  {
    "question": "器官",
    "answer": "きかん",
    "meaning": "organ (of body, plant, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "運び",
    "answer": "はこび",
    "meaning": "progress, pace, carriage, step, stage"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝言",
    "answer": "ねごと",
    "meaning": "sleep-talking, nonsense, gibberish"
  },
  {
    "question": "香ばしい",
    "answer": "こうばしい",
    "meaning": "aromatic (roasted beans, roasted tea, etc.), fragrant (e.g. burning wood), pleasant-smelling, savory"
  },
  {
    "question": "案じる",
    "answer": "あんじる",
    "meaning": "to be anxious or concerned about, to ponder (anxiously), to fear, to investigate, to consider, to pl"
  },
  {
    "question": "肢体",
    "answer": "したい",
    "meaning": "limbs, arms and legs, body"
  },
  {
    "question": "気高い",
    "answer": "けだかい",
    "meaning": "sublime, noble, high-minded"
  },
  {
    "question": "受話器",
    "answer": "じゅわき",
    "meaning": "(telephone) receiver"
  },
  {
    "question": "名物",
    "answer": "めいぶつ",
    "meaning": "famous product, special product, speciality, specialty"
  },
  {
    "question": "市内",
    "answer": "しない",
    "meaning": "(within a) city, local"
  },
  {
    "question": "面積",
    "answer": "めんせき",
    "meaning": "square measure, size (e.g. of land), area, surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "範疇",
    "answer": "はんちゅう",
    "meaning": "category"
  },
  {
    "question": "立候補",
    "answer": "りっこうほ",
    "meaning": "candidacy, standing as a candidate, bidding (to host an event, e.g. the Olympics)"
  },
  {
    "question": "然",
    "answer": "ぜん,さ,しか",
    "meaning": "-like, so, like that, in that way, as such, yeah, uh-huh"
  },
  {
    "question": "気がある",
    "answer": "きがある",
    "meaning": "to have an interest (in something), to feel inclined (toward doing something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "育む",
    "answer": "はぐくむ",
    "meaning": "to raise, to bring up, to rear, to cultivate, to foster, to nurture"
  },
  {
    "question": "使い切る",
    "answer": "つかいきる",
    "meaning": "to use up, to exhaust, to wear out"
  },
  {
    "question": "籠もる",
    "answer": "こもる",
    "meaning": "to shut oneself in (e.g. one's room), to be confined in, to seclude oneself, to hide away, to stay i"
  },
  {
    "question": "救援",
    "answer": "きゅうえん",
    "meaning": "relief, rescue"
  },
  {
    "question": "小隊",
    "answer": "しょうたい",
    "meaning": "platoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "反映",
    "answer": "はんえい",
    "meaning": "reflection (light, image, situation, attitude, etc.), reflecting, influence, application (e.g. of an"
  },
  {
    "question": "運搬",
    "answer": "うんぱん",
    "meaning": "transport, transportation, conveyance, carriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "作物",
    "answer": "さくぶつ,さくもつ",
    "meaning": "literary work, crop, crops, (agricultural) produce, farm products"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕虜",
    "answer": "ほりょ",
    "meaning": "prisoner (of war)"
  },
  {
    "question": "近接",
    "answer": "きんせつ",
    "meaning": "proximity, nearness, being nearby, being adjacent, approaching, drawing near, coming close"
  },
  {
    "question": "厳密",
    "answer": "げんみつ",
    "meaning": "strict, close, precise, scrupulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "神々しい",
    "answer": "こうごうしい",
    "meaning": "divine, sublime, solemn"
  },
  {
    "question": "投擲",
    "answer": "とうてき",
    "meaning": "throw, throwing, throwing event"
  },
  {
    "question": "発明",
    "answer": "はつめい",
    "meaning": "invention, intelligent, clever, smart, making sense (of something), understanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "救済",
    "answer": "きゅうさい,くさい,ぐさい",
    "meaning": "relief, aid, help, rescue, (religious) salvation, (Christian) grace, salvation (from suffering based"
  },
  {
    "question": "才",
    "answer": "さい",
    "meaning": "-years-old, ability, gift, talent, aptitude, genius, sai, traditional unit of volume, approx. 1.8 ml"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒板",
    "answer": "こくばん",
    "meaning": "blackboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "芽",
    "answer": "め",
    "meaning": "sprout, shoot, bud, germinal disk (in an egg)"
  },
  {
    "question": "酔い",
    "answer": "よい,えい",
    "meaning": "drunkenness, intoxication, motion sickness, travel sickness"
  },
  {
    "question": "忠誠",
    "answer": "ちゅうせい",
    "meaning": "loyalty, sincerity, allegiance, fidelity, integrity"
  },
  {
    "question": "直属",
    "answer": "ちょくぞく",
    "meaning": "direct control, direct supervision"
  },
  {
    "question": "肝",
    "answer": "きも",
    "meaning": "liver, innards, courage, spirit, pluck, guts, crux, essential point"
  },
  {
    "question": "手掛かり",
    "answer": "てがかり",
    "meaning": "clue, lead, key, trail, scent, track, handhold, hold"
  },
  {
    "question": "多々",
    "answer": "たた,ふさふさ",
    "meaning": "very much, very many, more and more, in tufts, tufty, bushy, thick, luxuriant"
  },
  {
    "question": "手料理",
    "answer": "てりょうり",
    "meaning": "home cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "超越",
    "answer": "ちょうえつ",
    "meaning": "transcendence, transcendency, transcendental, to transcend, to rise above"
  },
  {
    "question": "賜る",
    "answer": "たまわる",
    "meaning": "to be given, to be granted, to be honored with, to be honoured with, to give, to bestow, to confer,"
  },
  {
    "question": "性器",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "genitals"
  },
  {
    "question": "前者",
    "answer": "ぜんしゃ",
    "meaning": "the former"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄板",
    "answer": "てっぱん",
    "meaning": "iron plate, steel plane, sure thing, certain winner"
  },
  {
    "question": "老婆",
    "answer": "ろうば",
    "meaning": "old woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦がす",
    "answer": "こがす",
    "meaning": "to burn, to scorch, to singe, to char"
  },
  {
    "question": "翻す",
    "answer": "ひるがえす,こぼす",
    "meaning": "to turn over, to turn around, to change (one's mind), to reverse (one's decision), to take back (one"
  },
  {
    "question": "隻",
    "answer": "せき",
    "meaning": "counter for ships (large boats), counter for half of a pair (e.g. half of a folding screen), counter"
  },
  {
    "question": "代行",
    "answer": "だいこう",
    "meaning": "acting as agent, acting on (someone's) behalf, executing business for"
  },
  {
    "question": "剣幕",
    "answer": "けんまく",
    "meaning": "threatening attitude, menacing look, angry look"
  },
  {
    "question": "異議",
    "answer": "いぎ",
    "meaning": "objection, dissent, protest"
  },
  {
    "question": "式典",
    "answer": "しきてん",
    "meaning": "ceremony, rites"
  },
  {
    "question": "絹",
    "answer": "きぬ",
    "meaning": "silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "盛ん",
    "answer": "さかん",
    "meaning": "prosperous, flourishing, thriving, successful, popular, widespread, active, lively, energetic, vigor"
  },
  {
    "question": "伴侶",
    "answer": "はんりょ,ばんりょ",
    "meaning": "companion, partner, spouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗号",
    "answer": "あんごう",
    "meaning": "code, password, cipher"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑劣",
    "answer": "ひれつ",
    "meaning": "mean, contemptible, despicable, dirty, foul, cowardly, base"
  },
  {
    "question": "浴室",
    "answer": "よくしつ",
    "meaning": "bathroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "不毛",
    "answer": "ふもう",
    "meaning": "barren, sterile, infertile, unproductive (e.g. discussion), fruitless"
  },
  {
    "question": "無慈悲",
    "answer": "むじひ",
    "meaning": "merciless, ruthless, pitiless, unfeeling"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち回る",
    "answer": "たちまわる",
    "meaning": "to walk about, to walk around, to conduct oneself, to turn up, to brawl (in a play, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "効力",
    "answer": "こうりょく",
    "meaning": "effect, efficacy, validity, potency"
  },
  {
    "question": "異物",
    "answer": "いぶつ",
    "meaning": "foreign substance, foreign body, foreign contamination, foreign material, strange object, unusual ob"
  },
  {
    "question": "執念",
    "answer": "しゅうねん",
    "meaning": "tenacity, persistence, obsession, implacability"
  },
  {
    "question": "肩書き",
    "answer": "かたがき",
    "meaning": "title (e.g. Doctor, Professor, Lord), job title, position (in a company), degree, status, rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "同居",
    "answer": "どうきょ",
    "meaning": "coexistence, living together"
  },
  {
    "question": "社交",
    "answer": "しゃこう",
    "meaning": "social life, social intercourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "災難",
    "answer": "さいなん",
    "meaning": "calamity, misfortune, disaster"
  },
  {
    "question": "姉上",
    "answer": "あねうえ",
    "meaning": "older sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "間を置く",
    "answer": "まをおく,あいだをおく",
    "meaning": "to pause, to have a short intermission"
  },
  {
    "question": "感極まる",
    "answer": "かんきわまる",
    "meaning": "to be overcome with emotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "外交",
    "answer": "がいこう",
    "meaning": "diplomacy, selling (e.g. door-to-door), canvassing"
  },
  {
    "question": "深淵",
    "answer": "しんえん",
    "meaning": "abyss, ravine"
  },
  {
    "question": "外観",
    "answer": "がいかん",
    "meaning": "outward appearance, exterior appearance, outward show, looks"
  },
  {
    "question": "崇める",
    "answer": "あがめる",
    "meaning": "to revere, to respect, to worship"
  },
  {
    "question": "尽力",
    "answer": "じんりょく",
    "meaning": "efforts, exertion, endeavour, assistance, services"
  },
  {
    "question": "過保護",
    "answer": "かほご",
    "meaning": "overprotective, excessive care, overprotection, overprotectiveness"
  },
  {
    "question": "署名",
    "answer": "しょめい",
    "meaning": "signature"
  },
  {
    "question": "見越す",
    "answer": "みこす",
    "meaning": "to anticipate, to foresee"
  },
  {
    "question": "高熱",
    "answer": "こうねつ",
    "meaning": "high fever, pyro-"
  },
  {
    "question": "客間",
    "answer": "きゃくま",
    "meaning": "drawing room, parlor, parlour, guest room"
  },
  {
    "question": "谷間",
    "answer": "たにま,たにあい",
    "meaning": "valley, ravine, chasm, dell, cleavage (breasts), slum"
  },
  {
    "question": "採れる",
    "answer": "とれる",
    "meaning": "to be collected, to be gathered (e.g. mushrooms, etc.), to be harvested, to be mined, to be able to"
  },
  {
    "question": "身元",
    "answer": "みもと",
    "meaning": "person's identity, ID, past, background"
  },
  {
    "question": "空洞",
    "answer": "くうどう",
    "meaning": "cave, hollow, cavity"
  },
  {
    "question": "中学校",
    "answer": "ちゅうがっこう",
    "meaning": "junior high school, middle school, lower secondary school"
  },
  {
    "question": "編集",
    "answer": "へんしゅう",
    "meaning": "editing, compilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "見落とす",
    "answer": "みおとす",
    "meaning": "to overlook, to fail to notice, to miss (seeing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "元より",
    "answer": "もとより",
    "meaning": "from the beginning, from the first, all along, originally, of course"
  },
  {
    "question": "尻目",
    "answer": "しりめ",
    "meaning": "backward glance, sidelong glance, faceless ghost with an eye in its rump"
  },
  {
    "question": "体感",
    "answer": "たいかん",
    "meaning": "bodily sensation, sense, experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "大樹",
    "answer": "たいじゅ",
    "meaning": "large tree, big tree, huge tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "二の腕",
    "answer": "にのうで",
    "meaning": "upper arm"
  },
  {
    "question": "無機質",
    "answer": "むきしつ",
    "meaning": "inorganic matter, mineral matter, cold, inhuman, robotic"
  },
  {
    "question": "秘",
    "answer": "ひ",
    "meaning": "secret, mystery"
  },
  {
    "question": "心理",
    "answer": "しんり",
    "meaning": "state of mind, mentality, psychology"
  },
  {
    "question": "覆い隠す",
    "answer": "おおいかくす",
    "meaning": "to mask, to cover, to cloak, to hide, to conceal"
  },
  {
    "question": "散らかす",
    "answer": "ちらかす",
    "meaning": "to scatter around, to leave untidy"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘆き",
    "answer": "なげき",
    "meaning": "grief, lamentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "一時期",
    "answer": "いちじき",
    "meaning": "a period (of time)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷徹",
    "answer": "れいてつ",
    "meaning": "cool-headed, level-headed, hard-headed"
  },
  {
    "question": "常時",
    "answer": "じょうじ",
    "meaning": "usually, ordinarily, always, continuous, 24-hour (operation, care, etc.), constant, always on"
  },
  {
    "question": "縄張り",
    "answer": "なわばり",
    "meaning": "stretching a rope around, roping off, cordoning off, demarcation, one's turf, domain, territory, jur"
  },
  {
    "question": "半信半疑",
    "answer": "はんしんはんぎ",
    "meaning": "half in doubt, half-convinced, dubious, incredulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "侍",
    "answer": "さむらい,さぶらい",
    "meaning": "warrior (esp. of military retainers of daimyos in the Edo period), samurai, man in attendance (on a"
  },
  {
    "question": "保持",
    "answer": "ほじ",
    "meaning": "retention, maintenance, preservation"
  },
  {
    "question": "息遣い",
    "answer": "いきづかい",
    "meaning": "breathing, respiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "料",
    "answer": "りょう,はやし",
    "meaning": "fee, charge, rate, material, ornament, adornment, decoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "住居",
    "answer": "すまい,じゅうきょ",
    "meaning": "dwelling, house, residence, address, living, life"
  },
  {
    "question": "映える",
    "answer": "はえる,ばえる",
    "meaning": "to shine, to glow, to look attractive, to look nice, to be set off (by)"
  },
  {
    "question": "羞恥心",
    "answer": "しゅうちしん",
    "meaning": "shyness, shame"
  },
  {
    "question": "肩越し",
    "answer": "かたごし",
    "meaning": "over one's shoulder"
  },
  {
    "question": "就任",
    "answer": "しゅうにん",
    "meaning": "assumption (of office), taking up (a post), inauguration, installation"
  },
  {
    "question": "切れ味",
    "answer": "きれあじ",
    "meaning": "sharpness, cutting ability, quickness (of wit), incisiveness, technical proficiency, skill, peppines"
  },
  {
    "question": "溜め込む",
    "answer": "ためこむ",
    "meaning": "to save up, to stockpile, to stash away, to hoard, to amass, to salt away"
  },
  {
    "question": "義兄",
    "answer": "ぎけい,あに",
    "meaning": "brother-in-law (spouse's older brother or older sister's husband), older stepbrother"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽々しい",
    "answer": "かるがるしい,かろがろしい",
    "meaning": "rash, thoughtless, imprudent, careless, frivolous"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪事",
    "answer": "あくじ",
    "meaning": "evil deed, wrongdoing, crime, vice, misfortune, calamity"
  },
  {
    "question": "竿",
    "answer": "さお,かん",
    "meaning": "rod, pole, neck (of a shamisen, etc.), shamisen, beam (i.e. the crossbar of a balance), single line"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱入",
    "answer": "らんにゅう",
    "meaning": "trespassing, intrusion, to barge into, to burst into, to trespass"
  },
  {
    "question": "名門",
    "answer": "めいもん",
    "meaning": "noted family, noble family, prestigious school, organization, business, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "豪奢",
    "answer": "ごうしゃ",
    "meaning": "luxurious, magnificent, extravagant, sumptuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "凍える",
    "answer": "こごえる",
    "meaning": "to freeze (of one's body), to be frozen, to become numb (with cold), to be chilled"
  },
  {
    "question": "欺く",
    "answer": "あざむく",
    "meaning": "to deceive, to delude, to trick, to fool, to be as ... as ... (e.g. 'as bright as day', 'as beautifu"
  },
  {
    "question": "散乱",
    "answer": "さんらん",
    "meaning": "dispersion, scattering, spreading out, diffusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "読者",
    "answer": "どくしゃ",
    "meaning": "reader"
  },
  {
    "question": "拡張",
    "answer": "かくちょう",
    "meaning": "expansion, extension, enlargement, escape, ESC"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠回し",
    "answer": "とおまわし",
    "meaning": "indirect (roundabout) expression"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け",
    "answer": "つけ,づけ",
    "meaning": "bill, bill of sale, payment invoice, tab (for later payment), credit, contact move (in go), direct a"
  },
  {
    "question": "機構",
    "answer": "きこう",
    "meaning": "mechanism, organization, organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "所々",
    "answer": "ところどころ,しょしょ",
    "meaning": "here and there, some parts (of something), several places"
  },
  {
    "question": "別行動",
    "answer": "べつこうどう",
    "meaning": "doing something separately (from the group), going off on one's own"
  },
  {
    "question": "印刷",
    "answer": "いんさつ",
    "meaning": "printing"
  },
  {
    "question": "露店",
    "answer": "ろてん",
    "meaning": "street stall, stand, booth"
  },
  {
    "question": "改まる",
    "answer": "あらたまる",
    "meaning": "to be renewed, to change, to be improved, to be reformed, to be revised, to be corrected, to stand o"
  },
  {
    "question": "清掃",
    "answer": "せいそう",
    "meaning": "cleaning, clean-up, garbage collection, scavenging"
  },
  {
    "question": "来訪",
    "answer": "らいほう",
    "meaning": "visit, call"
  },
  {
    "question": "見回る",
    "answer": "みまわる",
    "meaning": "to make one's rounds, to patrol"
  },
  {
    "question": "甲冑",
    "answer": "かっちゅう",
    "meaning": "armor and helmet (armour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "求婚",
    "answer": "きゅうこん",
    "meaning": "marriage proposal, courtship"
  },
  {
    "question": "編",
    "answer": "へん",
    "meaning": "compilation (of a text), editing, volume (of a text), completed literary work"
  },
  {
    "question": "木陰",
    "answer": "こかげ",
    "meaning": "shade of tree, bower"
  },
  {
    "question": "梅",
    "answer": "うめ,むめ",
    "meaning": "Japanese apricot (Prunus mume), Japanese plum, ume, Chinese plum, lowest (of a three-tier ranking sy"
  },
  {
    "question": "請け負う",
    "answer": "うけおう",
    "meaning": "to contract, to undertake, to take over, to take responsibility for"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦燥",
    "answer": "しょうそう",
    "meaning": "impatience, uneasiness, irritation, fretfulness"
  },
  {
    "question": "阻害",
    "answer": "そがい",
    "meaning": "obstruction, inhibition"
  },
  {
    "question": "美味",
    "answer": "びみ",
    "meaning": "good flavor, good flavour, delicacy, dainty"
  },
  {
    "question": "区切る",
    "answer": "くぎる",
    "meaning": "to demarcate, to delimit, to divide (an area), to mark off, to cut off, to punctuate, to put an end"
  },
  {
    "question": "新品",
    "answer": "しんぴん",
    "meaning": "(brand-)new article"
  },
  {
    "question": "山積み",
    "answer": "やまづみ",
    "meaning": "huge mound, heap, pile"
  },
  {
    "question": "金属音",
    "answer": "きんぞくおん",
    "meaning": "metallic sound, metallic clank"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆音",
    "answer": "ばくおん",
    "meaning": "(sound of an) explosion or detonation, roar (of a machine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "知れ渡る",
    "answer": "しれわたる",
    "meaning": "to be well-known"
  },
  {
    "question": "七十",
    "answer": "しちじゅう,ななじゅう,ななそ",
    "meaning": "seventy, 70"
  },
  {
    "question": "減少",
    "answer": "げんしょう",
    "meaning": "decrease, reduction, decline"
  },
  {
    "question": "涙ぐむ",
    "answer": "なみだぐむ",
    "meaning": "to have tears in one's eyes, to be moved to tears"
  },
  {
    "question": "淫ら",
    "answer": "みだら",
    "meaning": "obscene, indecent, lewd, bawdy, loose, improper, dirty"
  },
  {
    "question": "郊外",
    "answer": "こうがい",
    "meaning": "suburb, residential area on the outskirt of a city, commuter belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "一目瞭然",
    "answer": "いちもくりょうぜん",
    "meaning": "apparent, obvious, very clear"
  },
  {
    "question": "失敬",
    "answer": "しっけい",
    "meaning": "rudeness, impoliteness, disrespect, impertinence, leaving, going (on one's way), saying goodbye, tak"
  },
  {
    "question": "表れる",
    "answer": "あらわれる",
    "meaning": "to appear, to come in sight, to become visible, to come out, to embody, to materialize, to materiali"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗り出す",
    "answer": "のりだす,のりいだす",
    "meaning": "to set out, to set sail, to embark on (a new venture), to set out (to achieve something), to begin t"
  },
  {
    "question": "酔っ払う",
    "answer": "よっぱらう",
    "meaning": "to get drunk"
  },
  {
    "question": "苛烈",
    "answer": "かれつ",
    "meaning": "severe, stern"
  },
  {
    "question": "未成年",
    "answer": "みせいねん",
    "meaning": "minor, not of age"
  },
  {
    "question": "合同",
    "answer": "ごうどう",
    "meaning": "combination, union, incorporation, amalgamation, fusion, congruence"
  },
  {
    "question": "日程",
    "answer": "にってい",
    "meaning": "schedule, program, programme, agenda"
  },
  {
    "question": "好き嫌い",
    "answer": "すききらい",
    "meaning": "likes and dislikes, pickiness (about food), choosiness, fussiness, tastes, preferences"
  },
  {
    "question": "格好良い",
    "answer": "かっこよい,かっこうよい",
    "meaning": "attractive, good-looking, stylish, cool, smooth, neat, with-it, groovy"
  },
  {
    "question": "怒気",
    "answer": "どき",
    "meaning": "anger, wrath"
  },
  {
    "question": "商",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "quotient, dealing, dealer, store, second degree (of the Japanese and Chinese pentatonic scale), Shan"
  },
  {
    "question": "装飾品",
    "answer": "そうしょくひん",
    "meaning": "ornament, decoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "主任",
    "answer": "しゅにん",
    "meaning": "person in charge, senior staff, manager, chief, head"
  },
  {
    "question": "開店",
    "answer": "かいてん",
    "meaning": "opening a new shop, opening a shop (for the day)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗り",
    "answer": "のり",
    "meaning": "riding, ride, spread (of paints), -seater (e.g. two-seater), (getting into the) mood, (entering into"
  },
  {
    "question": "山々",
    "answer": "やまやま",
    "meaning": "(many) mountains, very much (esp. wanting to do something one cannot), greatly, really"
  },
  {
    "question": "円形",
    "answer": "えんけい,まるがた",
    "meaning": "round shape, circle, circular form"
  },
  {
    "question": "商店",
    "answer": "しょうてん",
    "meaning": "shop, small store, business, firm"
  },
  {
    "question": "射出",
    "answer": "しゃしゅつ",
    "meaning": "shooting, firing, emitting, ejection, projection, injection, spouting, radiation"
  },
  {
    "question": "横たえる",
    "answer": "よこたえる",
    "meaning": "to lay down, to wear (a sword, etc.) at one's side"
  },
  {
    "question": "直径",
    "answer": "ちょっけい",
    "meaning": "diameter"
  },
  {
    "question": "矜持",
    "answer": "きょうじ,きんじ",
    "meaning": "pride, dignity, self-respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "退室",
    "answer": "たいしつ",
    "meaning": "exit from a room"
  },
  {
    "question": "当て",
    "answer": "あて",
    "meaning": "aim, object, purpose, end, expectations, prospects, hopes, something that can be relied upon, snack"
  },
  {
    "question": "負",
    "answer": "ふ,おい",
    "meaning": "negative, minus, wooden box carried on one's back to store items for a pilgrimage"
  },
  {
    "question": "畏まる",
    "answer": "かしこまる",
    "meaning": "to obey respectfully, to humble oneself, to sit straight (upright, respectfully, attentively)"
  },
  {
    "question": "発現",
    "answer": "はつげん",
    "meaning": "revelation, manifestation, appearance, expression (e.g. in molecular biology; protein expression or"
  },
  {
    "question": "昨年",
    "answer": "さくねん",
    "meaning": "last year"
  },
  {
    "question": "和む",
    "answer": "なごむ",
    "meaning": "to be softened, to calm down"
  },
  {
    "question": "峰",
    "answer": "みね",
    "meaning": "peak, summit, ridge, top, back of a blade"
  },
  {
    "question": "撤収",
    "answer": "てっしゅう",
    "meaning": "removal (e.g. of a building), dismantling (e.g. a tent), striking (e.g. a stage set), withdrawal (of"
  },
  {
    "question": "突っ走る",
    "answer": "つっぱしる",
    "meaning": "to run swiftly, to dash, to rush, to race"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼稚園",
    "answer": "ようちえん",
    "meaning": "kindergarten"
  },
  {
    "question": "野暮",
    "answer": "やぼ",
    "meaning": "boorish, unsophisticated, unrefined, uncouth, tasteless, insensitive, thoughtless, dumb"
  },
  {
    "question": "釘",
    "answer": "くぎ",
    "meaning": "nail, spike, tack, rivet, brad, (pachinko) pin"
  },
  {
    "question": "厭う",
    "answer": "いとう",
    "meaning": "to be loath to, to balk at (doing), to grudge (doing), to spare (oneself), to be weary of, to shun,"
  },
  {
    "question": "上級生",
    "answer": "じょうきゅうせい",
    "meaning": "student in a higher grade, upperclassman"
  },
  {
    "question": "曇り",
    "answer": "くもり",
    "meaning": "cloudiness, cloudy weather, fog (on a mirror, glasses, etc.), cloud (e.g. in marble), blur, mist, sh"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗り物",
    "answer": "のりもの",
    "meaning": "vehicle, conveyance, transport, ride (playground, fair, carnival), playground facility"
  },
  {
    "question": "奮い立つ",
    "answer": "ふるいたつ",
    "meaning": "to cheer up, to be encouraged (by), to be in high spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "大部分",
    "answer": "だいぶぶん",
    "meaning": "most part, greater part, majority"
  },
  {
    "question": "軌跡",
    "answer": "きせき",
    "meaning": "tire track, traces of a person or thing, path one has taken, locus"
  },
  {
    "question": "憤慨",
    "answer": "ふんがい",
    "meaning": "indignation, resentment"
  },
  {
    "question": "後ろ手",
    "answer": "うしろで",
    "meaning": "hands behind one's back, hands tied behind one's back, behind (e.g. someone), rear, back, appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤色",
    "answer": "あかいろ,せきしょく",
    "meaning": "red, red color (colour), red-colored, communism, the left"
  },
  {
    "question": "一線",
    "answer": "いっせん",
    "meaning": "line"
  },
  {
    "question": "胃袋",
    "answer": "いぶくろ",
    "meaning": "stomach, breadbasket, inner man, dietary needs"
  },
  {
    "question": "展示",
    "answer": "てんじ",
    "meaning": "exhibition, display"
  },
  {
    "question": "謳う",
    "answer": "うたう",
    "meaning": "to extol, to sing the praises of, to celebrate, to declare, to stipulate, to express, to state, to i"
  },
  {
    "question": "教え子",
    "answer": "おしえご",
    "meaning": "one's student (esp. a former one), one's pupil, one's disciple"
  },
  {
    "question": "金庫",
    "answer": "きんこ,かねぐら",
    "meaning": "safe, strongbox, cashbox, vault, strongroom, depository, cash office, treasury, provider of funds, t"
  },
  {
    "question": "新入り",
    "answer": "しんいり",
    "meaning": "newcomer, initiate, rookie"
  },
  {
    "question": "他ならぬ",
    "answer": "ほかならぬ",
    "meaning": "nothing but, none other than"
  },
  {
    "question": "風船",
    "answer": "ふうせん",
    "meaning": "balloon (esp. small, toy variety), airship, blimp"
  },
  {
    "question": "形容",
    "answer": "けいよう",
    "meaning": "describing, comparing, expressing figuratively, modifying, qualifying (e.g. an adjective qualifying"
  },
  {
    "question": "唸り声",
    "answer": "うなりごえ",
    "meaning": "groan, moan, roar, growl, buzz, hum (e.g. motor), whistling (e.g. wind, wires in the wind)"
  },
  {
    "question": "席を外す",
    "answer": "せきをはずす",
    "meaning": "to leave one's seat, to temporarily excuse oneself (from a meeting, etc.), to step outside, to be aw"
  },
  {
    "question": "配属",
    "answer": "はいぞく",
    "meaning": "assignment (of a person to somewhere), attachment (of a person to another unit, organization, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "吹雪",
    "answer": "ふぶき",
    "meaning": "snow storm, blizzard"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶命",
    "answer": "ぜつめい",
    "meaning": "end of life, death, annihilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "街灯",
    "answer": "がいとう",
    "meaning": "street light"
  },
  {
    "question": "甲板",
    "answer": "かんぱん,こうはん,こういた",
    "meaning": "deck (of a ship), top board (of a table, counter, etc.), surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "牢屋",
    "answer": "ろうや",
    "meaning": "jail, gaol, jailhouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "性的",
    "answer": "せいてき",
    "meaning": "(relating to) gender, sex, sexual"
  },
  {
    "question": "持参",
    "answer": "じさん",
    "meaning": "bringing, taking, carrying"
  },
  {
    "question": "診る",
    "answer": "みる",
    "meaning": "to examine (medically)"
  },
  {
    "question": "女装",
    "answer": "じょそう",
    "meaning": "female clothing, wearing female clothing, cross dressing (for a man)"
  },
  {
    "question": "観戦",
    "answer": "かんせん",
    "meaning": "watching a (sports) game, spectating, observing (military operations)"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠",
    "answer": "とお",
    "meaning": "distant"
  },
  {
    "question": "大佐",
    "answer": "たいさ,だいさ",
    "meaning": "colonel, (navy) captain"
  },
  {
    "question": "所業",
    "answer": "しょぎょう",
    "meaning": "deed, act"
  },
  {
    "question": "自国",
    "answer": "じこく",
    "meaning": "one's own country"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣告",
    "answer": "せんこく",
    "meaning": "sentence, verdict, pronouncement"
  },
  {
    "question": "好き放題",
    "answer": "すきほうだい",
    "meaning": "self-indulgence, doing as one pleases"
  },
  {
    "question": "品質",
    "answer": "ひんしつ",
    "meaning": "quality (of a product or a service)"
  },
  {
    "question": "代える",
    "answer": "かえる",
    "meaning": "to replace, to exchange, to interchange, to substitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "頻度",
    "answer": "ひんど",
    "meaning": "frequency (of occurrence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "名残",
    "answer": "なごり",
    "meaning": "remains, traces, vestiges, relics, (the sorrow of) parting, end"
  },
  {
    "question": "年代",
    "answer": "ねんだい",
    "meaning": "age, era, period, date"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥義",
    "answer": "おうぎ,おくぎ",
    "meaning": "secret techniques (of an art or skill), inner mysteries, essence, quintessence, heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "渋る",
    "answer": "しぶる",
    "meaning": "to hesitate, to hold back, to balk, to falter, to be reluctant, to be unwilling, to begrudge, to hav"
  },
  {
    "question": "使徒",
    "answer": "しと",
    "meaning": "apostle, disciple"
  },
  {
    "question": "安静",
    "answer": "あんせい",
    "meaning": "rest, quiet, repose"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸くなる",
    "answer": "まるくなる",
    "meaning": "to mellow (e.g. personality), to be rounded, to huddle, to cower, to be hunched, to curl up"
  },
  {
    "question": "無条件",
    "answer": "むじょうけん",
    "meaning": "unconditional"
  },
  {
    "question": "武",
    "answer": "ぶ",
    "meaning": "the art of war, martial arts, military arts, military force, the sword, valor, bravery, military off"
  },
  {
    "question": "心配性",
    "answer": "しんぱいしょう",
    "meaning": "nervous temperament, worrier's disposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "涼しい顔",
    "answer": "すずしいかお",
    "meaning": "nonchalant air, unruffled air"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏庭",
    "answer": "うらにわ",
    "meaning": "rear garden, back yard"
  },
  {
    "question": "失恋",
    "answer": "しつれん",
    "meaning": "disappointed love, broken heart, unrequited love, being lovelorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "眠たい",
    "answer": "ねむたい,ねぶたい",
    "meaning": "sleepy, drowsy"
  },
  {
    "question": "真っ当",
    "answer": "まっとう",
    "meaning": "proper, respectable, decent, honest"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠れ家",
    "answer": "かくれが,かくれや",
    "meaning": "hiding place, hideout, refuge, retreat, hideaway"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴露",
    "answer": "ばくろ",
    "meaning": "disclosure, exposure, revelation"
  },
  {
    "question": "侵食",
    "answer": "しんしょく",
    "meaning": "encroachment, erosion, corrosion"
  },
  {
    "question": "呪詛",
    "answer": "じゅそ,ずそ",
    "meaning": "curse, malediction, hex"
  },
  {
    "question": "生き生き",
    "answer": "いきいき",
    "meaning": "in a lively way, vividly, freshly, animatedly, actively, energetically"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り柄",
    "answer": "とりえ",
    "meaning": "worth, merit, value, good point, redeeming feature, saving grace"
  },
  {
    "question": "摂取",
    "answer": "せっしゅ",
    "meaning": "intake (e.g. of salt), ingestion, absorption (e.g. of new knowledge), adoption (e.g. of foreign cult"
  },
  {
    "question": "ドン引き",
    "answer": "ドンびき",
    "meaning": "being put off (by someone's words, behaviour, etc.), being taken aback, recoiling (in shock, disgust"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋭利",
    "answer": "えいり",
    "meaning": "sharp, keen, acute"
  },
  {
    "question": "算段",
    "answer": "さんだん",
    "meaning": "trying to think of a way (to), devising means (to), working out (how to do), contriving (to raise mo"
  },
  {
    "question": "手短",
    "answer": "てみじか",
    "meaning": "short, brief"
  },
  {
    "question": "坂道",
    "answer": "さかみち",
    "meaning": "hill road"
  },
  {
    "question": "電流",
    "answer": "でんりゅう",
    "meaning": "electric current"
  },
  {
    "question": "掛け声",
    "answer": "かけごえ",
    "meaning": "shout (of encouragement, etc.), yell (used to time or encourage activity, e.g. 'Heave ho!')"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き場",
    "answer": "ゆきば,いきば",
    "meaning": "place to go, destination"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦艦",
    "answer": "せんかん",
    "meaning": "battleship"
  },
  {
    "question": "団子",
    "answer": "だんご",
    "meaning": "dango, dumpling (usu. sweet), doughboy, ball-shaped object, something round, lump, group, bunch, kno"
  },
  {
    "question": "水泳",
    "answer": "すいえい",
    "meaning": "swimming"
  },
  {
    "question": "上部",
    "answer": "じょうぶ",
    "meaning": "top part, surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "毅然",
    "answer": "きぜん",
    "meaning": "resolute, firm, dauntless, undaunted"
  },
  {
    "question": "保有",
    "answer": "ほゆう",
    "meaning": "possession, retention, maintenance"
  },
  {
    "question": "火薬",
    "answer": "かやく",
    "meaning": "gunpowder, powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "節約",
    "answer": "せつやく",
    "meaning": "economising, saving"
  },
  {
    "question": "早める",
    "answer": "はやめる",
    "meaning": "to bring forward (e.g. by 3 hours), to advance, to hasten (e.g. one's death), to expedite, to precip"
  },
  {
    "question": "や否や",
    "answer": "やいなや",
    "meaning": "the minute (that) ..., no sooner than ..., whether or not"
  },
  {
    "question": "半月",
    "answer": "はんげつ,はんつき",
    "meaning": "half-moon, half a month, semicircle"
  },
  {
    "question": "朽ちる",
    "answer": "くちる",
    "meaning": "to rot, to decay, to die in obscurity, to be forgotten with time"
  },
  {
    "question": "枷",
    "answer": "かせ",
    "meaning": "shackles, fetters, irons, handcuffs, restraint, constraint, bonds (e.g. family), ties, binding relat"
  },
  {
    "question": "長々",
    "answer": "ながなが",
    "meaning": "long, drawn-out, very long"
  },
  {
    "question": "柔軟",
    "answer": "じゅうなん",
    "meaning": "flexible, lithe, soft, pliable"
  },
  {
    "question": "原",
    "answer": "げん,はら,ばら",
    "meaning": "original, primitive, primary, fundamental, raw, field, plain, prairie, tundra, moor, wilderness, suf"
  },
  {
    "question": "難儀",
    "answer": "なんぎ",
    "meaning": "affliction, hardship, difficulty, suffering, trouble"
  },
  {
    "question": "私室",
    "answer": "ししつ",
    "meaning": "private room"
  },
  {
    "question": "分裂",
    "answer": "ぶんれつ",
    "meaning": "split, division, break up"
  },
  {
    "question": "諸々",
    "answer": "もろもろ",
    "meaning": "all kinds of things, various things, large number of people"
  },
  {
    "question": "斜面",
    "answer": "しゃめん",
    "meaning": "slope, slanting surface, bevel"
  },
  {
    "question": "報い",
    "answer": "むくい",
    "meaning": "reward, recompense, return, punishment, retribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "学園祭",
    "answer": "がくえんさい",
    "meaning": "school festival, campus festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "替わる",
    "answer": "かわる",
    "meaning": "to succeed, to relieve, to replace, to take the place of, to substitute for, to take over for, to re"
  },
  {
    "question": "神秘的",
    "answer": "しんぴてき",
    "meaning": "mysterious, mystical"
  },
  {
    "question": "高額",
    "answer": "こうがく",
    "meaning": "large sum (money)"
  },
  {
    "question": "質素",
    "answer": "しっそ",
    "meaning": "simple, plain, modest, frugal, reserved"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝算",
    "answer": "しょうさん",
    "meaning": "prospects of victory, chances of success"
  },
  {
    "question": "心遣い",
    "answer": "こころづかい",
    "meaning": "consideration (for), thoughtfulness, solicitude, care, watchfulness, concern, sympathy"
  },
  {
    "question": "口止め",
    "answer": "くちどめ",
    "meaning": "forbidding to speak, muzzling (a person), bribing into secrecy, hush money"
  },
  {
    "question": "一位",
    "answer": "いちい",
    "meaning": "first place, first rank, unit's position, Japanese yew (Taxus cuspidata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大仰",
    "answer": "おおぎょう",
    "meaning": "exaggeration"
  },
  {
    "question": "来",
    "answer": "らい",
    "meaning": "next (year, spring, etc.), coming, since (last month, etc.), for (20 years, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "運動神経",
    "answer": "うんどうしんけい",
    "meaning": "motor nerves, reflexes"
  },
  {
    "question": "在庫",
    "answer": "ざいこ",
    "meaning": "inventory, stock, stockpile"
  },
  {
    "question": "修学旅行",
    "answer": "しゅうがくりょこう",
    "meaning": "excursion, field trip, school trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "善",
    "answer": "ぜん",
    "meaning": "good, goodness, right, virtue"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽減",
    "answer": "けいげん",
    "meaning": "abatement, reduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "濃密",
    "answer": "のうみつ",
    "meaning": "thick, dense, rich (as in taste or content), deep (colour), strong (smell, scent), crowded"
  },
  {
    "question": "膨張",
    "answer": "ぼうちょう",
    "meaning": "expansion, swelling, increase, growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "肌寒い",
    "answer": "はださむい,はだざむい",
    "meaning": "chilly, unpleasantly cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "悩ましい",
    "answer": "なやましい",
    "meaning": "seductive, carnal, enchanting, troubling, difficult, thorny, hard, anxious, uneasy"
  },
  {
    "question": "得策",
    "answer": "とくさく",
    "meaning": "profitable plan, good plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡き",
    "answer": "なき",
    "meaning": "the late, the deceased"
  },
  {
    "question": "爪先",
    "answer": "つまさき",
    "meaning": "toes, tips of the toes, toe of a shoe, sock, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "解読",
    "answer": "かいどく",
    "meaning": "deciphering, decoding"
  },
  {
    "question": "直面",
    "answer": "ちょくめん,ひためん",
    "meaning": "confrontation, to face, to confront, to encounter, performing without a mask (noh)"
  },
  {
    "question": "名字",
    "answer": "みょうじ",
    "meaning": "surname, family name"
  },
  {
    "question": "端っこ",
    "answer": "はしっこ,はじっこ",
    "meaning": "end, edge, tip"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝機",
    "answer": "しょうき",
    "meaning": "chance to win, opportunity to win, chance of victory"
  },
  {
    "question": "設立",
    "answer": "せつりつ",
    "meaning": "establishment, founding, incorporation (of a business)"
  },
  {
    "question": "災い",
    "answer": "わざわい",
    "meaning": "disaster, calamity, misfortune, trouble, woes"
  },
  {
    "question": "千切れる",
    "answer": "ちぎれる",
    "meaning": "to be torn off, to come off, to be torn to pieces, to be torn to shreds"
  },
  {
    "question": "波動",
    "answer": "はどう",
    "meaning": "wave motion, undulation, surge, wave"
  },
  {
    "question": "録音",
    "answer": "ろくおん",
    "meaning": "(audio) recording"
  },
  {
    "question": "天候",
    "answer": "てんこう",
    "meaning": "weather"
  },
  {
    "question": "十代",
    "answer": "じゅうだい",
    "meaning": "the teens (10-19), teenage, the tenth generation"
  },
  {
    "question": "視認",
    "answer": "しにん",
    "meaning": "visual confirmation, sighting"
  },
  {
    "question": "平原",
    "answer": "へいげん",
    "meaning": "plain, moor, prairie"
  },
  {
    "question": "流し",
    "answer": "ながし",
    "meaning": "sink (e.g. in a kitchen), cruising (e.g. taxi), strolling (entertainer, musician, etc.), washing are"
  },
  {
    "question": "共通点",
    "answer": "きょうつうてん",
    "meaning": "point in common, common feature"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱意",
    "answer": "ねつい",
    "meaning": "zeal, enthusiasm, ardor, ardour"
  },
  {
    "question": "説く",
    "answer": "とく",
    "meaning": "to explain, to advocate, to preach, to persuade"
  },
  {
    "question": "荷",
    "answer": "に,か",
    "meaning": "load, baggage, cargo, freight, goods, burden, responsibility, counter for loads (that can be carried"
  },
  {
    "question": "目掛ける",
    "answer": "めがける",
    "meaning": "to aim at"
  },
  {
    "question": "極秘",
    "answer": "ごくひ",
    "meaning": "absolute secrecy"
  },
  {
    "question": "固有",
    "answer": "こゆう",
    "meaning": "characteristic, traditional, peculiar, inherent, native, eigen-"
  },
  {
    "question": "恒例",
    "answer": "こうれい",
    "meaning": "established practice, custom"
  },
  {
    "question": "書庫",
    "answer": "しょこ",
    "meaning": "library, book storage, stack room, archive (file)"
  },
  {
    "question": "統合",
    "answer": "とうごう",
    "meaning": "integration, unification, unity, combination, consolidation, synthesis"
  },
  {
    "question": "親愛",
    "answer": "しんあい",
    "meaning": "deep affection, dear, beloved"
  },
  {
    "question": "請求",
    "answer": "せいきゅう",
    "meaning": "claim, demand, charge, application, request, billing (for a service)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大統領",
    "answer": "だいとうりょう",
    "meaning": "president (of a nation), big man, boss, buddy, mate"
  },
  {
    "question": "発散",
    "answer": "はっさん",
    "meaning": "emission, emanation, radiation, diffusion, dispersion, letting out (feelings), venting, divergence ("
  },
  {
    "question": "的中",
    "answer": "てきちゅう",
    "meaning": "hitting the target, striking home, proving to be right, coming true, being on the mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "染みる",
    "answer": "しみる,じみる",
    "meaning": "to pierce, to penetrate, to soak in, to permeate, to sting (wound or sensitive area, etc.), to smart"
  },
  {
    "question": "気が向く",
    "answer": "きがむく",
    "meaning": "to feel like, to feel inclined to do"
  },
  {
    "question": "教養",
    "answer": "きょうよう",
    "meaning": "cultivation, refinement, culture, education"
  },
  {
    "question": "感傷",
    "answer": "かんしょう",
    "meaning": "sentiment, sentimentality"
  },
  {
    "question": "停まる",
    "answer": "とまる,とどまる",
    "meaning": "to stop (moving), to come to a stop, to stop (doing, working, being supplied), to come to a halt, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "照準",
    "answer": "しょうじゅん",
    "meaning": "sight (e.g. of a gun), aim, alignment"
  },
  {
    "question": "束縛",
    "answer": "そくばく",
    "meaning": "restraint, restriction, fetters, yoke, shackles, binding, confinement with rope"
  },
  {
    "question": "も一つ",
    "answer": "もひとつ",
    "meaning": "furthermore, adding to the above-mentioned, not quite, not very good, lacking"
  },
  {
    "question": "概ね",
    "answer": "おおむね",
    "meaning": "in general, generally, mostly, roughly, largely, mainly, on the whole, by and large, gist, point, ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "電子",
    "answer": "でんし",
    "meaning": "electron, electronic"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘んじる",
    "answer": "あまんじる",
    "meaning": "to content oneself with, to be resigned to (one's fate), to be contented (satisfied) with (one's lot"
  },
  {
    "question": "名刺",
    "answer": "めいし",
    "meaning": "business card"
  },
  {
    "question": "典型的",
    "answer": "てんけいてき",
    "meaning": "typical, representative, archetypal, quintessential, stereotypical, model"
  },
  {
    "question": "不敬",
    "answer": "ふけい",
    "meaning": "disrespect, irreverence, impiety, blasphemy, profanity"
  },
  {
    "question": "路上",
    "answer": "ろじょう",
    "meaning": "on the road, on the street, in the street, on the way"
  },
  {
    "question": "極み",
    "answer": "きわみ",
    "meaning": "height, acme, extremity, peak, end, limit"
  },
  {
    "question": "次いで",
    "answer": "ついで",
    "meaning": "next, secondly, subsequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "評する",
    "answer": "ひょうする",
    "meaning": "to evaluate, to appraise, to comment on"
  },
  {
    "question": "目隠し",
    "answer": "めかくし",
    "meaning": "something used to cover the eyes, blindfold, blinder, blinker, eye bandage, concealing one's home su"
  },
  {
    "question": "異能",
    "answer": "いのう",
    "meaning": "unusual power, superpower, ability beyond that of humans"
  },
  {
    "question": "貯金",
    "answer": "ちょきん",
    "meaning": "putting money aside, savings, deposit (e.g. in a bank), accumulated surplus of wins, wins in the ban"
  },
  {
    "question": "手強い",
    "answer": "てごわい,てづよい",
    "meaning": "difficult, tough, formidable, redoubtable, stubborn, strong, resolute, firm, strict"
  },
  {
    "question": "味わい",
    "answer": "あじわい",
    "meaning": "flavour, flavor, taste, charm, appeal, interest, meaning, significance"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄付",
    "answer": "きふ",
    "meaning": "contribution, donation"
  },
  {
    "question": "私物",
    "answer": "しぶつ",
    "meaning": "private property, personal belongings, personal effects"
  },
  {
    "question": "浸す",
    "answer": "ひたす",
    "meaning": "to soak, to dip, to steep, to immerse, to moisten, to wet"
  },
  {
    "question": "呪術",
    "answer": "じゅじゅつ",
    "meaning": "magic, sorcery, incantation"
  },
  {
    "question": "気に病む",
    "answer": "きにやむ",
    "meaning": "to worry, to fret (over something), to be worried, to be anxious"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺るがす",
    "answer": "ゆるがす",
    "meaning": "to shake, to swing, to sway, to shock"
  },
  {
    "question": "主君",
    "answer": "しゅくん",
    "meaning": "lord, master"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳を塞ぐ",
    "answer": "みみをふさぐ",
    "meaning": "to stop (plug) one's ears"
  },
  {
    "question": "多忙",
    "answer": "たぼう",
    "meaning": "being very busy, busyness"
  },
  {
    "question": "性癖",
    "answer": "せいへき",
    "meaning": "disposition, inclination, characteristic, idiosyncrasy, propensity, sexual disposition, fetish"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉛",
    "answer": "なまり",
    "meaning": "lead (Pb)"
  },
  {
    "question": "涎",
    "answer": "よだれ",
    "meaning": "drool"
  },
  {
    "question": "着弾",
    "answer": "ちゃくだん",
    "meaning": "impact (of a projectile)"
  },
  {
    "question": "儲ける",
    "answer": "もうける",
    "meaning": "to profit, to get, to earn, to gain, to have (bear, beget) a child, to have a stroke of luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "目障り",
    "answer": "めざわり",
    "meaning": "eyesore, unpleasant sight, obstructing a view"
  },
  {
    "question": "資源",
    "answer": "しげん",
    "meaning": "resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "薙ぎ払う",
    "answer": "なぎはらう",
    "meaning": "to mow down"
  },
  {
    "question": "葬式",
    "answer": "そうしき",
    "meaning": "funeral"
  },
  {
    "question": "結成",
    "answer": "けっせい",
    "meaning": "formation, combination"
  },
  {
    "question": "砲弾",
    "answer": "ほうだん",
    "meaning": "shell, cannonball"
  },
  {
    "question": "開拓",
    "answer": "かいたく",
    "meaning": "reclamation (e.g. wasteland), cultivation, development, pioneering, opening up (e.g. new market), br"
  },
  {
    "question": "独断",
    "answer": "どくだん",
    "meaning": "one's own judgement (judgment), decision made without consulting others, arbitrary decision, dogmati"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄り",
    "answer": "より",
    "meaning": "pushing back one's opponent while locked in close quarters, having a tendency towards, being close t"
  },
  {
    "question": "実質的",
    "answer": "じっしつてき",
    "meaning": "substantial, real (as opposed to nominal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "縁談",
    "answer": "えんだん",
    "meaning": "marriage proposal, marriage talks"
  },
  {
    "question": "喉が渇く",
    "answer": "のどがかわく",
    "meaning": "to be thirsty"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り開く",
    "answer": "きりひらく",
    "meaning": "to clear (land), to open up, to cut through"
  },
  {
    "question": "健康的",
    "answer": "けんこうてき",
    "meaning": "hygienic, healthy, healthful, sanitary"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔いる",
    "answer": "くいる",
    "meaning": "to regret"
  },
  {
    "question": "発光",
    "answer": "はっこう",
    "meaning": "emission (of light), radiation (of light), luminescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "正義感",
    "answer": "せいぎかん",
    "meaning": "sense of justice"
  },
  {
    "question": "五感",
    "answer": "ごかん",
    "meaning": "the five senses"
  },
  {
    "question": "損失",
    "answer": "そんしつ",
    "meaning": "loss (of assets, profit, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑賞",
    "answer": "かんしょう",
    "meaning": "appreciation (of art, music, poetry, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "魔界",
    "answer": "まかい",
    "meaning": "world of spirits, hell"
  },
  {
    "question": "天空",
    "answer": "てんくう",
    "meaning": "sky, air, ether, firmament, the heavens"
  },
  {
    "question": "御免",
    "answer": "ごめん",
    "meaning": "I'm sorry, my apologies, excuse me, pardon me, may I come in?, permission, leave, license, dismissal"
  },
  {
    "question": "続々",
    "answer": "ぞくぞく",
    "meaning": "successively, one after another"
  },
  {
    "question": "翻訳",
    "answer": "ほんやく",
    "meaning": "translation, deciphering, decoding"
  },
  {
    "question": "例える",
    "answer": "たとえる",
    "meaning": "to compare (something) to, to liken, to speak figuratively, to use a simile, to use a metaphor"
  },
  {
    "question": "壮大",
    "answer": "そうだい",
    "meaning": "magnificent, grand, majestic, splendid"
  },
  {
    "question": "一つ目",
    "answer": "ひとつめ",
    "meaning": "one-eyed, first (in a series), initial"
  },
  {
    "question": "聴覚",
    "answer": "ちょうかく",
    "meaning": "the sense of hearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "共同",
    "answer": "きょうどう",
    "meaning": "doing together (as equals), sharing, common (land, etc.), joint (statement, etc.), cooperation, co-o"
  },
  {
    "question": "色彩",
    "answer": "しきさい",
    "meaning": "colour, color, hue, tints"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷鳴",
    "answer": "らいめい",
    "meaning": "thunder, thunderclap, crash of thunder"
  },
  {
    "question": "物好き",
    "answer": "ものずき",
    "meaning": "(idle) curiosity, fancifulness, whimsy, (having) strange tastes"
  },
  {
    "question": "面倒臭い",
    "answer": "めんどくさい,めんどうくさい",
    "meaning": "bothersome, tiresome, bother to do"
  },
  {
    "question": "保障",
    "answer": "ほしょう",
    "meaning": "guarantee, security, assurance, pledge, warranty"
  },
  {
    "question": "成就",
    "answer": "じょうじゅ",
    "meaning": "fulfillment, fulfilment, realization, realisation, completion"
  },
  {
    "question": "心得",
    "answer": "こころえ",
    "meaning": "knowledge, understanding, rules, regulations, guideline, directions, deputy, acting"
  },
  {
    "question": "催促",
    "answer": "さいそく",
    "meaning": "pressing, urging, demanding, demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "末路",
    "answer": "まつろ,ばつろ",
    "meaning": "last days, the end, one's fate"
  },
  {
    "question": "木材",
    "answer": "もくざい",
    "meaning": "lumber, timber, wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "即ち",
    "answer": "すなわち",
    "meaning": "that is, namely, i.e."
  },
  {
    "question": "資産",
    "answer": "しさん",
    "meaning": "property, fortune, means, assets"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗客",
    "answer": "じょうきゃく,じょうかく",
    "meaning": "passenger"
  },
  {
    "question": "小細工",
    "answer": "こざいく",
    "meaning": "intricate workmanship, delicate handiwork, cheap trick, petty trick, obvious stratagem"
  },
  {
    "question": "近辺",
    "answer": "きんぺん",
    "meaning": "neighbourhood, neighborhood, vicinity"
  },
  {
    "question": "稼働",
    "answer": "かどう",
    "meaning": "operation (of machine), operating, running, working"
  },
  {
    "question": "眺め",
    "answer": "ながめ",
    "meaning": "scene, view, prospect, outlook"
  },
  {
    "question": "善良",
    "answer": "ぜんりょう",
    "meaning": "goodness, excellence, virtue"
  },
  {
    "question": "発砲",
    "answer": "はっぽう",
    "meaning": "firing, discharge of gun"
  },
  {
    "question": "紛らわす",
    "answer": "まぎらわす",
    "meaning": "to divert, to distract"
  },
  {
    "question": "温存",
    "answer": "おんぞん",
    "meaning": "preservation, retainment, keeping"
  },
  {
    "question": "上官",
    "answer": "じょうかん",
    "meaning": "superior officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "野心",
    "answer": "やしん",
    "meaning": "ambition, aspiration, sinister designs, treachery"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱",
    "answer": "あけ,あか,しゅ",
    "meaning": "scarlet, red, crimson, red-containing colour (e.g. brown, pink, orange), Red (i.e. communist), red l"
  },
  {
    "question": "突起",
    "answer": "とっき",
    "meaning": "protuberance, projection, prominence, bump, boss, process, apophysis"
  },
  {
    "question": "目を引く",
    "answer": "めをひく",
    "meaning": "to attract notice, to catch the eye, to stand out"
  },
  {
    "question": "意気揚々",
    "answer": "いきようよう",
    "meaning": "triumphant, exultant, in high and proud spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "走り",
    "answer": "はしり",
    "meaning": "running, gliding, first (harvest) of the season, beginning, start, kitchen sink"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗示",
    "answer": "あんじ",
    "meaning": "hint, suggestion"
  },
  {
    "question": "腐敗",
    "answer": "ふはい",
    "meaning": "decomposition, putrefaction, putrescence, spoilage, corruption, degeneracy, decay, depravity"
  },
  {
    "question": "気質",
    "answer": "きしつ,かたぎ",
    "meaning": "disposition, temperament, nature, mentality, spirit, character, trait, turn of mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "日間",
    "answer": "ひあい,にっかん",
    "meaning": "number of days, period of days, daily interest rate, daytime, during the day"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠伸",
    "answer": "あくび,けんしん",
    "meaning": "yawn, yawning"
  },
  {
    "question": "通行人",
    "answer": "つうこうにん",
    "meaning": "passerby, pedestrian, foot passenger"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝令",
    "answer": "でんれい",
    "meaning": "delivering an order, dispatch of an order, messenger, orderly, runner"
  },
  {
    "question": "寛大",
    "answer": "かんだい",
    "meaning": "tolerant, generous, lenient, broad-minded, magnanimous"
  },
  {
    "question": "武人",
    "answer": "ぶじん",
    "meaning": "military man"
  },
  {
    "question": "湛える",
    "answer": "たたえる",
    "meaning": "to fill (with), to be filled with, to express (an emotion), to project (sadness, joy, etc.), to wear"
  },
  {
    "question": "大手",
    "answer": "おおて,おおで",
    "meaning": "major company, big company, front castle gate, force attacking the front of a castle, full length of"
  },
  {
    "question": "実態",
    "answer": "じったい",
    "meaning": "true state, actual condition, reality"
  },
  {
    "question": "順",
    "answer": "じゅん,ずん",
    "meaning": "order, turn, sorting, obedient, docile, submissive, meek"
  },
  {
    "question": "腕時計",
    "answer": "うでどけい",
    "meaning": "wristwatch, watch"
  },
  {
    "question": "会計",
    "answer": "かいけい",
    "meaning": "accounting, finance, account, reckoning, bill (at a restaurant), check, accountant, treasurer, payma"
  },
  {
    "question": "重々",
    "answer": "じゅうじゅう",
    "meaning": "repeatedly, over and over again, fully (e.g. understand), very much, very well, exceedingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "慈しむ",
    "answer": "いつくしむ",
    "meaning": "to love (someone weaker than oneself), to be affectionate towards, to treat with tender loving care"
  },
  {
    "question": "危",
    "answer": "き",
    "meaning": "danger, Chinese 'rooftop' constellation (one of the 28 mansions)"
  },
  {
    "question": "還る",
    "answer": "かえる",
    "meaning": "to return, to come home, to go home, to go back, to leave, to get home, to get to home plate"
  },
  {
    "question": "学食",
    "answer": "がくしょく",
    "meaning": "school cafeteria"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗い流す",
    "answer": "あらいながす",
    "meaning": "to wash away, to rinse off"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉛筆",
    "answer": "えんぴつ",
    "meaning": "pencil"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦",
    "answer": "く",
    "meaning": "pain, anguish, suffering, distress, anxiety, worry, trouble, difficulty, hardship, duhkha (suffering"
  },
  {
    "question": "大好物",
    "answer": "だいこうぶつ",
    "meaning": "(one's) favourite food, (one's) favorite food"
  },
  {
    "question": "真珠",
    "answer": "しんじゅ",
    "meaning": "pearl"
  },
  {
    "question": "挙動",
    "answer": "きょどう",
    "meaning": "conduct, behavior, behaviour"
  },
  {
    "question": "同一",
    "answer": "どういつ",
    "meaning": "identical, same, one and the same, equal, fair, equal treatment, without discrimination"
  },
  {
    "question": "図々しい",
    "answer": "ずうずうしい",
    "meaning": "impudent, shameless, brazen, forward, audacious, cheeky"
  },
  {
    "question": "失神",
    "answer": "しっしん",
    "meaning": "faint, trance, swoon, stupefaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "待ち望む",
    "answer": "まちのぞむ",
    "meaning": "to wait eagerly for, to look forward to"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し相手",
    "answer": "はなしあいて",
    "meaning": "person with whom to speak, someone to talk to, companion, advisor, adviser"
  },
  {
    "question": "切実",
    "answer": "せつじつ",
    "meaning": "earnest, sincere, acute, keen, fervent, pressing, urgent, serious, severe, pertinent, appropriate"
  },
  {
    "question": "見切る",
    "answer": "みきる",
    "meaning": "to see everything, to see all, to abandon, to give up, to sell at a loss, to sell off"
  },
  {
    "question": "八十",
    "answer": "はちじゅう,やそ",
    "meaning": "eighty, 80"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿呆",
    "answer": "あほ,あほう",
    "meaning": "fool, idiot, simpleton"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨折",
    "answer": "こっせつ",
    "meaning": "bone fracture"
  },
  {
    "question": "破損",
    "answer": "はそん",
    "meaning": "damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "刻",
    "answer": "きざ,こく,とき",
    "meaning": "scratch, period of time (usu. a period of approx. two hours corresponding to one of the signs of the"
  },
  {
    "question": "税金",
    "answer": "ぜいきん",
    "meaning": "tax, duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "栄える",
    "answer": "さかえる,はえる,ばえる",
    "meaning": "to prosper, to flourish, to shine, to glow, to look attractive, to look nice, to be set off (by)"
  },
  {
    "question": "介す",
    "answer": "かいす",
    "meaning": "to use as an intermediary, to mediate, to assist, to worry, to mind, to care"
  },
  {
    "question": "参謀",
    "answer": "さんぼう",
    "meaning": "staff officer, military staff, adviser, counselor, counsellor"
  },
  {
    "question": "要員",
    "answer": "よういん",
    "meaning": "(necessary) personnel, required person"
  },
  {
    "question": "発つ",
    "answer": "たつ",
    "meaning": "to depart (on a plane, train, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "支給",
    "answer": "しきゅう",
    "meaning": "provision, supply, payment, allowance, grant"
  },
  {
    "question": "台風",
    "answer": "たいふう",
    "meaning": "typhoon, hurricane"
  },
  {
    "question": "診断",
    "answer": "しんだん",
    "meaning": "diagnosis, medical examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "食感",
    "answer": "しょっかん",
    "meaning": "food texture, mouthfeel"
  },
  {
    "question": "完治",
    "answer": "かんち,かんじ",
    "meaning": "complete recovery"
  },
  {
    "question": "自立",
    "answer": "じりつ",
    "meaning": "independence, self-reliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮座",
    "answer": "ちんざ",
    "meaning": "enshrinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "彫る",
    "answer": "ほる",
    "meaning": "to carve, to engrave, to sculpt, to chisel, to tattoo"
  },
  {
    "question": "探検",
    "answer": "たんけん",
    "meaning": "exploration, expedition"
  },
  {
    "question": "全世界",
    "answer": "ぜんせかい",
    "meaning": "the whole world"
  },
  {
    "question": "至高",
    "answer": "しこう",
    "meaning": "supreme, supremacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "混雑",
    "answer": "こんざつ",
    "meaning": "congestion, crush, crowding, jam, confusion, disorder"
  },
  {
    "question": "器具",
    "answer": "きぐ",
    "meaning": "utensil, implement, tool, instrument, appliance, apparatus"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍服",
    "answer": "ぐんぷく",
    "meaning": "military uniform"
  },
  {
    "question": "根源",
    "answer": "こんげん",
    "meaning": "root, source, origin, foundation, base, principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣かす",
    "answer": "なかす",
    "meaning": "to make someone cry, to move someone to tears, to grieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "騒々しい",
    "answer": "そうぞうしい",
    "meaning": "noisy, loud, boisterous, clamorous, raucous, turbulent, unsettled, restless"
  },
  {
    "question": "打倒",
    "answer": "だとう",
    "meaning": "knockdown (e.g. in boxing), overthrow, defeat"
  },
  {
    "question": "罵声",
    "answer": "ばせい",
    "meaning": "shout of abuse, jeers, boos"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚痴る",
    "answer": "ぐちる",
    "meaning": "to grumble, to gripe, to complain"
  },
  {
    "question": "火種",
    "answer": "ひだね",
    "meaning": "live coals (for firelighting), cause (of disturbance, conflict, etc.), trigger"
  },
  {
    "question": "優位",
    "answer": "ゆうい",
    "meaning": "predominance, superiority, ascendancy, advantage, supremacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦らす",
    "answer": "じらす",
    "meaning": "to tease, to irritate, to tantalize, to keep (someone) in suspense"
  },
  {
    "question": "扇",
    "answer": "おうぎ,おおぎ",
    "meaning": "folding fan"
  },
  {
    "question": "課す",
    "answer": "かす",
    "meaning": "to levy, to charge, to assess, to impose, to assign"
  },
  {
    "question": "奔流",
    "answer": "ほんりゅう",
    "meaning": "torrent, rapid stream, violently rushing stream"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇怪",
    "answer": "きかい,きっかい",
    "meaning": "strange, wonderful, weird, outrageous, mysterious"
  },
  {
    "question": "水路",
    "answer": "すいろ",
    "meaning": "waterway, canal, channel, watercourse, aqueduct, swimming pool lane"
  },
  {
    "question": "付き従う",
    "answer": "つきしたがう",
    "meaning": "to follow, to accompany, to cleave to, to join up with, to obey implicitly, to flatter"
  },
  {
    "question": "上げ",
    "answer": "あげ",
    "meaning": "tuck (e.g. in a dress), rise (e.g. in price)"
  },
  {
    "question": "加勢",
    "answer": "かせい",
    "meaning": "assistance, backing, reinforcements"
  },
  {
    "question": "九十",
    "answer": "きゅうじゅう,くじゅう",
    "meaning": "ninety, 90"
  },
  {
    "question": "進み出る",
    "answer": "すすみでる",
    "meaning": "to step forward, to volunteer"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち話",
    "answer": "たちばなし",
    "meaning": "talking while standing, standing around talking"
  },
  {
    "question": "長老",
    "answer": "ちょうろう",
    "meaning": "elder, senior, senior monk, dean, presbyter, patriarch"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔い",
    "answer": "くい",
    "meaning": "regret, repentance"
  },
  {
    "question": "無愛想",
    "answer": "ぶあいそう",
    "meaning": "unsociable, unfriendly, blunt, surly, curt, cold, brusque"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴力的",
    "answer": "ぼうりょくてき",
    "meaning": "violent"
  },
  {
    "question": "中にも",
    "answer": "なかにも",
    "meaning": "among (other things), especially, particularly, inter alia, above all (else), at the same time, simu"
  },
  {
    "question": "更衣室",
    "answer": "こういしつ",
    "meaning": "locker room, changing room, dressing room"
  },
  {
    "question": "云う",
    "answer": "いう,ゆう",
    "meaning": "to say, to utter, to declare, to name, to call"
  },
  {
    "question": "高め",
    "answer": "たかめ",
    "meaning": "high (e.g. ball in baseball), highish, on the high side, on the expensive side, comparatively expens"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し込む",
    "answer": "はなしこむ",
    "meaning": "to be deep in talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "名高い",
    "answer": "なだかい",
    "meaning": "famous, noted, renowned, celebrated, well-known"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳を貸す",
    "answer": "みみをかす",
    "meaning": "to lend an ear to, to listen to"
  },
  {
    "question": "不謹慎",
    "answer": "ふきんしん",
    "meaning": "indiscrete, imprudent, unscrupulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "死因",
    "answer": "しいん",
    "meaning": "cause of death"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳障り",
    "answer": "みみざわり",
    "meaning": "hard (on the ears), offensive (to the ear), rasping, rough, harsh, grating, jarring, cacophonous"
  },
  {
    "question": "手腕",
    "answer": "しゅわん",
    "meaning": "ability, capability, skill"
  },
  {
    "question": "狩猟",
    "answer": "しゅりょう",
    "meaning": "hunting"
  },
  {
    "question": "士官",
    "answer": "しかん",
    "meaning": "officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "地中",
    "answer": "ちちゅう",
    "meaning": "underground, subterranean"
  },
  {
    "question": "催す",
    "answer": "もよおす",
    "meaning": "to hold (an event), to give (a dinner, party, etc.), to feel (sensation, emotion, call of nature, et"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠方",
    "answer": "えんぽう,おちかた",
    "meaning": "long way, distant place"
  },
  {
    "question": "参上",
    "answer": "さんじょう",
    "meaning": "calling on, visiting"
  },
  {
    "question": "同化",
    "answer": "どうか",
    "meaning": "assimilation, absorption, adaptation, anabolism, assimilation (phonology)"
  },
  {
    "question": "命運",
    "answer": "めいうん",
    "meaning": "fate, destiny"
  },
  {
    "question": "一拍",
    "answer": "いっぱく",
    "meaning": "one clap, one beat, one mora (taken as a unit of time)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大尉",
    "answer": "たいい,だいい",
    "meaning": "captain (Army, U.S. Marine Corps, USAF), lieutenant (Navy), flight lieutenant (RAF, RAAF, RNZAF, etc"
  },
  {
    "question": "日に日に",
    "answer": "ひにひに",
    "meaning": "day by day, by the day, daily, every day"
  },
  {
    "question": "局面",
    "answer": "きょくめん",
    "meaning": "position in a game of go or shogi, state of the game, aspect of an affair, situation"
  },
  {
    "question": "昇格",
    "answer": "しょうかく",
    "meaning": "raising of status, promotion, advance"
  },
  {
    "question": "天敵",
    "answer": "てんてき",
    "meaning": "natural enemy"
  },
  {
    "question": "直結",
    "answer": "ちょっけつ",
    "meaning": "direct connection, direct link"
  },
  {
    "question": "煩わしい",
    "answer": "わずらわしい",
    "meaning": "troublesome, annoying, complicated"
  },
  {
    "question": "画",
    "answer": "かく,え,が",
    "meaning": "stroke (of a kanji, etc.), picture, drawing, painting, sketch, image (TV, film, etc.), footage"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪霊",
    "answer": "あくりょう,あくれい",
    "meaning": "evil spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "松",
    "answer": "まつ",
    "meaning": "pine tree (Pinus spp.), highest (of a three-tier ranking system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "戯れる",
    "answer": "たわむれる,ざれる,じゃれる",
    "meaning": "to be playful, to gambol, to be amused (with something), to play, to sport, to frolic, to joke, to f"
  },
  {
    "question": "瀬",
    "answer": "せ",
    "meaning": "shallows, shoal, rapids, current, torrent, position, place, chance, opportunity"
  },
  {
    "question": "弦",
    "answer": "つる,げん",
    "meaning": "bowstring, string (of shamisen, guitar, violin, etc.), bail (arched pot handle), diagonal levelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "安らぐ",
    "answer": "やすらぐ",
    "meaning": "to feel at ease"
  },
  {
    "question": "沸かす",
    "answer": "わかす",
    "meaning": "to boil, to heat, to excite, to melt (metal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "野蛮",
    "answer": "やばん",
    "meaning": "savage, barbarous, barbaric, uncivilized, uncivilised"
  },
  {
    "question": "名簿",
    "answer": "めいぼ,みょうぶ",
    "meaning": "register of names, list of names, roll, register, roster, proof of identity (for nobles, doctors, et"
  },
  {
    "question": "徘徊",
    "answer": "はいかい",
    "meaning": "loitering, roaming, sauntering, wandering about, prowling"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘み",
    "answer": "あまみ",
    "meaning": "sweetness, sugary taste, sweets, dessert, cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "意気込む",
    "answer": "いきごむ",
    "meaning": "to be enthusiastic about, to be eager, to be keen"
  },
  {
    "question": "征服",
    "answer": "せいふく",
    "meaning": "conquest, subjugation, overcoming"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘲る",
    "answer": "あざける",
    "meaning": "to scoff, to laugh at, to make fun of, to ridicule, to jeer at"
  },
  {
    "question": "模索",
    "answer": "もさく",
    "meaning": "groping (for), fumbling around (for), searching (for an answer, solution, etc.), trying to find"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠密",
    "answer": "おんみつ",
    "meaning": "secret, clandestine, covert, spy (for a daimyo, shogun, etc.), secret agent"
  },
  {
    "question": "処",
    "answer": "ところ,どころ",
    "meaning": "place, spot, scene, site, address, district, area, locality, one's house, point, aspect, side, facet"
  },
  {
    "question": "綴る",
    "answer": "つづる",
    "meaning": "to spell, to write, to compose, to frame, to bind (e.g. documents), to patch, to sew together, to st"
  },
  {
    "question": "一大事",
    "answer": "いちだいじ",
    "meaning": "important matter, matter of great importance, serious affair, major incident, emergency"
  },
  {
    "question": "間一髪",
    "answer": "かんいっぱつ",
    "meaning": "hair's breadth"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸が痛む",
    "answer": "むねがいたむ",
    "meaning": "to experience chest pain, to have a pain in one's chest, to feel sick at heart, to have one's heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "下っ端",
    "answer": "したっぱ",
    "meaning": "underling, person of low standing, grunt, petty (work, official, etc.), minor, lowly, humble"
  },
  {
    "question": "辛辣",
    "answer": "しんらつ",
    "meaning": "bitter (e.g. criticism), sharp, biting, severe, scathing, harsh"
  },
  {
    "question": "比例",
    "answer": "ひれい",
    "meaning": "proportion"
  },
  {
    "question": "単体",
    "answer": "たんたい",
    "meaning": "simple substance (e.g. chemical), something standing alone, separate item, solo item"
  },
  {
    "question": "萎える",
    "answer": "なえる",
    "meaning": "to lose strength, to become weak, to disappear (of energy, drive, etc.), to wither, to droop, to wil"
  },
  {
    "question": "電話番号",
    "answer": "でんわばんごう",
    "meaning": "telephone number"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑猥",
    "answer": "ひわい",
    "meaning": "indecent, obscene"
  },
  {
    "question": "町中",
    "answer": "まちなか,まちじゅう",
    "meaning": "downtown, the whole town, all over the town, throughout the town"
  },
  {
    "question": "軸",
    "answer": "じく",
    "meaning": "axis, shaft, axle, center, centre, focal point, key point, stalk, stem, hanging scroll"
  },
  {
    "question": "一安心",
    "answer": "ひとあんしん",
    "meaning": "feeling of relief (for the time being), peace of mind (for now)"
  },
  {
    "question": "日光",
    "answer": "にっこう",
    "meaning": "sunlight, sunshine, sunbeams"
  },
  {
    "question": "身の回り",
    "answer": "みのまわり",
    "meaning": "one's personal belongings, one's vicinity, one's daily life, everyday necessities"
  },
  {
    "question": "会合",
    "answer": "かいごう",
    "meaning": "meeting, assembly, gathering, association, conjunction"
  },
  {
    "question": "組合",
    "answer": "くみあい",
    "meaning": "association, union, guild"
  },
  {
    "question": "嬌声",
    "answer": "きょうせい",
    "meaning": "coquettish voice, flirtatious voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "北海道",
    "answer": "ほっかいどう",
    "meaning": "Hokkaido (island, prefectural-level administrative unit)"
  },
  {
    "question": "刺激的",
    "answer": "しげきてき",
    "meaning": "stimulating, exciting, provocative"
  },
  {
    "question": "見立て",
    "answer": "みたて",
    "meaning": "choice, selection, diagnosis, medical opinion, judgement, opinion, estimation, comparison (in haiku,"
  },
  {
    "question": "由",
    "answer": "よし",
    "meaning": "reason, significance, cause, piece of information that one has heard, I hear that ..., it is said th"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦情",
    "answer": "くじょう",
    "meaning": "complaint, troubles, objection, grievance"
  },
  {
    "question": "有",
    "answer": "ゆう,う",
    "meaning": "existence, possession, having, limited company, bhava (becoming, existence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "貪欲",
    "answer": "どんよく,とんよく,たんよく",
    "meaning": "avarice, greed, covetousness, raga (desire)"
  },
  {
    "question": "近道",
    "answer": "ちかみち",
    "meaning": "short way, shortcut"
  },
  {
    "question": "居眠り",
    "answer": "いねむり",
    "meaning": "nodding off (while sitting), dozing"
  },
  {
    "question": "強いて",
    "answer": "しいて",
    "meaning": "by force"
  },
  {
    "question": "大雑把",
    "answer": "おおざっぱ",
    "meaning": "rough (estimate, manner, etc.), crude, broad, loose, careless (work)"
  },
  {
    "question": "意気",
    "answer": "いき",
    "meaning": "spirit, heart, disposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "眩暈",
    "answer": "めまい,げんうん",
    "meaning": "dizziness, giddiness, vertigo"
  },
  {
    "question": "葬儀",
    "answer": "そうぎ",
    "meaning": "funeral service"
  },
  {
    "question": "定着",
    "answer": "ていちゃく",
    "meaning": "sticking (in one place, position, etc.), settling, fixing, adherence, becoming established (of a cus"
  },
  {
    "question": "停める",
    "answer": "とめる,とどめる",
    "meaning": "to stop, to turn off, to park, to prevent, to suppress (a cough), to hold back (tears), to hold (one"
  },
  {
    "question": "北部",
    "answer": "ほくぶ",
    "meaning": "northern part, the north (of a region)"
  },
  {
    "question": "自動車",
    "answer": "じどうしゃ",
    "meaning": "automobile, motorcar, motor vehicle, car, auto"
  },
  {
    "question": "迎え",
    "answer": "むかえ",
    "meaning": "meeting, greeting, welcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜間",
    "answer": "やかん",
    "meaning": "night, nighttime"
  },
  {
    "question": "滲み出る",
    "answer": "しみでる,にじみでる",
    "meaning": "to ooze, to exude, to percolate, to soak through, to exude (e.g. sweat), to seep out, to reveal itse"
  },
  {
    "question": "発信",
    "answer": "はっしん",
    "meaning": "dispatch, despatch, transmission, submission, informing (e.g. of opinion), sharing (thoughts, etc.),"
  },
  {
    "question": "和解",
    "answer": "わかい,わげ",
    "meaning": "reconciliation, amicable settlement, accommodation, compromise, mediation, rapprochement, court-medi"
  },
  {
    "question": "承る",
    "answer": "うけたまわる",
    "meaning": "to hear, to be told, to know, to receive (order), to undertake, to comply, to take (a reservation, e"
  },
  {
    "question": "毛並み",
    "answer": "けなみ",
    "meaning": "coat (of hair or fur), lie of (dog's) hair, type, sort, lineage, breeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "掟",
    "answer": "おきて",
    "meaning": "law, regulation, rule, code, agreement, arrangement, compact"
  },
  {
    "question": "不憫",
    "answer": "ふびん",
    "meaning": "poor, pitiful, piteous, pitiable"
  },
  {
    "question": "一介",
    "answer": "いっかい",
    "meaning": "mere, only a ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "受かる",
    "answer": "うかる",
    "meaning": "to pass (examination)"
  },
  {
    "question": "森林",
    "answer": "しんりん",
    "meaning": "forest, woods"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼馴染み",
    "answer": "おさななじみ,おさなじみ",
    "meaning": "childhood friend, friend from infancy, old playmate"
  },
  {
    "question": "藤",
    "answer": "ふじ",
    "meaning": "wisteria (esp. Japanese wisteria, Wisteria floribunda), wistaria"
  },
  {
    "question": "装い",
    "answer": "よそおい",
    "meaning": "dress, outfit, equipment, makeup, adornment, guise, get-up"
  },
  {
    "question": "囁き",
    "answer": "ささやき,つつやき",
    "meaning": "whispering, whisper, secret talk, murmur"
  },
  {
    "question": "防止",
    "answer": "ぼうし",
    "meaning": "prevention, check"
  },
  {
    "question": "肩口",
    "answer": "かたぐち",
    "meaning": "top of the shoulders, tip of the shoulder, collar"
  },
  {
    "question": "怠惰",
    "answer": "たいだ",
    "meaning": "lazy, idle, indolent, slothful"
  },
  {
    "question": "発作",
    "answer": "ほっさ",
    "meaning": "fit, spasm, attack, seizure"
  },
  {
    "question": "揚げる",
    "answer": "あげる",
    "meaning": "to raise, to elevate, to do up (one's hair), to fly (a kite, etc.), to launch (fireworks, etc.), to"
  },
  {
    "question": "直線",
    "answer": "ちょくせん",
    "meaning": "straight line"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会人",
    "answer": "しゃかいじん",
    "meaning": "working adult, full-fledged member of society"
  },
  {
    "question": "盗み聞き",
    "answer": "ぬすみぎき",
    "meaning": "eavesdropping, tapping"
  },
  {
    "question": "若造",
    "answer": "わかぞう",
    "meaning": "youngster, neophyte, greenhorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "他所",
    "answer": "よそ,たしょ",
    "meaning": "another place, somewhere else, strange parts, outside (one's family or group), someone else, other p"
  },
  {
    "question": "中立",
    "answer": "ちゅうりつ,なかだち",
    "meaning": "neutrality, break between the light meal and the actual serving of tea (during a formal tea ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "垂れ流す",
    "answer": "たれながす",
    "meaning": "to discharge (e.g. effluent)"
  },
  {
    "question": "分間",
    "answer": "ふんかん",
    "meaning": "minutes (period of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹立つ",
    "answer": "はらだつ",
    "meaning": "to get angry"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳天",
    "answer": "のうてん",
    "meaning": "top of the head, crown of the head"
  },
  {
    "question": "靄",
    "answer": "もや",
    "meaning": "mist, haze"
  },
  {
    "question": "指紋",
    "answer": "しもん",
    "meaning": "fingerprint"
  },
  {
    "question": "用紙",
    "answer": "ようし",
    "meaning": "blank form, sheets of paper, sheet of paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "侮蔑",
    "answer": "ぶべつ",
    "meaning": "scorn, disdain, contempt, slight"
  },
  {
    "question": "三番",
    "answer": "さんばん",
    "meaning": "third, no. three"
  },
  {
    "question": "非情",
    "answer": "ひじょう",
    "meaning": "cold-hearted, callous, unfeeling, cruel, insentient (objects), insensate, inanimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "晴れやか",
    "answer": "はれやか",
    "meaning": "clear, bright, sunny"
  },
  {
    "question": "安らぎ",
    "answer": "やすらぎ",
    "meaning": "peace (of mind), tranquility, tranquillity, serenity"
  },
  {
    "question": "関東",
    "answer": "かんとう",
    "meaning": "Kanto, region consisting of Tokyo and surrounding prefectures, north-eastern half of Japan (during t"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠落",
    "answer": "けつらく",
    "meaning": "missing, lacking"
  },
  {
    "question": "飄々",
    "answer": "ひょうひょう",
    "meaning": "whistling (wind), blowing, howling, fluttering (in the wind), waving, flapping, swirling, dancing, s"
  },
  {
    "question": "出勤",
    "answer": "しゅっきん",
    "meaning": "going to work, leaving for work, attendance (at work), being at work, presence (in the office), repo"
  },
  {
    "question": "半透明",
    "answer": "はんとうめい",
    "meaning": "semi-transparent, translucent"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り消す",
    "answer": "とりけす",
    "meaning": "to cancel, to withdraw, to retract, to take back (words, etc.), to revoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "師団",
    "answer": "しだん",
    "meaning": "(army) division"
  },
  {
    "question": "宜しい",
    "answer": "よろしい",
    "meaning": "good, OK, all right, fine, very well, will do, may, can"
  },
  {
    "question": "何物",
    "answer": "なにもの",
    "meaning": "something, nothing (with neg. verb)"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜風",
    "answer": "よかぜ",
    "meaning": "night wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗面所",
    "answer": "せんめんじょ",
    "meaning": "washroom, bathroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "暖か",
    "answer": "あたたか,あったか",
    "meaning": "warm, mild, genial"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け足す",
    "answer": "つけたす",
    "meaning": "to add (to), to add on, to append"
  },
  {
    "question": "隣接",
    "answer": "りんせつ",
    "meaning": "adjacency, contiguity, being adjoined"
  },
  {
    "question": "索敵",
    "answer": "さくてき",
    "meaning": "searching for the enemy"
  },
  {
    "question": "共和国",
    "answer": "きょうわこく",
    "meaning": "republic, commonwealth"
  },
  {
    "question": "手札",
    "answer": "てふだ",
    "meaning": "one's hand (when playing cards), name tag, nameplate, business card, wallet-sized (photo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸まる",
    "answer": "まるまる",
    "meaning": "to become rounded, to roll into a ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "桶",
    "answer": "おけ",
    "meaning": "bucket, pail, tub"
  },
  {
    "question": "昆虫",
    "answer": "こんちゅう",
    "meaning": "insect, bug"
  },
  {
    "question": "若手",
    "answer": "わかて",
    "meaning": "young person"
  },
  {
    "question": "演習",
    "answer": "えんしゅう",
    "meaning": "practice, practising, exercises, manoeuvres, maneuvers, seminar (student debates, presentations, etc"
  },
  {
    "question": "暑苦しい",
    "answer": "あつくるしい",
    "meaning": "sultry, sweltering, stuffy, oppressively hot, uncomfortably hot-looking (clothing, etc.), stuffy-loo"
  },
  {
    "question": "劣化",
    "answer": "れっか",
    "meaning": "deterioration, degradation, drop in quality, becoming unattractive (because of aging)"
  },
  {
    "question": "返却",
    "answer": "へんきゃく",
    "meaning": "return of something, repayment"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱げる",
    "answer": "ぬげる",
    "meaning": "to come off, to slip down, to slip off"
  },
  {
    "question": "棺",
    "answer": "かん,ひつぎ",
    "meaning": "coffin, casket"
  },
  {
    "question": "落とし穴",
    "answer": "おとしあな",
    "meaning": "pitfall, trap, pit"
  },
  {
    "question": "異界",
    "answer": "いかい",
    "meaning": "spirit world, underworld, the next world"
  },
  {
    "question": "媚びる",
    "answer": "こびる",
    "meaning": "to flatter, to curry favor with, to curry favour with, to fawn on, to butter up to, to flirt with (w"
  },
  {
    "question": "老いる",
    "answer": "おいる",
    "meaning": "to age, to grow old"
  },
  {
    "question": "口に合う",
    "answer": "くちにあう",
    "meaning": "to be palatable, to suit one's taste"
  },
  {
    "question": "一式",
    "answer": "いっしき",
    "meaning": "complete set, all, everything"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒れ狂う",
    "answer": "あれくるう",
    "meaning": "to rampage, to run wild, to go berserk, to run amok, to be violent (waves, wind, etc.), to be rough"
  },
  {
    "question": "手品",
    "answer": "てじな",
    "meaning": "magic (illusion), conjuring, magic trick, conjuring trick, sleight of hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "平らげる",
    "answer": "たいらげる",
    "meaning": "to eat up (completely), to put down (a rebellion), to suppress, to subjugate, to make flat, to level"
  },
  {
    "question": "採掘",
    "answer": "さいくつ",
    "meaning": "mining"
  },
  {
    "question": "消え入る",
    "answer": "きえいる",
    "meaning": "to vanish"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆ぜる",
    "answer": "はぜる",
    "meaning": "to burst open, to pop, to split"
  },
  {
    "question": "三角",
    "answer": "さんかく",
    "meaning": "triangle, triangular shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "物件",
    "answer": "ぶっけん",
    "meaning": "article, thing, object, property (real estate)"
  },
  {
    "question": "横取り",
    "answer": "よこどり",
    "meaning": "snatching, stealing, seizure, usurpation"
  },
  {
    "question": "西側",
    "answer": "にしがわ",
    "meaning": "west side, west bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "垂直",
    "answer": "すいちょく",
    "meaning": "vertical, perpendicular"
  },
  {
    "question": "城門",
    "answer": "じょうもん",
    "meaning": "castle gate"
  },
  {
    "question": "子供扱い",
    "answer": "こどもあつかい",
    "meaning": "treating someone like a child"
  },
  {
    "question": "思念",
    "answer": "しねん",
    "meaning": "thought"
  },
  {
    "question": "虐める",
    "answer": "いじめる",
    "meaning": "to ill-treat, to bully, to torment, to pick on, to tease, to be cruel to, to persecute, to be tough"
  },
  {
    "question": "長距離",
    "answer": "ちょうきょり",
    "meaning": "long distance, long haul"
  },
  {
    "question": "家賃",
    "answer": "やちん",
    "meaning": "rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "情勢",
    "answer": "じょうせい",
    "meaning": "state of things, state of affairs, condition, situation, circumstances"
  },
  {
    "question": "小瓶",
    "answer": "こびん",
    "meaning": "small bottle"
  },
  {
    "question": "脂",
    "answer": "あぶら,やに",
    "meaning": "fat, tallow, lard, grease, resin, (tobacco) resin, tar, nicotine, sleep (in one's eyes, i.e. eye muc"
  },
  {
    "question": "麦",
    "answer": "むぎ",
    "meaning": "wheat, barley, oat (oats)"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶葉",
    "answer": "ちゃば",
    "meaning": "tea leaf, tea leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "団員",
    "answer": "だんいん",
    "meaning": "group member"
  },
  {
    "question": "達成感",
    "answer": "たっせいかん",
    "meaning": "sense of accomplishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "替え",
    "answer": "かえ,がえ",
    "meaning": "change, alteration, substitute, spare, replacement, proxy, rate of exchange"
  },
  {
    "question": "現す",
    "answer": "あらわす",
    "meaning": "to represent, to signify, to stand for, to reveal, to show, to display, to express, to make widely k"
  },
  {
    "question": "虐げる",
    "answer": "しいたげる",
    "meaning": "to oppress, to persecute, to tyrannize"
  },
  {
    "question": "刻み込む",
    "answer": "きざみこむ",
    "meaning": "to etch (name, etc.), to carve (design)"
  },
  {
    "question": "光沢",
    "answer": "こうたく",
    "meaning": "brilliance, polish, lustre, luster, glossy finish (of photographs)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一品",
    "answer": "いっぴん,ひとしな",
    "meaning": "item, article, dish, course, finest item"
  },
  {
    "question": "適応",
    "answer": "てきおう",
    "meaning": "adaptation, accommodation, conformity"
  },
  {
    "question": "導き",
    "answer": "みちびき",
    "meaning": "guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "一心不乱",
    "answer": "いっしんふらん",
    "meaning": "wholeheartedly, with heart and soul, intently, with undivided attention, with intense concentration,"
  },
  {
    "question": "良心",
    "answer": "りょうしん",
    "meaning": "conscience"
  },
  {
    "question": "心構え",
    "answer": "こころがまえ",
    "meaning": "preparedness, readiness, mental attitude, frame of mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "差出人",
    "answer": "さしだしにん",
    "meaning": "sender"
  },
  {
    "question": "高笑い",
    "answer": "たかわらい",
    "meaning": "loud laughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "と言えど",
    "answer": "といえど",
    "meaning": "be (that) as it may, having said that"
  },
  {
    "question": "言及",
    "answer": "げんきゅう",
    "meaning": "reference, allusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "転落",
    "answer": "てんらく",
    "meaning": "fall, tumble, spill, plunge, dive, degradation, comedown, demotion, slump"
  },
  {
    "question": "措置",
    "answer": "そち",
    "meaning": "measure, step, action"
  },
  {
    "question": "終焉",
    "answer": "しゅうえん",
    "meaning": "demise"
  },
  {
    "question": "罰ゲーム",
    "answer": "ばつゲーム",
    "meaning": "batsu game, punishment given to the loser of a game or contest"
  },
  {
    "question": "秘匿",
    "answer": "ひとく",
    "meaning": "hiding, concealment"
  },
  {
    "question": "左様",
    "answer": "さよう",
    "meaning": "so, like that, that's right, indeed, let me see..."
  },
  {
    "question": "引き攣る",
    "answer": "ひきつる",
    "meaning": "to have a cramp, to twitch, to spasm, to stiffen (of a face, expression), to freeze, to grow tight ("
  },
  {
    "question": "心を開く",
    "answer": "こころをひらく",
    "meaning": "to divulge one's true feelings, to open one's heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "道端",
    "answer": "みちばた",
    "meaning": "roadside, wayside"
  },
  {
    "question": "口をきく",
    "answer": "くちをきく",
    "meaning": "to speak, to talk, to mediate, to act as a go-between, to put in a good word (for someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "痺れ",
    "answer": "しびれ",
    "meaning": "numbness, going to sleep (of a limb), pins and needles"
  },
  {
    "question": "顧みる",
    "answer": "かえりみる",
    "meaning": "to look back on (the past), to reflect on, to reminisce about, to look behind (at), to turn round (a"
  },
  {
    "question": "隅っこ",
    "answer": "すみっこ",
    "meaning": "corner, nook, recess"
  },
  {
    "question": "見定める",
    "answer": "みさだめる",
    "meaning": "to make sure of, to ascertain, to confirm, to grasp"
  },
  {
    "question": "受信",
    "answer": "じゅしん",
    "meaning": "receiving (a message, letter, email, etc.), reception (radio, TV, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "無理強い",
    "answer": "むりじい",
    "meaning": "forcing, compulsion, coercion, pushing (to do)"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝転ぶ",
    "answer": "ねころぶ",
    "meaning": "to lie down, to throw oneself down"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕上がる",
    "answer": "しあがる",
    "meaning": "to be finished, to be completed, to be done"
  },
  {
    "question": "どす黒い",
    "answer": "どすぐろい",
    "meaning": "darkish, dusky"
  },
  {
    "question": "南部",
    "answer": "なんぶ",
    "meaning": "southern part, the south (of a region)"
  },
  {
    "question": "修業",
    "answer": "しゅうぎょう,しゅぎょう",
    "meaning": "pursuit of knowledge, studying, learning, training, completing a course"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞き逃す",
    "answer": "ききのがす",
    "meaning": "to fail to hear something, to miss, to act as if one didn't hear something, to let a remark slide"
  },
  {
    "question": "睨み合う",
    "answer": "にらみあう",
    "meaning": "to glare at each other, to confront each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "義姉",
    "answer": "ぎし,あね",
    "meaning": "sister-in-law (spouse's older sister or older brother's wife), older stepsister, older adopted siste"
  },
  {
    "question": "地響き",
    "answer": "じひびき",
    "meaning": "subterranean rumbling, earth tremor"
  },
  {
    "question": "複製",
    "answer": "ふくせい",
    "meaning": "reproduction, duplication, reprinting"
  },
  {
    "question": "陥落",
    "answer": "かんらく",
    "meaning": "fall, sinking, surrender, capitulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い",
    "answer": "かい",
    "meaning": "buying, shopping, buyer, purchase"
  },
  {
    "question": "野次馬",
    "answer": "やじうま",
    "meaning": "curious onlookers, rubbernecks"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己嫌悪",
    "answer": "じこけんお",
    "meaning": "self-hatred, self-abhorrence, self-loathing"
  },
  {
    "question": "化す",
    "answer": "かす,けす",
    "meaning": "to change into, to convert to, to transform, to be reduced, to influence, to improve (someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "教団",
    "answer": "きょうだん",
    "meaning": "religious organization, religious organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "栽培",
    "answer": "さいばい",
    "meaning": "cultivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁える",
    "answer": "わきまえる",
    "meaning": "to discern (e.g. right from wrong), to discriminate, to distinguish, to know (manners, one's place,"
  },
  {
    "question": "会談",
    "answer": "かいだん",
    "meaning": "conversation, conference (usu. between important people), discussion, interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "失言",
    "answer": "しつげん",
    "meaning": "verbal gaffe, verbal slip, slip of the tongue, using improper words"
  },
  {
    "question": "空想",
    "answer": "くうそう",
    "meaning": "daydream, fantasy, fancy, vision"
  },
  {
    "question": "抹殺",
    "answer": "まっさつ",
    "meaning": "erasure, denial, obliteration, ignoring (an opinion)"
  },
  {
    "question": "訝しむ",
    "answer": "いぶかしむ",
    "meaning": "to be suspicious of, to be doubtful of, to be dubious of"
  },
  {
    "question": "流れ出す",
    "answer": "ながれだす",
    "meaning": "to flow out, to stream out, to pour out, to gush forth, to leak, to ooze out, to drift away"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い直す",
    "answer": "いいなおす",
    "meaning": "to correct oneself, to restate"
  },
  {
    "question": "票",
    "answer": "ひょう",
    "meaning": "vote, ballot, label, ticket, tag, stub"
  },
  {
    "question": "秘密裏",
    "answer": "ひみつり",
    "meaning": "behind closed doors, behind-the-scenes, (under the veil of) secrecy"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕捉",
    "answer": "ほそく",
    "meaning": "capture, seizure, prehension, trapping, apprehension, understanding, grasp"
  },
  {
    "question": "余分",
    "answer": "よぶん",
    "meaning": "extra, excess, surplus"
  },
  {
    "question": "獲る",
    "answer": "とる,える",
    "meaning": "to take, to catch, to capture, to get, to earn, to acquire, to procure, to gain, to secure, to attai"
  },
  {
    "question": "策略",
    "answer": "さくりゃく",
    "meaning": "scheme, tactic, stratagem, trick"
  },
  {
    "question": "蜂蜜",
    "answer": "はちみつ,はつみつ",
    "meaning": "honey"
  },
  {
    "question": "出直す",
    "answer": "でなおす",
    "meaning": "to make a fresh start, to turn over a new leaf, to call again, to visit again, to come again"
  },
  {
    "question": "責任感",
    "answer": "せきにんかん",
    "meaning": "sense of responsibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "市長",
    "answer": "しちょう",
    "meaning": "mayor"
  },
  {
    "question": "儲かる",
    "answer": "もうかる",
    "meaning": "to be profitable, to yield a profit"
  },
  {
    "question": "真っ最中",
    "answer": "まっさいちゅう,まっさなか",
    "meaning": "right in the middle (of), midst, height"
  },
  {
    "question": "昭和",
    "answer": "しょうわ",
    "meaning": "Shōwa era (1926.12.25-1989.1.7), reminiscent of the Shōwa era, Shōwa-nostalgic, old-fashioned, quain"
  },
  {
    "question": "貸し",
    "answer": "かし",
    "meaning": "loan, lending, favor, favour, debt, obligation, creditor, method of lending, credit side"
  },
  {
    "question": "何にせよ",
    "answer": "なんにせよ",
    "meaning": "at any rate, anyhow, anyway, in any case, because"
  },
  {
    "question": "調節",
    "answer": "ちょうせつ",
    "meaning": "regulation, adjustment, control"
  },
  {
    "question": "味噌",
    "answer": "みそ",
    "meaning": "miso, fermented condiment usu. made from soybeans, innards (from crabs, shrimps, etc.) resembling mi"
  },
  {
    "question": "祖国",
    "answer": "そこく",
    "meaning": "motherland, fatherland, native country"
  },
  {
    "question": "奮闘",
    "answer": "ふんとう",
    "meaning": "hard struggle, strenuous effort"
  },
  {
    "question": "培う",
    "answer": "つちかう",
    "meaning": "to cultivate, to foster"
  },
  {
    "question": "大笑い",
    "answer": "おおわらい",
    "meaning": "great laughter, burst of laughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "残滓",
    "answer": "ざんし,ざんさい",
    "meaning": "remains, dregs, vestiges, remnant, residue"
  },
  {
    "question": "概要",
    "answer": "がいよう",
    "meaning": "outline, summary, overview, synopsis, abstract, abridgment, abridgement"
  },
  {
    "question": "痣",
    "answer": "あざ",
    "meaning": "birthmark, nevus, bruise"
  },
  {
    "question": "父ちゃん",
    "answer": "とうちゃん,とっちゃん",
    "meaning": "dad, daddy, papa, pa, pop"
  },
  {
    "question": "流れ出る",
    "answer": "ながれでる",
    "meaning": "to flow out, to stream out, to pour out, to gush forth, to leak, to ooze out, to drift away"
  },
  {
    "question": "主力",
    "answer": "しゅりょく",
    "meaning": "main force, chief object, mainline"
  },
  {
    "question": "最速",
    "answer": "さいそく",
    "meaning": "fastest"
  },
  {
    "question": "進軍",
    "answer": "しんぐん",
    "meaning": "march, advance"
  },
  {
    "question": "精密",
    "answer": "せいみつ",
    "meaning": "precise, exact, detailed, accurate, minute, close"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼子",
    "answer": "おさなご",
    "meaning": "infant, baby, little child"
  },
  {
    "question": "今時",
    "answer": "いまどき",
    "meaning": "these days, nowadays, present day, modern times, at this time (of the day)"
  },
  {
    "question": "重厚",
    "answer": "じゅうこう,ちょうこう",
    "meaning": "profound, deep, grave, solid, dignified, stately, solemn, massive, composed"
  },
  {
    "question": "興じる",
    "answer": "きょうじる",
    "meaning": "to amuse oneself, to make merry"
  },
  {
    "question": "容疑",
    "answer": "ようぎ",
    "meaning": "suspicion, charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "相殺",
    "answer": "そうさい,そうさつ",
    "meaning": "offset, offsetting each other, cancelling each other out, counterbalancing, set-off, setoff"
  },
  {
    "question": "手触り",
    "answer": "てざわり",
    "meaning": "feel, touch"
  },
  {
    "question": "樹木",
    "answer": "じゅもく",
    "meaning": "tree, trees and shrubs"
  },
  {
    "question": "一戦",
    "answer": "いっせん",
    "meaning": "battle, game, bout"
  },
  {
    "question": "手法",
    "answer": "しゅほう",
    "meaning": "technique, method"
  },
  {
    "question": "解答",
    "answer": "かいとう",
    "meaning": "answer, solution"
  },
  {
    "question": "地雷",
    "answer": "じらい",
    "meaning": "land mine, topic that sets someone off, sensitive topic, taboo topic, trigger, something that seems"
  },
  {
    "question": "分断",
    "answer": "ぶんだん",
    "meaning": "dividing into parts"
  },
  {
    "question": "連射",
    "answer": "れんしゃ",
    "meaning": "rapid-fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "憤り",
    "answer": "いきどおり",
    "meaning": "resentment, indignation, anger"
  },
  {
    "question": "分離",
    "answer": "ぶんり",
    "meaning": "separation, partition, detachment, segregation, isolation"
  },
  {
    "question": "風貌",
    "answer": "ふうぼう",
    "meaning": "looks, appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "安物",
    "answer": "やすもの",
    "meaning": "cheap article, poor quality article"
  },
  {
    "question": "堂",
    "answer": "どう",
    "meaning": "temple, shrine, chapel, hall, company, front room"
  },
  {
    "question": "背く",
    "answer": "そむく",
    "meaning": "to run counter to, to go against, to disobey, to infringe"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆発的",
    "answer": "ばくはつてき",
    "meaning": "explosive, sudden and dramatic (of an increase in sales, popularity, etc.), rapid, abrupt, tremendou"
  },
  {
    "question": "凝縮",
    "answer": "ぎょうしゅく",
    "meaning": "condensation (of ideas, emotions, etc.), condensation (of a vapour or gas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "出所",
    "answer": "しゅっしょ,でどころ,でどこ",
    "meaning": "origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, ti"
  },
  {
    "question": "活性化",
    "answer": "かっせいか",
    "meaning": "stimulation (e.g. of an economy), revitalization (e.g. of a town), rejuvenation, invigoration, activ"
  },
  {
    "question": "膝枕",
    "answer": "ひざまくら",
    "meaning": "laying one's head in someone's lap"
  },
  {
    "question": "受け答え",
    "answer": "うけこたえ",
    "meaning": "reply, response, answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "企み",
    "answer": "たくらみ",
    "meaning": "plot, scheme, trick, design, intrigue, artifice, conspiracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "呪縛",
    "answer": "じゅばく",
    "meaning": "spell (that restricts one's movements), binding spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会的",
    "answer": "しゃかいてき",
    "meaning": "social, societal, societary"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄昏",
    "answer": "たそがれ,こうこん",
    "meaning": "dusk, twilight, twilight years, melancholia, melancholic nostalgia"
  },
  {
    "question": "一掃",
    "answer": "いっそう",
    "meaning": "clean sweep, purging, doing away with, eradication"
  },
  {
    "question": "主婦",
    "answer": "しゅふ",
    "meaning": "housewife, mistress (of the house), homemaker"
  },
  {
    "question": "無神経",
    "answer": "むしんけい",
    "meaning": "insensitive, inconsiderate, callous, thick-skinned"
  },
  {
    "question": "鐘の音",
    "answer": "かねのね",
    "meaning": "chimes, toll of a bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "出演",
    "answer": "しゅつえん",
    "meaning": "performance, appearance (in a stage, film, TV show, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大木",
    "answer": "たいぼく",
    "meaning": "large tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "殺人鬼",
    "answer": "さつじんき",
    "meaning": "bloodthirsty killer, cold-blooded murderer, homicidal maniac"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼠",
    "answer": "ねずみ,ねず",
    "meaning": "mouse, rat, dark gray, dark grey, slate (color, colour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "考察",
    "answer": "こうさつ",
    "meaning": "consideration, inquiry, enquiry, investigation, study"
  },
  {
    "question": "草木",
    "answer": "くさき,そうもく",
    "meaning": "plants, vegetation"
  },
  {
    "question": "怒り狂う",
    "answer": "いかりくるう",
    "meaning": "to be in a fit (of anger), to rage"
  },
  {
    "question": "上体",
    "answer": "じょうたい",
    "meaning": "upper body"
  },
  {
    "question": "手口",
    "answer": "てぐち",
    "meaning": "modus operandi, criminal technique, trick"
  },
  {
    "question": "機密",
    "answer": "きみつ",
    "meaning": "secrecy, highly classified information"
  },
  {
    "question": "口を噤む",
    "answer": "くちをつぐむ",
    "meaning": "to hold one's tongue, to shut up"
  },
  {
    "question": "上陸",
    "answer": "じょうりく",
    "meaning": "landing, disembarkation, landfall"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経質",
    "answer": "しんけいしつ",
    "meaning": "nervous, highly strung, sensitive, fussy, worried about petty things"
  },
  {
    "question": "有益",
    "answer": "ゆうえき",
    "meaning": "beneficial, profitable, useful, helpful, instructive"
  },
  {
    "question": "葵",
    "answer": "あおい",
    "meaning": "mallow (any plant of family Malvaceae), Asarum caulescens (species of wild ginger), hollyhock"
  },
  {
    "question": "試行錯誤",
    "answer": "しこうさくご",
    "meaning": "trial and error"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い抜く",
    "answer": "おいぬく",
    "meaning": "to pass (a car), to overtake, to surpass, to outstrip, to outdistance, to outsail"
  },
  {
    "question": "狼狽える",
    "answer": "うろたえる",
    "meaning": "to be flustered, to lose one's presence of mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "生き抜く",
    "answer": "いきぬく",
    "meaning": "to live through, to survive"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁明",
    "answer": "べんめい",
    "meaning": "explanation, excuse, clarification, vindication, apology"
  },
  {
    "question": "餌食",
    "answer": "えじき",
    "meaning": "prey, victim"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑巾",
    "answer": "ぞうきん",
    "meaning": "house-cloth, dust cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "不慣れ",
    "answer": "ふなれ",
    "meaning": "inexperienced, unfamiliar (with), unversed, lacking experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "調教",
    "answer": "ちょうきょう",
    "meaning": "training (animals), breaking (animals)"
  },
  {
    "question": "話が早い",
    "answer": "はなしがはやい",
    "meaning": "being settled quickly, reaching a quick conclusion, no need to say any more, no problem"
  },
  {
    "question": "唯",
    "answer": "ただ",
    "meaning": "ordinary, common, usual, free of charge, unaffected, as is, safe, only, merely, just, simply, but, h"
  },
  {
    "question": "応戦",
    "answer": "おうせん",
    "meaning": "fighting back, returning fire, counter-attack, responding to an attack, accepting a challenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "交易",
    "answer": "こうえき",
    "meaning": "trade, commerce"
  },
  {
    "question": "猪",
    "answer": "いのしし,しし,い",
    "meaning": "wild boar, wild pig, beast (esp. one used for its meat, such as a boar or a deer), hunting (of anima"
  },
  {
    "question": "情景",
    "answer": "じょうけい",
    "meaning": "spectacle, sight, scene"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪獣",
    "answer": "かいじゅう",
    "meaning": "monster"
  },
  {
    "question": "紋",
    "answer": "もん",
    "meaning": "(family) crest, coat of arms, pattern, figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬品",
    "answer": "やくひん",
    "meaning": "medicine, chemicals"
  },
  {
    "question": "海水",
    "answer": "かいすい",
    "meaning": "seawater, saltwater"
  },
  {
    "question": "文献",
    "answer": "ぶんけん",
    "meaning": "literature, books (reference), document"
  },
  {
    "question": "挟み込む",
    "answer": "はさみこむ",
    "meaning": "to insert, to put between, to tuck (e.g. fabric into a gap)"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤み",
    "answer": "あかみ",
    "meaning": "reddish tinge, tinge of red, slight redness, reddishness, blush"
  },
  {
    "question": "修練",
    "answer": "しゅうれん",
    "meaning": "training, drill, practice, practising, discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "萌える",
    "answer": "もえる",
    "meaning": "to burst into bud, to sprout, to have a crush, to be infatuated"
  },
  {
    "question": "移住",
    "answer": "いじゅう",
    "meaning": "migration, immigration"
  },
  {
    "question": "超絶",
    "answer": "ちょうぜつ",
    "meaning": "transcendence, excellence, superiority"
  },
  {
    "question": "不可思議",
    "answer": "ふかしぎ",
    "meaning": "mystery, something inexplicable, wonder, miracle, unfathomable (of a Buddha's abilities), 10^64 (or"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き",
    "answer": "なき",
    "meaning": "weeping, lamenting"
  },
  {
    "question": "初老",
    "answer": "しょろう",
    "meaning": "past middle age, nearing old age, near-elderly, age 40"
  },
  {
    "question": "凡人",
    "answer": "ぼんじん,ぼんにん",
    "meaning": "ordinary person, average person, mediocre person"
  },
  {
    "question": "二分",
    "answer": "にぶん,にふん",
    "meaning": "halving, dividing (into two parts), bisection, the two equinoxes (vernal and autumnal), two minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "発端",
    "answer": "ほったん",
    "meaning": "origin, genesis, opening, start, beginning"
  },
  {
    "question": "波紋",
    "answer": "はもん",
    "meaning": "ripple, ring on the water, repercussions, Japanese slit drum, instrument made of iron with slits on"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑屈",
    "answer": "ひくつ",
    "meaning": "menial, meanness, servility, abject"
  },
  {
    "question": "償い",
    "answer": "つぐない",
    "meaning": "recompense, indemnity, atonement"
  },
  {
    "question": "別段",
    "answer": "べつだん,べちだん",
    "meaning": "particular, special, (not) particularly, (not) especially"
  },
  {
    "question": "辞書",
    "answer": "じしょ",
    "meaning": "dictionary, lexicon, letter of resignation"
  },
  {
    "question": "白紙",
    "answer": "はくし,しらかみ",
    "meaning": "white paper, flyleaf, blank paper, clean slate, lack of prior opinion, positions, etc., scratch, beg"
  },
  {
    "question": "教皇",
    "answer": "きょうこう,きょうおう",
    "meaning": "Pope"
  },
  {
    "question": "予選",
    "answer": "よせん",
    "meaning": "preliminary contest, qualifying round, trial, heat, primary"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚意",
    "answer": "こうい",
    "meaning": "kindness, favor, favour"
  },
  {
    "question": "挟まる",
    "answer": "はさまる",
    "meaning": "to get between, to be caught in"
  },
  {
    "question": "部門",
    "answer": "ぶもん",
    "meaning": "division (of a larger group), branch, field, class (subclass), group, category, department"
  },
  {
    "question": "不調",
    "answer": "ふちょう",
    "meaning": "bad condition, not to work out (i.e. a deal), disagreement, break-off, disorder, slump, out of form"
  },
  {
    "question": "揶揄",
    "answer": "やゆ",
    "meaning": "banter, raillery, ridicule, teasing, making fun of"
  },
  {
    "question": "信",
    "answer": "しん",
    "meaning": "honesty, sincerity, fidelity, trust, reliance, confidence, (religious) faith, devotion, counter for"
  },
  {
    "question": "醜悪",
    "answer": "しゅうあく",
    "meaning": "ugly, unsightly, hideous, mean, repulsive, disgraceful"
  },
  {
    "question": "傷付ける",
    "answer": "きずつける",
    "meaning": "to wound, to injure, to hurt someone's feelings (pride, etc.), to damage, to chip, to scratch"
  },
  {
    "question": "箒",
    "answer": "ほうき",
    "meaning": "broom"
  },
  {
    "question": "野宿",
    "answer": "のじゅく",
    "meaning": "sleeping outdoors, sleeping out in the open air, camping"
  },
  {
    "question": "頼み込む",
    "answer": "たのみこむ",
    "meaning": "to request earnestly"
  },
  {
    "question": "兆候",
    "answer": "ちょうこう",
    "meaning": "sign, indication, omen, symptom"
  },
  {
    "question": "大まか",
    "answer": "おおまか",
    "meaning": "rough (estimate, outline, etc.), broad, general, loose, generous, openhanded"
  },
  {
    "question": "問い返す",
    "answer": "といかえす",
    "meaning": "to ask again, to repeat one's question, to ask back, to ask in return, to counter"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄汚れる",
    "answer": "うすよごれる",
    "meaning": "to get slightly dirty (all over)"
  },
  {
    "question": "猛獣",
    "answer": "もうじゅう",
    "meaning": "fierce animal, beast of prey, big game"
  },
  {
    "question": "長髪",
    "answer": "ちょうはつ",
    "meaning": "long hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "配達",
    "answer": "はいたつ,はいだつ",
    "meaning": "delivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "手合わせ",
    "answer": "てあわせ",
    "meaning": "game, contest, bout"
  },
  {
    "question": "断然",
    "answer": "だんぜん",
    "meaning": "firmly, absolutely, flatly, resolutely, decisively, definitely, by far, far and away, by a long shot"
  },
  {
    "question": "パン屋",
    "answer": "パンや",
    "meaning": "bakery, baker, pastry shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "豊満",
    "answer": "ほうまん",
    "meaning": "stout, corpulent, plump, voluptuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "糸を引く",
    "answer": "いとをひく",
    "meaning": "to pull (the puppet) strings, to direct things from behind the scenes, to stretch out (and keep goin"
  },
  {
    "question": "財宝",
    "answer": "ざいほう",
    "meaning": "treasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "均衡",
    "answer": "きんこう",
    "meaning": "equilibrium, balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "言わす",
    "answer": "いわす",
    "meaning": "to get someone to say, to make someone say, to let someone say, to let someone speak out, to make a"
  },
  {
    "question": "発注",
    "answer": "はっちゅう",
    "meaning": "ordering (materials), placing an order, order"
  },
  {
    "question": "融通",
    "answer": "ゆうずう,ゆうづう,ゆずう",
    "meaning": "lending (money), finance, loan, adaptability, versatility, flexibility, accommodation"
  },
  {
    "question": "往来",
    "answer": "おうらい",
    "meaning": "coming and going, traffic, road, street, association, socializing, socialising, fellowship, mutual v"
  },
  {
    "question": "民家",
    "answer": "みんか",
    "meaning": "private house"
  },
  {
    "question": "行儀",
    "answer": "ぎょうぎ",
    "meaning": "manners, behavior, behaviour"
  },
  {
    "question": "農業",
    "answer": "のうぎょう",
    "meaning": "agriculture"
  },
  {
    "question": "名案",
    "answer": "めいあん",
    "meaning": "good idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "口論",
    "answer": "こうろん",
    "meaning": "quarrel, argument, row, (verbal) dispute"
  },
  {
    "question": "物腰",
    "answer": "ものごし",
    "meaning": "manner, demeanour, demeanor, bearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "睫毛",
    "answer": "まつげ",
    "meaning": "eyelashes"
  },
  {
    "question": "農家",
    "answer": "のうか",
    "meaning": "farmer, farming family, farmhouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い付く",
    "answer": "おもいつく",
    "meaning": "to think of, to hit upon, to come into one's mind, to be struck with an idea, to remember, to recall"
  },
  {
    "question": "細心",
    "answer": "さいしん",
    "meaning": "meticulous, careful, discreet, scrupulous, prudent"
  },
  {
    "question": "燃え盛る",
    "answer": "もえさかる",
    "meaning": "to blaze, to burn brightly"
  },
  {
    "question": "平坦",
    "answer": "へいたん",
    "meaning": "even, flat, level, smooth, calm, peaceful, uneventful, easy, uncomplicated, trouble-free"
  },
  {
    "question": "勇ましい",
    "answer": "いさましい",
    "meaning": "brave, valiant, gallant, courageous, stirring, vigorous, rousing"
  },
  {
    "question": "壁面",
    "answer": "へきめん",
    "meaning": "surface of a wall"
  },
  {
    "question": "月曜日",
    "answer": "げつようび",
    "meaning": "Monday"
  },
  {
    "question": "山奥",
    "answer": "やまおく",
    "meaning": "deep in the mountains, mountain recesses"
  },
  {
    "question": "助っ人",
    "answer": "すけっと",
    "meaning": "helper, supporter, second, backer, foreign player (hired to strengthen a team)"
  },
  {
    "question": "先っぽ",
    "answer": "さきっぽ",
    "meaning": "tip, end"
  },
  {
    "question": "意義",
    "answer": "いぎ",
    "meaning": "meaning, significance"
  },
  {
    "question": "良",
    "answer": "りょう",
    "meaning": "good (quality, condition, etc.), Good (grade), B"
  },
  {
    "question": "合わす",
    "answer": "あわす",
    "meaning": "to match (rhythm, speed, etc.), to join together, to unite, to combine, to add up, to face, to be op"
  },
  {
    "question": "殊勝",
    "answer": "しゅしょう",
    "meaning": "admirable, laudable"
  },
  {
    "question": "白々しい",
    "answer": "しらじらしい",
    "meaning": "barefaced (e.g. lie), shameless, transparent, pure white, very clear"
  },
  {
    "question": "収容",
    "answer": "しゅうよう",
    "meaning": "accommodation, reception, housing, seating, custody (e.g. awaiting deportation), internment, admissi"
  },
  {
    "question": "後ろ向き",
    "answer": "うしろむき",
    "meaning": "back-facing, backwards, backward-looking, retrogressive, reactionary, retrospective, negative"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆風",
    "answer": "ばくふう",
    "meaning": "bomb blast, blast (from an explosion), shock wave"
  },
  {
    "question": "体裁",
    "answer": "ていさい,たいさい",
    "meaning": "(outward) appearance, (proper) format (e.g. of an essay), form, style, appearances, decency, show, d"
  },
  {
    "question": "密集",
    "answer": "みっしゅう",
    "meaning": "crowding together, clustering together, close formation, swarm"
  },
  {
    "question": "略奪",
    "answer": "りゃくだつ",
    "meaning": "pillage, plunder, looting, robbery"
  },
  {
    "question": "木の実",
    "answer": "このみ,きのみ",
    "meaning": "fruit of a tree, nut, berry"
  },
  {
    "question": "払拭",
    "answer": "ふっしょく,ふっしき",
    "meaning": "wiping out, sweeping away, eradicating, dispelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "険悪",
    "answer": "けんあく",
    "meaning": "dangerous, perilous, threatening, stormy, volatile, tense, critical, serious, stern (expression), ho"
  },
  {
    "question": "知覚",
    "answer": "ちかく",
    "meaning": "perception, sensation, awareness"
  },
  {
    "question": "応対",
    "answer": "おうたい",
    "meaning": "dealing with (people, customers, complaints, etc.), receiving (callers, visitors, etc.), attending t"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾度",
    "answer": "いくど,いくたび",
    "meaning": "(how) many times, (how) often"
  },
  {
    "question": "個別",
    "answer": "こべつ",
    "meaning": "individual, separate, personal, case-by-case"
  },
  {
    "question": "私的",
    "answer": "してき,わたしてき",
    "meaning": "private, personal, my personal (e.g. opinion)"
  },
  {
    "question": "推察",
    "answer": "すいさつ",
    "meaning": "guess, conjecture, surmise"
  },
  {
    "question": "串",
    "answer": "くし",
    "meaning": "spit, skewer, proxy (computer server)"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻勢",
    "answer": "こうせい",
    "meaning": "offensive (movement), aggression"
  },
  {
    "question": "出店",
    "answer": "でみせ,しゅってん",
    "meaning": "food stand, food stall, branch store, setting up a stall or booth (bazaar, festival), opening a bran"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻き添え",
    "answer": "まきぞえ",
    "meaning": "getting mixed up in, getting embroiled in, involvement, entanglement, by-blow"
  },
  {
    "question": "運び出す",
    "answer": "はこびだす",
    "meaning": "to carry out (of somewhere), to transport, to take out"
  },
  {
    "question": "先刻",
    "answer": "せんこく",
    "meaning": "a short while ago, already"
  },
  {
    "question": "三枚",
    "answer": "さんまい",
    "meaning": "three flat objects (sheets of paper, pieces of cloth, etc.), cutting a fish into two boneless fillet"
  },
  {
    "question": "裁縫",
    "answer": "さいほう",
    "meaning": "sewing, needlework"
  },
  {
    "question": "娼婦",
    "answer": "しょうふ",
    "meaning": "prostitute, harlot"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆逐",
    "answer": "くちく",
    "meaning": "extermination, expulsion, destruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "上質",
    "answer": "じょうしつ",
    "meaning": "fine quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "艶",
    "answer": "つや,えん",
    "meaning": "gloss, luster, lustre, shine, sheen, polish, mellowness (of a voice), youthfulness (e.g. of skin), i"
  },
  {
    "question": "小規模",
    "answer": "しょうきぼ",
    "meaning": "small scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "第一歩",
    "answer": "だいいっぽ",
    "meaning": "first step"
  },
  {
    "question": "日焼け",
    "answer": "ひやけ",
    "meaning": "sunburn, suntan, tan, becoming discolored from the sun (e.g. paper), yellowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "大群",
    "answer": "たいぐん",
    "meaning": "large crowd, large herd, large flock, large school, large shoal, swarm"
  },
  {
    "question": "前面",
    "answer": "ぜんめん",
    "meaning": "front part, frontage, facade, initial pledge (e.g. election), opening slogan"
  },
  {
    "question": "動力",
    "answer": "どうりょく",
    "meaning": "power, motive power, dynamic force, three-phase electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "屈む",
    "answer": "かがむ,こごむ,くぐむ",
    "meaning": "to stoop, to lean over, to bend forward, to bend down, to crouch, to squat"
  },
  {
    "question": "発掘",
    "answer": "はっくつ",
    "meaning": "excavation, exhumation, discovery (e.g. new talent)"
  },
  {
    "question": "虐待",
    "answer": "ぎゃくたい",
    "meaning": "abuse, ill-treatment, maltreatment, mistreatment, cruelty"
  },
  {
    "question": "降臨",
    "answer": "こうりん,ごうりん",
    "meaning": "descent (to earth, esp. of a god), advent, epiphany, arrival (of an important person), appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "行く末",
    "answer": "ゆくすえ",
    "meaning": "one's future, one's fate, one's way, one's path"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘美",
    "answer": "かんび",
    "meaning": "sweet (taste), luscious, sweet (melody, dream, etc.), delightful, pleasant, mellow, mellifluous"
  },
  {
    "question": "親しみ",
    "answer": "したしみ",
    "meaning": "intimacy, affection, familiarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "最後尾",
    "answer": "さいこうび",
    "meaning": "end (e.g. of a line), tail end, rear, backmost part"
  },
  {
    "question": "死に方",
    "answer": "しにかた",
    "meaning": "way to die, means of dying, quality of one's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "正装",
    "answer": "せいそう",
    "meaning": "full dress, formal dress, uniform"
  },
  {
    "question": "吟味",
    "answer": "ぎんみ",
    "meaning": "close examination, careful investigation, close inspection, careful selection, inquiry, enquiry, scr"
  },
  {
    "question": "欲情",
    "answer": "よくじょう",
    "meaning": "passion, passions, (sexual) desire, craving"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽率",
    "answer": "けいそつ",
    "meaning": "rash, thoughtless, careless, hasty, imprudent"
  },
  {
    "question": "長期",
    "answer": "ちょうき",
    "meaning": "long-term"
  },
  {
    "question": "好評",
    "answer": "こうひょう",
    "meaning": "favorable reception, good reputation, popularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "着席",
    "answer": "ちゃくせき",
    "meaning": "taking a seat, sitting down (in one's seat)"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊戯",
    "answer": "ゆうぎ",
    "meaning": "game, play, sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "素通り",
    "answer": "すどおり",
    "meaning": "passing through without stopping, passing by"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬師",
    "answer": "やくし,くすし,くすりし",
    "meaning": "Bhaisajyaguru, Pindola, The Healing Buddha, doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "買収",
    "answer": "ばいしゅう",
    "meaning": "acquisition (esp. corporate), buy-out, takeover, purchase, bribery, buying off, corruption"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾重にも",
    "answer": "いくえにも",
    "meaning": "repeatedly, over and over again, several layers deep, layer upon layer, row upon row, (folding) seve"
  },
  {
    "question": "外界",
    "answer": "がいかい",
    "meaning": "outside world, physical world"
  },
  {
    "question": "携わる",
    "answer": "たずさわる",
    "meaning": "to engage in, to participate in, to take part in, to be involved in"
  },
  {
    "question": "生活費",
    "answer": "せいかつひ",
    "meaning": "living expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己満足",
    "answer": "じこまんぞく",
    "meaning": "self-satisfaction, (self-)complacency, smugness"
  },
  {
    "question": "投票",
    "answer": "とうひょう",
    "meaning": "voting, poll"
  },
  {
    "question": "悩ます",
    "answer": "なやます",
    "meaning": "to afflict, to torment, to harass, to molest"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕向ける",
    "answer": "しむける",
    "meaning": "to induce (somebody to do something), to tempt, to act toward (somebody in a certain way), to handle"
  },
  {
    "question": "張り合う",
    "answer": "はりあう",
    "meaning": "to compete (with each other), to contend for, to vie for, to rival"
  },
  {
    "question": "志望",
    "answer": "しぼう",
    "meaning": "wish, desire, ambition"
  },
  {
    "question": "沈み込む",
    "answer": "しずみこむ",
    "meaning": "to sink (into), to get depressed"
  },
  {
    "question": "度々",
    "answer": "たびたび",
    "meaning": "often, again and again, over and over again, repeatedly, frequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "穿く",
    "answer": "はく",
    "meaning": "to put on (lower-body clothing, e.g. pants, skirt, footwear), to wear, to affix (a sword to one's hi"
  },
  {
    "question": "上書き",
    "answer": "うわがき",
    "meaning": "superscription (on a letter, parcel, etc.), address, overwriting (data, file, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鷲",
    "answer": "わし",
    "meaning": "eagle (Accipitridae family)"
  },
  {
    "question": "羨望",
    "answer": "せんぼう",
    "meaning": "envy"
  },
  {
    "question": "正午",
    "answer": "しょうご",
    "meaning": "noon, midday"
  },
  {
    "question": "繫がる",
    "answer": "つながる",
    "meaning": "to be tied together, to be connected to, to be linked to, to lead to, to be related to, to be relate"
  },
  {
    "question": "信憑性",
    "answer": "しんぴょうせい",
    "meaning": "authenticity, credibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "四本",
    "answer": "よんほん",
    "meaning": "four (long cylindrical things)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一大",
    "answer": "いちだい",
    "meaning": "one large ..., a great ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "好感",
    "answer": "こうかん",
    "meaning": "good feeling, good will, favourable impression, favorable impression"
  },
  {
    "question": "臆する",
    "answer": "おくする",
    "meaning": "to be hesitant, to feel timid"
  },
  {
    "question": "領内",
    "answer": "りょうない",
    "meaning": "(within a) territory, domains"
  },
  {
    "question": "転じる",
    "answer": "てんじる",
    "meaning": "to turn, to shift, to alter, to distract"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙虚",
    "answer": "けんきょ",
    "meaning": "modest, humble"
  },
  {
    "question": "一目惚れ",
    "answer": "ひとめぼれ",
    "meaning": "love at first sight, being taken with someone at the first meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "投げ込む",
    "answer": "なげこむ",
    "meaning": "to throw into"
  },
  {
    "question": "一軒",
    "answer": "いっけん",
    "meaning": "one house"
  },
  {
    "question": "就寝",
    "answer": "しゅうしん",
    "meaning": "going to bed, retiring (for the night)"
  },
  {
    "question": "殺し屋",
    "answer": "ころしや",
    "meaning": "professional killer, hit man"
  },
  {
    "question": "野営",
    "answer": "やえい",
    "meaning": "camping, campground, making camp"
  },
  {
    "question": "醜態",
    "answer": "しゅうたい",
    "meaning": "disgraceful behavior, disgraceful behaviour, shameful sight"
  },
  {
    "question": "潤う",
    "answer": "うるおう",
    "meaning": "to be moist, to be damp, to get wet, to be watered, to profit by, to receive benefits, to receive fa"
  },
  {
    "question": "横を向く",
    "answer": "よこをむく",
    "meaning": "to look away, to turn away"
  },
  {
    "question": "妨げる",
    "answer": "さまたげる",
    "meaning": "to disturb, to prevent, to obstruct, to hinder"
  },
  {
    "question": "味覚",
    "answer": "みかく",
    "meaning": "taste, palate, sense of taste"
  },
  {
    "question": "国外",
    "answer": "こくがい",
    "meaning": "outside the country, abroad"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛想笑い",
    "answer": "あいそわらい,あいそうわらい",
    "meaning": "insincere smile, ingratiating smile, polite smile, forced smile"
  },
  {
    "question": "調",
    "answer": "ちょう",
    "meaning": "pitch, tone, key, time, tempo, mood, tendency, style, tax paid in kind (ritsuryo period), first a ta"
  },
  {
    "question": "端的",
    "answer": "たんてき",
    "meaning": "frank, direct, plain, straightforward, point-blank, concise"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺品",
    "answer": "いひん",
    "meaning": "things left (to one) by the deceased, inherited item, estate, memento, keepsake, lost item, lost pro"
  },
  {
    "question": "下僕",
    "answer": "げぼく",
    "meaning": "manservant"
  },
  {
    "question": "蟻",
    "answer": "あり",
    "meaning": "ant"
  },
  {
    "question": "名声",
    "answer": "めいせい",
    "meaning": "fame, reputation, renown"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊迫",
    "answer": "きんぱく",
    "meaning": "tension, strain"
  },
  {
    "question": "凍結",
    "answer": "とうけつ",
    "meaning": "freezing (e.g. water), freezing (prices, wages, assets, etc.), moratorium, suspension (e.g. investme"
  },
  {
    "question": "気候",
    "answer": "きこう",
    "meaning": "climate"
  },
  {
    "question": "雇い主",
    "answer": "やといぬし",
    "meaning": "employer"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰せ",
    "answer": "おおせ",
    "meaning": "order (from one's superior), command, what you say, (someone's) words"
  },
  {
    "question": "意地悪い",
    "answer": "いじわるい",
    "meaning": "ill-natured, mean, nasty, sadistic, cruel, mean-spirited"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶髪",
    "answer": "ちゃぱつ",
    "meaning": "hair dyed brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "締め付け",
    "answer": "しめつけ",
    "meaning": "pressure, clamping, tightening, fastening"
  },
  {
    "question": "得物",
    "answer": "えもの",
    "meaning": "specialized weapon or skill, specialised weapon or skill"
  },
  {
    "question": "出し抜く",
    "answer": "だしぬく",
    "meaning": "to outwit, to outmanoeuvre, to steal a march on, to get the jump on, to anticipate, to forestall"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖堂",
    "answer": "せいどう",
    "meaning": "(Confucian) temple, church, sanctuary"
  },
  {
    "question": "可",
    "answer": "か",
    "meaning": "acceptable, satisfactory, allowed, permitted, approval, being in favour, (a) vote in favour, aye, Pa"
  },
  {
    "question": "入部",
    "answer": "にゅうぶ",
    "meaning": "joining a club"
  },
  {
    "question": "呆気ない",
    "answer": "あっけない",
    "meaning": "unsatisfying, disappointing, abrupt, not enough, too quick, too short, over too soon"
  },
  {
    "question": "七つ",
    "answer": "ななつ",
    "meaning": "seven, seven years of age, four o'clock (old time system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱する",
    "answer": "だっする",
    "meaning": "to escape from, to get out"
  },
  {
    "question": "政略結婚",
    "answer": "せいりゃくけっこん",
    "meaning": "marriage of convenience, marriage for political reasons"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗じる",
    "answer": "じょうじる",
    "meaning": "to take advantage of, to follow blindly, to multiply"
  },
  {
    "question": "達者",
    "answer": "たっしゃ",
    "meaning": "in good health, healthy, well, fit, robust, strong, skilled, proficient, adept, master, expert"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き顔",
    "answer": "なきがお",
    "meaning": "tear-stained face"
  },
  {
    "question": "流星",
    "answer": "りゅうせい",
    "meaning": "meteor, falling star"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱量",
    "answer": "ねつりょう",
    "meaning": "quantity of heat, heat value, calorific value, calories, (degree of) enthusiasm, zeal, passion"
  },
  {
    "question": "突風",
    "answer": "とっぷう",
    "meaning": "gust (of wind), blast"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹲る",
    "answer": "うずくまる,つくばる",
    "meaning": "to crouch, to squat, to cower"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄情",
    "answer": "はくじょう",
    "meaning": "unfeeling, heartless, cold-hearted, cruel"
  },
  {
    "question": "柔和",
    "answer": "にゅうわ",
    "meaning": "gentle, mild, meek, tender"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆除",
    "answer": "くじょ",
    "meaning": "extermination (esp. pests), expulsion, destruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "清らか",
    "answer": "きよらか",
    "meaning": "clean, pure, chaste"
  },
  {
    "question": "望ましい",
    "answer": "のぞましい",
    "meaning": "desirable, hoped for, preferable, advisable"
  },
  {
    "question": "心残り",
    "answer": "こころのこり",
    "meaning": "regret, flesh, blood vessels and fat from around chicken heart (usu. served as yakitori)"
  },
  {
    "question": "最上級",
    "answer": "さいじょうきゅう",
    "meaning": "highest grade, superlative degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "惨劇",
    "answer": "さんげき",
    "meaning": "tragedy, tragic event"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣形",
    "answer": "じんけい",
    "meaning": "battle formation, military formation"
  },
  {
    "question": "無情",
    "answer": "むじょう",
    "meaning": "heartlessness, hardness of heart, coldheartedness, cruelty, insentient, inanimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "女将",
    "answer": "おかみ,じょしょう,にょしょう",
    "meaning": "proprietress (of a traditional Japanese inn or restaurant), landlady, hostess, mistress"
  },
  {
    "question": "目論見",
    "answer": "もくろみ",
    "meaning": "plan, scheme, plot, design, project, intention, aim"
  },
  {
    "question": "麺",
    "answer": "めん",
    "meaning": "noodles, flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "有用",
    "answer": "ゆうよう",
    "meaning": "useful, helpful"
  },
  {
    "question": "下位",
    "answer": "かい",
    "meaning": "low rank, lower position, subordinate position, lower order (e.g. byte)"
  },
  {
    "question": "色濃い",
    "answer": "いろこい",
    "meaning": "marked, pronounced, strongly tending to"
  },
  {
    "question": "幽閉",
    "answer": "ゆうへい",
    "meaning": "confinement, imprisonment, incarceration"
  },
  {
    "question": "易い",
    "answer": "やすい",
    "meaning": "easy, likely to ..., have a tendency to ..., easy to ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "幼児",
    "answer": "ようじ",
    "meaning": "young child, toddler, child over 1 but not yet of school age"
  },
  {
    "question": "憚る",
    "answer": "はばかる",
    "meaning": "to hesitate, to have scruples, to be afraid of what others may think, to lord it over, to have great"
  },
  {
    "question": "変色",
    "answer": "へんしょく",
    "meaning": "change of color, change of colour, fading, discoloration, discolouration"
  },
  {
    "question": "深紅",
    "answer": "しんく,しんこう",
    "meaning": "deep crimson"
  },
  {
    "question": "導入",
    "answer": "どうにゅう",
    "meaning": "introduction, bringing in, leading in, installation"
  },
  {
    "question": "知的",
    "answer": "ちてき",
    "meaning": "intellectual"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷ます",
    "answer": "さます",
    "meaning": "to cool (e.g. from a high temperature to room temperature), to let cool, to dampen, to throw a dampe"
  },
  {
    "question": "凄惨",
    "answer": "せいさん",
    "meaning": "ghastly, gruesome, appalling, lurid"
  },
  {
    "question": "重圧",
    "answer": "じゅうあつ",
    "meaning": "strong pressure, heavy pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "狡猾",
    "answer": "こうかつ",
    "meaning": "sly, cunning, crafty"
  },
  {
    "question": "真夏",
    "answer": "まなつ",
    "meaning": "midsummer"
  },
  {
    "question": "蜂",
    "answer": "はち",
    "meaning": "bee, wasp, hornet"
  },
  {
    "question": "十字",
    "answer": "じゅうじ",
    "meaning": "cross, crossed, cruciform"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛び退く",
    "answer": "とびのく",
    "meaning": "to jump (out of the way), to jump back, to jump aside"
  },
  {
    "question": "丹念",
    "answer": "たんねん",
    "meaning": "painstaking, careful, meticulous, scrupulous, detailed, elaborate"
  },
  {
    "question": "風習",
    "answer": "ふうしゅう",
    "meaning": "custom"
  },
  {
    "question": "手当",
    "answer": "てあて",
    "meaning": "salary, pay, compensation, allowance (e.g. housing allowance), benefit, bonus, medical care, treatme"
  },
  {
    "question": "日向",
    "answer": "ひなた,ひゅうが",
    "meaning": "sunny place, in the sun, Hyūga (former province located in present-day Miyazaki Prefecture), Hyūga ("
  },
  {
    "question": "無償",
    "answer": "むしょう",
    "meaning": "without compensation, without reward, without pay, free (of charge)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬼畜",
    "answer": "きちく",
    "meaning": "brute, savage, fiend"
  },
  {
    "question": "中級",
    "answer": "ちゅうきゅう",
    "meaning": "intermediate level"
  },
  {
    "question": "際限",
    "answer": "さいげん",
    "meaning": "limits, end, bounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "志願",
    "answer": "しがん",
    "meaning": "aspiration, volunteering, desire, application"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻水",
    "answer": "はなみず",
    "meaning": "nasal mucus, dripping nose, snot"
  },
  {
    "question": "闘争",
    "answer": "とうそう",
    "meaning": "fight, battle, combat, conflict, struggle (for rights, higher wages, etc.), strife, (labor) dispute,"
  },
  {
    "question": "生い茂る",
    "answer": "おいしげる",
    "meaning": "to grow thickly, to be overgrown, to thrive, to grow in abundance"
  },
  {
    "question": "亭",
    "answer": "てい,ちん",
    "meaning": "arbor, arbour, bower, pavilion, suffix forming the final part of the pseudonyms of some writers and"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅蓮",
    "answer": "ぐれん",
    "meaning": "bright red, crimson lotus flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "一粒",
    "answer": "ひとつぶ",
    "meaning": "(a) grain, (a) drop, (a) bead"
  },
  {
    "question": "虐殺",
    "answer": "ぎゃくさつ",
    "meaning": "slaughter, massacre"
  },
  {
    "question": "歴",
    "answer": "れき,ふ",
    "meaning": "history of, experience of, to pass, to elapse, to go by, to pass through, to go through, to experien"
  },
  {
    "question": "土台",
    "answer": "どだい",
    "meaning": "foundation, base, basis, from the beginning, from the outset, by nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "呆れ顔",
    "answer": "あきれがお",
    "meaning": "look of amazement, looking dumbfounded"
  },
  {
    "question": "利点",
    "answer": "りてん",
    "meaning": "advantage, point in favor, point in favour"
  },
  {
    "question": "不可",
    "answer": "ふか",
    "meaning": "wrong, bad, improper, unjustifiable, inadvisable, not allowed, not possible, failing grade"
  },
  {
    "question": "創作",
    "answer": "そうさく",
    "meaning": "creation, production, creative work (novel, film, etc.), original work, (creative) writing, fabricat"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴発",
    "answer": "ぼうはつ",
    "meaning": "spontaneous discharge, accidental gun discharge"
  },
  {
    "question": "不死身",
    "answer": "ふじみ",
    "meaning": "invulnerability, immortality, insensibility to pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "悠々",
    "answer": "ゆうゆう",
    "meaning": "quiet, calm, leisurely, distant, far off, boundless, endless, easily, comfortably, without difficult"
  },
  {
    "question": "療養",
    "answer": "りょうよう",
    "meaning": "recuperation, medical treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "石像",
    "answer": "せきぞう",
    "meaning": "stone statue"
  },
  {
    "question": "手慣れる",
    "answer": "てなれる",
    "meaning": "to get used (to), to get familiar with, to get skillful with"
  },
  {
    "question": "安っぽい",
    "answer": "やすっぽい",
    "meaning": "cheap-looking, tawdry, insignificant"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗を流す",
    "answer": "あせをながす",
    "meaning": "to work hard, to sweat, to wash off one's sweat"
  },
  {
    "question": "執り行う",
    "answer": "とりおこなう",
    "meaning": "to hold a ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "命懸け",
    "answer": "いのちがけ",
    "meaning": "putting one's life on the line, staking one's life (on), risking one's life, life and death situatio"
  },
  {
    "question": "車体",
    "answer": "しゃたい",
    "meaning": "body (of car), frame"
  },
  {
    "question": "骸",
    "answer": "から,むくろ",
    "meaning": "shell, husk, hull, pod, chaff, (dead) body, corpse"
  },
  {
    "question": "大根",
    "answer": "だいこん,だいこ,おおね",
    "meaning": "daikon (variety of large white Oriental radish, Raphanus sativus var. longipinnatus), ham actor, roo"
  },
  {
    "question": "候補者",
    "answer": "こうほしゃ",
    "meaning": "candidate, applicant"
  },
  {
    "question": "跡取り",
    "answer": "あととり",
    "meaning": "heir, heiress, inheritor, successor"
  },
  {
    "question": "増援",
    "answer": "ぞうえん",
    "meaning": "reinforcement (e.g. of troops)"
  },
  {
    "question": "契約書",
    "answer": "けいやくしょ",
    "meaning": "(written) contract, agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "麻薬",
    "answer": "まやく",
    "meaning": "narcotic, drug, dope"
  },
  {
    "question": "大阪",
    "answer": "おおさか,おおざか",
    "meaning": "Osaka (city, prefecture), large hill"
  },
  {
    "question": "穢れ",
    "answer": "けがれ",
    "meaning": "uncleanness, impurity, defilement, disgrace, shame, stain, blot, corruption, depravity, uncleanlines"
  },
  {
    "question": "親方",
    "answer": "おやかた,おやがた",
    "meaning": "master, boss, chief, foreman, supervisor, stable master, craftsman, artisan, foster parent"
  },
  {
    "question": "姉貴",
    "answer": "あねき",
    "meaning": "elder sister, older female friend"
  },
  {
    "question": "新規",
    "answer": "しんき",
    "meaning": "new, fresh, new item (e.g. customer, regulation), newly created object, new customer"
  },
  {
    "question": "停滞",
    "answer": "ていたい",
    "meaning": "stagnation, tie-up, standstill, congestion, delay, accumulation, falling into arrears"
  },
  {
    "question": "出し物",
    "answer": "だしもの",
    "meaning": "program (e.g. theatre, theater), programme, (theatrical) piece, number, performance, feature"
  },
  {
    "question": "毎月",
    "answer": "まいつき,まいげつ",
    "meaning": "every month, each month, monthly"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴風",
    "answer": "ぼうふう,あらし",
    "meaning": "storm, windstorm, gale"
  },
  {
    "question": "機械的",
    "answer": "きかいてき",
    "meaning": "mechanical"
  },
  {
    "question": "傷む",
    "answer": "いたむ",
    "meaning": "to hurt, to ache, to feel a pain, to be injured, to be spoiled (e.g. food), to be damaged"
  },
  {
    "question": "形見",
    "answer": "かたみ",
    "meaning": "memento (esp. of a deceased person), keepsake, heirloom, remembrance, souvenir"
  },
  {
    "question": "錆びる",
    "answer": "さびる",
    "meaning": "to rust, to become rusty"
  },
  {
    "question": "選抜",
    "answer": "せんばつ",
    "meaning": "selection, choice, picking out"
  },
  {
    "question": "無骨",
    "answer": "ぶこつ",
    "meaning": "boorish, unrefined, rustic, uncouth, clumsy, brusque"
  },
  {
    "question": "論外",
    "answer": "ろんがい",
    "meaning": "out of the question, outrageous, impossible, irrelevant, not pertinent"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦果",
    "answer": "せんか",
    "meaning": "military gains, war results, fruit of battle"
  },
  {
    "question": "客席",
    "answer": "きゃくせき",
    "meaning": "guest seating (e.g. theater, stadium), passenger seat (e.g. taxi), audience"
  },
  {
    "question": "称える",
    "answer": "たたえる,となえる",
    "meaning": "to extol, to give praise, to assume the name of"
  },
  {
    "question": "気味悪い",
    "answer": "きみわるい,きびわるい",
    "meaning": "unpleasant, uncomfortable, creepy, spooky"
  },
  {
    "question": "動悸",
    "answer": "どうき",
    "meaning": "palpitation (of the heart), pounding, throbbing, thumping"
  },
  {
    "question": "居候",
    "answer": "いそうろう",
    "meaning": "lodger who pays nothing for room and board, freeloader, sponger"
  },
  {
    "question": "津",
    "answer": "つ",
    "meaning": "Tsu (city in Mie), harbour, harbor, port, ferry"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺言",
    "answer": "ゆいごん,いごん,いげん",
    "meaning": "will, testament, last request"
  },
  {
    "question": "変わり者",
    "answer": "かわりもの",
    "meaning": "eccentric, oddball, character, weirdo"
  },
  {
    "question": "佇まい",
    "answer": "たたずまい",
    "meaning": "appearance, shape, form, atmosphere, look, feel"
  },
  {
    "question": "認知",
    "answer": "にんち",
    "meaning": "acknowledgement, acknowledgment, recognition, cognition"
  },
  {
    "question": "根回し",
    "answer": "ねまわし",
    "meaning": "laying the groundwork, behind-the-scenes maneuvering, consensus-building process, digging around the"
  },
  {
    "question": "全般",
    "answer": "ぜんぱん",
    "meaning": "(the) whole, entirety, wholly, as a whole, generally, universally"
  },
  {
    "question": "串刺し",
    "answer": "くしざし",
    "meaning": "skewer, spit, skewering, impalement, running through (e.g. with spear), stabbing"
  },
  {
    "question": "反逆",
    "answer": "はんぎゃく",
    "meaning": "treason, treachery, mutiny, rebellion, insurrection"
  },
  {
    "question": "転換",
    "answer": "てんかん",
    "meaning": "conversion, diversion, changeover, commutation, switchover"
  },
  {
    "question": "御意",
    "answer": "ぎょい",
    "meaning": "your will, your pleasure, your wish, certainly, as you say, you are quite right"
  },
  {
    "question": "物置",
    "answer": "ものおき",
    "meaning": "storage room, storeroom, lumber room"
  },
  {
    "question": "命乞い",
    "answer": "いのちごい",
    "meaning": "begging for one's life, pleading for one's life"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い越す",
    "answer": "おいこす",
    "meaning": "to pass (e.g. car), to overtake, to surpass, to outstrip, to get ahead of, to outdistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "長椅子",
    "answer": "ながいす",
    "meaning": "couch, bench, ottoman"
  },
  {
    "question": "大人数",
    "answer": "おおにんずう,おおにんず",
    "meaning": "large number of people"
  },
  {
    "question": "性分",
    "answer": "しょうぶん",
    "meaning": "nature, disposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "座標",
    "answer": "ざひょう",
    "meaning": "coordinate, coordinates"
  },
  {
    "question": "不規則",
    "answer": "ふきそく",
    "meaning": "irregularity, unsteadiness, disorderly"
  },
  {
    "question": "待たす",
    "answer": "またす",
    "meaning": "to keep (a person) waiting"
  },
  {
    "question": "傑作",
    "answer": "けっさく",
    "meaning": "masterpiece, best work, amusing blunder, funny mistake, boner"
  },
  {
    "question": "何分",
    "answer": "なにぶん,なんぷん",
    "meaning": "some, any, (a) little, of some kind, of some sort, please, anyway, anyhow, at any rate, after all, w"
  },
  {
    "question": "改変",
    "answer": "かいへん",
    "meaning": "change, alteration, modification"
  },
  {
    "question": "瑞々しい",
    "answer": "みずみずしい",
    "meaning": "fresh and youthful, lively, vibrant, vivacious, juicy (e.g. fruit)"
  },
  {
    "question": "人魚",
    "answer": "にんぎょ",
    "meaning": "mermaid, merman"
  },
  {
    "question": "親衛隊",
    "answer": "しんえいたい",
    "meaning": "bodyguards, elite guards, imperial guards, Schutzstaffel, SS, groupies, ardent fans"
  },
  {
    "question": "適用",
    "answer": "てきよう",
    "meaning": "applying (e.g. a technology), adoption"
  },
  {
    "question": "一蹴",
    "answer": "いっしゅう",
    "meaning": "flatly rejecting, curtly refusing, brushing aside, beating easily, defeating handily, a kick"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅はか",
    "answer": "あさはか",
    "meaning": "shallow, superficial, thoughtless, short-sighted, foolish, silly"
  },
  {
    "question": "小銭",
    "answer": "こぜに",
    "meaning": "small change, coins, small sum of money"
  },
  {
    "question": "副作用",
    "answer": "ふくさよう",
    "meaning": "side effect, adverse reaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "路線",
    "answer": "ろせん",
    "meaning": "route (bus, train, air, etc.), line, line (taken by a group, organization, etc.), policy, course"
  },
  {
    "question": "賞金",
    "answer": "しょうきん",
    "meaning": "prize money, monetary award, reward"
  },
  {
    "question": "見本",
    "answer": "みほん",
    "meaning": "sample, specimen, pattern, model, example"
  },
  {
    "question": "二手",
    "answer": "ふたて",
    "meaning": "two groups, two bands"
  },
  {
    "question": "駆け足",
    "answer": "かけあし",
    "meaning": "running fast, double time, cantering, doing things in a hurry"
  },
  {
    "question": "控え室",
    "answer": "ひかえしつ",
    "meaning": "waiting room, anteroom, antechamber, green room"
  },
  {
    "question": "議員",
    "answer": "ぎいん",
    "meaning": "member of an assembly, member of the Diet, member of parliament, member of Congress"
  },
  {
    "question": "水筒",
    "answer": "すいとう",
    "meaning": "canteen, flask, water bottle, thermos"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い寄る",
    "answer": "いいよる",
    "meaning": "to court, to woo, to approach defiantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "核心",
    "answer": "かくしん",
    "meaning": "core, heart (of the matter), point, crux, kernel"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き払う",
    "answer": "やきはらう",
    "meaning": "to burn down (to the ground), to clear away by burning, to reduce to ashes, to burn off"
  },
  {
    "question": "芳しい",
    "answer": "かんばしい,かぐわしい",
    "meaning": "sweet-smelling, fragrant, aromatic, good (reputation, condition, results, etc.), favorable, scentful"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛",
    "answer": "ひよこ,ひよっこ,ひな",
    "meaning": "young bird, chick, fledgling, greenhorn, fledgeling, novice, rookie, hina doll, doll displayed durin"
  },
  {
    "question": "全身全霊",
    "answer": "ぜんしんぜんれい",
    "meaning": "complete devotion, body and soul, one's best"
  },
  {
    "question": "点検",
    "answer": "てんけん",
    "meaning": "inspection, examination, checking"
  },
  {
    "question": "回線",
    "answer": "かいせん",
    "meaning": "circuit, line"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち直す",
    "answer": "もちなおす",
    "meaning": "to recover, to rally, to improve, to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "庇護",
    "answer": "ひご",
    "meaning": "patronage, protection"
  },
  {
    "question": "推奨",
    "answer": "すいしょう",
    "meaning": "recommendation, endorsement"
  },
  {
    "question": "大急ぎ",
    "answer": "おおいそぎ",
    "meaning": "great hurry, great haste, rush"
  },
  {
    "question": "着陸",
    "answer": "ちゃくりく",
    "meaning": "landing, alighting, touch down"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁断",
    "answer": "きんだん",
    "meaning": "prohibition, interdiction, forbidden, prohibited"
  },
  {
    "question": "格別",
    "answer": "かくべつ,かくべち",
    "meaning": "particular, special, exceptional, especial, particularly, especially, exceptionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "麓",
    "answer": "ふもと",
    "meaning": "foot (of a mountain or hill), bottom, base"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽者",
    "answer": "にせもの",
    "meaning": "impostor, imposter, pretender, liar"
  },
  {
    "question": "匂う",
    "answer": "におう",
    "meaning": "to be fragrant, to smell (good), to stink, to smell (bad), to glow, to be bright, to smack of, to sh"
  },
  {
    "question": "判断力",
    "answer": "はんだんりょく",
    "meaning": "judgment, judgement, discernment"
  },
  {
    "question": "厳か",
    "answer": "おごそか",
    "meaning": "solemn (ceremony, atmosphere, etc.), austere, grave, majestic, dignified, stately, impressive"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗末",
    "answer": "そまつ",
    "meaning": "crude, rough, plain, humble, shabby"
  },
  {
    "question": "余波",
    "answer": "よは,なごり,なごろ",
    "meaning": "waves that remain after the wind has subsided, after-effect, aftermath"
  },
  {
    "question": "庭師",
    "answer": "にわし",
    "meaning": "gardener"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳を疑う",
    "answer": "みみをうたがう",
    "meaning": "to not believe one's ears"
  },
  {
    "question": "重心",
    "answer": "じゅうしん",
    "meaning": "centre of gravity (center), centroid, barycenter, (one's) balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "介抱",
    "answer": "かいほう",
    "meaning": "nursing, looking after"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿舎",
    "answer": "しゅくしゃ",
    "meaning": "lodging house"
  },
  {
    "question": "重荷",
    "answer": "おもに,じゅうか",
    "meaning": "load, heavy burden, encumbrance, heavy freight, heavy responsibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙切れ",
    "answer": "かみきれ,かみぎれ",
    "meaning": "piece of paper, slip of paper, strip of paper, scrap of paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "誉める",
    "answer": "ほめる",
    "meaning": "to praise, to commend, to compliment, to speak well of, to speak highly of"
  },
  {
    "question": "残党",
    "answer": "ざんとう",
    "meaning": "remnants, survivors, refugees, pocket (of resistance)"
  },
  {
    "question": "弛緩",
    "answer": "しかん,ちかん",
    "meaning": "relaxation (e.g. of muscles), becoming flaccid"
  },
  {
    "question": "疲れ切る",
    "answer": "つかれきる",
    "meaning": "to be exhausted, to be tired out"
  },
  {
    "question": "平",
    "answer": "ひら,へい,だいら",
    "meaning": "something broad and flat, common, ordinary, plain, rank-and-file, low-ranking employee, freshman, no"
  },
  {
    "question": "大穴",
    "answer": "おおあな",
    "meaning": "large hole, great deficit, heavy losses, big and unexpected winnings, a killing (e.g. on a race), da"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜道",
    "answer": "よみち",
    "meaning": "street at night, making a night journey"
  },
  {
    "question": "応募",
    "answer": "おうぼ",
    "meaning": "application, subscription, entry (competition, raffle, etc.), enlistment"
  },
  {
    "question": "人並み",
    "answer": "ひとなみ",
    "meaning": "ordinary, average, common, normal, like the average person, like most people"
  },
  {
    "question": "短縮",
    "answer": "たんしゅく",
    "meaning": "shortening, contraction, reduction, curtailment, abbreviation"
  },
  {
    "question": "大罪",
    "answer": "だいざい,たいざい",
    "meaning": "serious crime, grave sin"
  },
  {
    "question": "跳ね返す",
    "answer": "はねかえす",
    "meaning": "to reject, to repulse, to repel, to bounce back, to counterattack, to strike back"
  },
  {
    "question": "大砲",
    "answer": "たいほう",
    "meaning": "gun, cannon, artillery"
  },
  {
    "question": "営む",
    "answer": "いとなむ",
    "meaning": "to run (a business), to operate, to conduct, to practice (law, medicine, etc.), to carry out, to per"
  },
  {
    "question": "集",
    "answer": "しゅう",
    "meaning": "collection, compilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "増大",
    "answer": "ぞうだい",
    "meaning": "enlargement, increase"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖人",
    "answer": "せいじん,しょうにん",
    "meaning": "(Christian) saint, wise and virtuous person (esp. in Confucianism), great religious teacher, sage, r"
  },
  {
    "question": "受け身",
    "answer": "うけみ",
    "meaning": "the defensive, passive attitude, passivity, passiveness, the passive, passive voice, ukemi (the art"
  },
  {
    "question": "気弱",
    "answer": "きよわ",
    "meaning": "timid, fainthearted"
  },
  {
    "question": "斜め上",
    "answer": "ななめうえ",
    "meaning": "diagonally upward, (going in a) completely unexpected direction (of a story, result, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "百万",
    "answer": "ひゃくまん",
    "meaning": "1,000,000, one million, million, many"
  },
  {
    "question": "超能力",
    "answer": "ちょうのうりょく",
    "meaning": "extra-sensory perception, ESP, psi, psychic ability, psychokinesis, PK"
  },
  {
    "question": "抑制",
    "answer": "よくせい",
    "meaning": "control, restraint, suppression, constraint, curtailment, inhibition, check, curb"
  },
  {
    "question": "統べる",
    "answer": "すべる",
    "meaning": "to rule over, to govern, to command, to control, to integrate, to consolidate, to unite, to incorpor"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛称",
    "answer": "あいしょう",
    "meaning": "pet name, nickname, name used to indicate affection, intimacy, informality, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "連動",
    "answer": "れんどう",
    "meaning": "operating together, working together, being linked (to), being tied (to), being connected (with), in"
  },
  {
    "question": "屠る",
    "answer": "ほふる,ほぶる,はふる",
    "meaning": "to slaughter, to massacre, to butcher, to defeat soundly, to overpower, to vanquish"
  },
  {
    "question": "真新しい",
    "answer": "まあたらしい",
    "meaning": "brand new"
  },
  {
    "question": "整列",
    "answer": "せいれつ",
    "meaning": "standing in a row, forming a line, alignment"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙一重",
    "answer": "かみひとえ",
    "meaning": "paper-thin (difference)"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛沫",
    "answer": "しぶき,ひまつ",
    "meaning": "splash, spray, droplet"
  },
  {
    "question": "美少年",
    "answer": "びしょうねん",
    "meaning": "handsome youth (male), pretty boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "招集",
    "answer": "しょうしゅう",
    "meaning": "call, summons, convening, convocation"
  },
  {
    "question": "精々",
    "answer": "せいぜい",
    "meaning": "at the most, at best, to the utmost, as much (far) as possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "渇望",
    "answer": "かつぼう",
    "meaning": "craving, longing, thirsting"
  },
  {
    "question": "雌",
    "answer": "めす,めん,め",
    "meaning": "female (animal, plant), female, smaller (of the two), weaker, woman, wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "処遇",
    "answer": "しょぐう",
    "meaning": "treatment (of a person), dealing with"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣地",
    "answer": "じんち",
    "meaning": "encampment, position"
  },
  {
    "question": "火の粉",
    "answer": "ひのこ,ほのこ",
    "meaning": "sparks"
  },
  {
    "question": "復元",
    "answer": "ふくげん",
    "meaning": "restoration (to original state or location), reconstruction, reversion"
  },
  {
    "question": "海軍",
    "answer": "かいぐん",
    "meaning": "navy"
  },
  {
    "question": "人違い",
    "answer": "ひとちがい",
    "meaning": "mistaking one person for another, (case of) mistaken identity"
  },
  {
    "question": "長剣",
    "answer": "ちょうけん,ながだち",
    "meaning": "long sword, minute hand (of a clock), ancient longsword"
  },
  {
    "question": "億劫",
    "answer": "おっくう,おくこう,おっこう",
    "meaning": "troublesome, bothersome, tiresome, annoying"
  },
  {
    "question": "少佐",
    "answer": "しょうさ",
    "meaning": "major, lieutenant commander, wing commander"
  },
  {
    "question": "萎縮",
    "answer": "いしゅく",
    "meaning": "withering, shrivelling, shrinking, atrophy, contraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "文書",
    "answer": "ぶんしょ,もんじょ,ぶんじょ",
    "meaning": "document, writing, letter, papers, notes, records, archives, document addressed to someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "資材",
    "answer": "しざい",
    "meaning": "(raw) material"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠し",
    "answer": "かくし",
    "meaning": "hiding, concealing, being hidden, being concealed, pocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "最良",
    "answer": "さいりょう",
    "meaning": "the best, ideal"
  },
  {
    "question": "学問",
    "answer": "がくもん",
    "meaning": "scholarship, study, learning, discipline, branch of learning, (a) science"
  },
  {
    "question": "窓辺",
    "answer": "まどべ",
    "meaning": "by the window"
  },
  {
    "question": "明け方",
    "answer": "あけがた",
    "meaning": "dawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥方",
    "answer": "おくがた",
    "meaning": "lady, nobleman's wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "半開き",
    "answer": "はんびらき",
    "meaning": "partly open, in half bloom"
  },
  {
    "question": "補習",
    "answer": "ほしゅう",
    "meaning": "supplementary lessons"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸板",
    "answer": "むないた",
    "meaning": "breast, chest"
  },
  {
    "question": "暦",
    "answer": "こよみ,れき",
    "meaning": "calendar, almanac"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱中",
    "answer": "ねっちゅう",
    "meaning": "being enthusiastic about, being wild about, being absorbed in, being engrossed in, being devoted to"
  },
  {
    "question": "艦長",
    "answer": "かんちょう",
    "meaning": "captain (of a warship)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大股",
    "answer": "おおまた",
    "meaning": "spreading one's legs wide apart, straddle, long stride, big steps, thigh-scooping body drop"
  },
  {
    "question": "道筋",
    "answer": "みちすじ",
    "meaning": "path, route, itinerary"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻聴",
    "answer": "げんちょう",
    "meaning": "auditory hallucination"
  },
  {
    "question": "後片付け",
    "answer": "あとかたづけ",
    "meaning": "tidying up, clearing up, cleaning up, clearing away, putting in order"
  },
  {
    "question": "酸味",
    "answer": "さんみ,すみ",
    "meaning": "sourness, acidity"
  },
  {
    "question": "悶絶",
    "answer": "もんぜつ",
    "meaning": "fainting in agony"
  },
  {
    "question": "亜",
    "answer": "あ",
    "meaning": "sub-, -ous (indicating a low oxidation state), -ite, Asia, Argentina, Arabia, America, American pers"
  },
  {
    "question": "醒める",
    "answer": "さめる",
    "meaning": "to wake, to wake up, to become sober, to sober up, to regain consciousness (e.g. after anaesthesia),"
  },
  {
    "question": "建造物",
    "answer": "けんぞうぶつ",
    "meaning": "structure, building"
  },
  {
    "question": "特大",
    "answer": "とくだい",
    "meaning": "extra-large, king-size"
  },
  {
    "question": "顔合わせ",
    "answer": "かおあわせ",
    "meaning": "meeting together, introduction, costarring, appearing together, being matched, facing off"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸騒ぎ",
    "answer": "むなさわぎ",
    "meaning": "uneasiness, vague apprehension, premonition"
  },
  {
    "question": "捲る",
    "answer": "まくる,めくる",
    "meaning": "to turn up, to roll up (e.g. sleeves), to do over and over again, to do relentlessly, to do with rec"
  },
  {
    "question": "作り直す",
    "answer": "つくりなおす",
    "meaning": "to remake, to rebuild"
  },
  {
    "question": "月日",
    "answer": "つきひ,がっぴ",
    "meaning": "time, years, days, (one's) life, the Moon and the Sun, month and day (of the year), (the) date"
  },
  {
    "question": "占う",
    "answer": "うらなう",
    "meaning": "to tell someone's fortune, to forecast, to predict, to divine"
  },
  {
    "question": "余所",
    "answer": "よそ",
    "meaning": "another place, somewhere else, strange parts, outside (one's family or group), someone else, other p"
  },
  {
    "question": "一文字",
    "answer": "いちもんじ,ひともじ",
    "meaning": "straight line, beeline, one (written) character, Welsh onion (Allium fistulosum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "白黒",
    "answer": "しろくろ",
    "meaning": "black and white, monochrome, good and evil, right and wrong, guilt and innocence"
  },
  {
    "question": "最短",
    "answer": "さいたん",
    "meaning": "shortest"
  },
  {
    "question": "条",
    "answer": "すじ,じょう,くだり",
    "meaning": "muscle, tendon, sinew, vein, artery, fiber, fibre, string, line, stripe, streak, reason, logic, plot"
  },
  {
    "question": "隣人",
    "answer": "りんじん",
    "meaning": "neighbour, neighbor, neighbourhood, neighborhood"
  },
  {
    "question": "女房",
    "answer": "にょうぼう,にょうぼ,にゅうぼう",
    "meaning": "wife (esp. one's own wife), court lady, female court attache, woman who served at the imperial palac"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀河",
    "answer": "ぎんが",
    "meaning": "Milky Way, galaxy"
  },
  {
    "question": "一声",
    "answer": "いっせい,ひとこえ",
    "meaning": "voice, cry, shout"
  },
  {
    "question": "司令",
    "answer": "しれい",
    "meaning": "command, control, commander"
  },
  {
    "question": "脈動",
    "answer": "みゃくどう",
    "meaning": "pulsation, pulsatory motion"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉塊",
    "answer": "にくかい,にっかい",
    "meaning": "lump of meat, piece of flesh, human body"
  },
  {
    "question": "台座",
    "answer": "だいざ",
    "meaning": "pedestal"
  },
  {
    "question": "毎週",
    "answer": "まいしゅう",
    "meaning": "every week"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞き込み",
    "answer": "ききこみ",
    "meaning": "getting information (esp. by interviewing witnesses, etc. in a police investigation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲線",
    "answer": "きょくせん",
    "meaning": "curve"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽名",
    "answer": "ぎめい",
    "meaning": "false name, alias, assumed name, pseudonym"
  },
  {
    "question": "墓地",
    "answer": "ぼち,はかち",
    "meaning": "cemetery, graveyard"
  },
  {
    "question": "天秤",
    "answer": "てんびん",
    "meaning": "(balance) scales, shoulder carrying pole, steelyard"
  },
  {
    "question": "記憶喪失",
    "answer": "きおくそうしつ",
    "meaning": "loss of memory, amnesia"
  },
  {
    "question": "陶器",
    "answer": "とうき,すえき",
    "meaning": "porcelain (esp. soft-paste porcelain), china, chinaware, earthenware, pottery, ceramics, crockery, S"
  },
  {
    "question": "深み",
    "answer": "ふかみ",
    "meaning": "depth, deep place"
  },
  {
    "question": "訴え",
    "answer": "うったえ",
    "meaning": "lawsuit, complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "修道院",
    "answer": "しゅうどういん",
    "meaning": "monastery, convent, cloister, abbey"
  },
  {
    "question": "見え隠れ",
    "answer": "みえかくれ,みえがくれ",
    "meaning": "appearing and disappearing, slipping in and out of view"
  },
  {
    "question": "窓枠",
    "answer": "まどわく",
    "meaning": "window frame, sash"
  },
  {
    "question": "事務",
    "answer": "じむ",
    "meaning": "office work, clerical work, administration, business, affairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "優勢",
    "answer": "ゆうせい",
    "meaning": "superiority, superior power, predominance, preponderance"
  },
  {
    "question": "衰弱",
    "answer": "すいじゃく",
    "meaning": "weakness, debility, breakdown, prostration"
  },
  {
    "question": "一通",
    "answer": "いっつう",
    "meaning": "one copy (of a document), one letter, one-way traffic, pure straight, winning hand containing nine c"
  },
  {
    "question": "休まる",
    "answer": "やすまる",
    "meaning": "to be rested, to feel at ease, to repose, to be relieved"
  },
  {
    "question": "張り",
    "answer": "はり,ばり",
    "meaning": "stretch, tension, resilience, springiness, tone, will-power, pluck, pride, in the style of (esp. lit"
  },
  {
    "question": "初々しい",
    "answer": "ういういしい",
    "meaning": "innocent, naive, artless, unsophisticated, pure, fresh"
  },
  {
    "question": "様相",
    "answer": "ようそう",
    "meaning": "aspect, phase, condition, modality (philosophy)"
  },
  {
    "question": "仁王立ち",
    "answer": "におうだち",
    "meaning": "imposing stance, daunting pose"
  },
  {
    "question": "手の内",
    "answer": "てのうち",
    "meaning": "palm (of one's hand), skill, (in one's) grip, (under one's) control, (in one's) pocket, one's (conce"
  },
  {
    "question": "無駄遣い",
    "answer": "むだづかい",
    "meaning": "waste (of money, time, etc.), squandering, frittering away"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い付く",
    "answer": "おいつく",
    "meaning": "to catch up (with), to draw level, to pull even, to reach, to be compensated, to make up for one's l"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛍",
    "answer": "ほたる",
    "meaning": "firefly (Luciola cruciata), lightning bug, glowworm"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち場",
    "answer": "もちば",
    "meaning": "one's post, one's position, one's station, one's place of duty, one's round, one's beat, one's route"
  },
  {
    "question": "異名",
    "answer": "いみょう,いめい",
    "meaning": "another name, nickname, alias, synonym (taxonomy)"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱烈",
    "answer": "ねつれつ",
    "meaning": "ardent, passionate, vehement"
  },
  {
    "question": "女官",
    "answer": "じょかん,にょかん,にょうかん",
    "meaning": "court lady, lady-in-waiting"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽薄",
    "answer": "けいはく",
    "meaning": "frivolous, flippant, superficial, shallow, trifling, insincere"
  },
  {
    "question": "役所",
    "answer": "やくしょ,やくどころ",
    "meaning": "government office, public office, assigned role, duty, position, suitable role, best-suited job"
  },
  {
    "question": "論理",
    "answer": "ろんり",
    "meaning": "logic, logical"
  },
  {
    "question": "見通し",
    "answer": "みとおし",
    "meaning": "unobstructed view, perspective, visibility, vista, forecast, outlook, prospect, prediction, insight,"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦後",
    "answer": "せんご",
    "meaning": "postwar period, period after Second World War"
  },
  {
    "question": "生還",
    "answer": "せいかん",
    "meaning": "returning alive, surviving, reaching the home plate"
  },
  {
    "question": "重症",
    "answer": "じゅうしょう",
    "meaning": "serious illness"
  },
  {
    "question": "論文",
    "answer": "ろんぶん",
    "meaning": "thesis, essay, treatise, paper, article"
  },
  {
    "question": "新婚",
    "answer": "しんこん",
    "meaning": "newly-wed, newly married"
  },
  {
    "question": "繁華街",
    "answer": "はんかがい",
    "meaning": "business district, shopping district, bustling street, shopping centre, shopping center, downtown"
  },
  {
    "question": "使い捨て",
    "answer": "つかいすて,つかいずて",
    "meaning": "throwaway, disposable, single-use"
  },
  {
    "question": "目を疑う",
    "answer": "めをうたがう",
    "meaning": "to doubt one's own eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "大戦",
    "answer": "たいせん",
    "meaning": "great war, great battle"
  },
  {
    "question": "転",
    "answer": "くるり,てん,うたた",
    "meaning": "turning around (once), suddenly, abruptly, completely (wrapped in something), quickly (unwrapping so"
  },
  {
    "question": "崩落",
    "answer": "ほうらく",
    "meaning": "collapse, break, cave-in, crash, (market) decline"
  },
  {
    "question": "支配下",
    "answer": "しはいか",
    "meaning": "under control (e.g. of territory)"
  },
  {
    "question": "武闘",
    "answer": "ぶとう",
    "meaning": "armed struggle"
  },
  {
    "question": "統率",
    "answer": "とうそつ",
    "meaning": "command, lead, generalship, leadership"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉店",
    "answer": "へいてん",
    "meaning": "closing up shop (for the day), stopping business, going out of business"
  },
  {
    "question": "一片",
    "answer": "いっぺん,ひとひら",
    "meaning": "a piece, a scrap, a fragment, a bit, iota, modicum, trace, scrap, the slightest bit (of), (one) leaf"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏み潰す",
    "answer": "ふみつぶす",
    "meaning": "to trample, to crush underfoot"
  },
  {
    "question": "三日月",
    "answer": "みかづき,みかずき",
    "meaning": "new moon, crescent moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱落",
    "answer": "だつらく",
    "meaning": "dropping out, falling behind, falling by the wayside, desertion, omission, being left out, missing p"
  },
  {
    "question": "住処",
    "answer": "すみか,じゅうしょ",
    "meaning": "dwelling, house, residence, den, habitat, address (e.g. of house), domicile"
  },
  {
    "question": "拙",
    "answer": "せつ",
    "meaning": "poor, unskillful, clumsy, I, me"
  },
  {
    "question": "十字架",
    "answer": "じゅうじか",
    "meaning": "cross (for crucifixion), the Cross (of Christ)"
  },
  {
    "question": "即席",
    "answer": "そくせき",
    "meaning": "extempore, impromptu, improvised, ad-lib, off-the-cuff, instant"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧妙",
    "answer": "こうみょう",
    "meaning": "ingenious, skillful, clever, deft"
  },
  {
    "question": "存外",
    "answer": "ぞんがい",
    "meaning": "beyond expectation, contrary to expectations, unexpectedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "長所",
    "answer": "ちょうしょ",
    "meaning": "strong point, merit, virtue, advantage"
  },
  {
    "question": "補強",
    "answer": "ほきょう",
    "meaning": "reinforcement, strengthening"
  },
  {
    "question": "大々的",
    "answer": "だいだいてき",
    "meaning": "great, grand, extensive, large-scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "勉学",
    "answer": "べんがく",
    "meaning": "study, pursuit of knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "輝かしい",
    "answer": "かがやかしい",
    "meaning": "brilliant, glorious, glittering, bright, splendid (e.g. achievement, success), promising (e.g. futur"
  },
  {
    "question": "沖",
    "answer": "おき",
    "meaning": "open sea, Okinawa"
  },
  {
    "question": "善人",
    "answer": "ぜんにん",
    "meaning": "good person, virtuous person"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り返し",
    "answer": "とりかえし",
    "meaning": "recovery, undoing, recall"
  },
  {
    "question": "優美",
    "answer": "ゆうび",
    "meaning": "grace, refinement, elegance, daintiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "違える",
    "answer": "ちがえる,たがえる",
    "meaning": "to change, to alter, to mistake, to make a mistake, to fail to keep (e.g. one's promise), to sprain"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔦",
    "answer": "つた",
    "meaning": "ivy (esp. Boston ivy, Parthenocissus tricuspidata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り調べ",
    "answer": "とりしらべ",
    "meaning": "investigation (e.g. by police or prosecutors), examination, inquiry, enquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "闘志",
    "answer": "とうし",
    "meaning": "fighting spirit, (will to) fight"
  },
  {
    "question": "叔母",
    "answer": "おば,しゅくぼ",
    "meaning": "aunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "確固",
    "answer": "かっこ",
    "meaning": "firm, unshakeable, resolute"
  },
  {
    "question": "石化",
    "answer": "せきか,せっか",
    "meaning": "petrifaction, petrification, mineralization, mineralisation, lithification, fossilization, fossilisa"
  },
  {
    "question": "線路",
    "answer": "せんろ",
    "meaning": "railway track, railway line, railroad, railway, track, line"
  },
  {
    "question": "念願",
    "answer": "ねんがん",
    "meaning": "one's heart's desire, one's dearest wish"
  },
  {
    "question": "炊く",
    "answer": "たく",
    "meaning": "to cook (grains, e.g. rice), to boil, to simmer, to stew, to seethe"
  },
  {
    "question": "描写",
    "answer": "びょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "depiction, description, portrayal"
  },
  {
    "question": "先方",
    "answer": "せんぽう,さきかた,さきがた",
    "meaning": "other party, other side, ahead, in front, destination, a short while ago"
  },
  {
    "question": "有り難い",
    "answer": "ありがたい",
    "meaning": "grateful, thankful, welcome, appreciated, evoking gratitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "怒鳴り声",
    "answer": "どなりごえ",
    "meaning": "angry voice, one's voice when shouting with anger"
  },
  {
    "question": "急用",
    "answer": "きゅうよう",
    "meaning": "urgent business"
  },
  {
    "question": "水槽",
    "answer": "すいそう",
    "meaning": "water tank, cistern, fish tank, aquarium"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜更かし",
    "answer": "よふかし",
    "meaning": "staying up late, keeping late hours, sitting up late at night, nighthawk"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃棄",
    "answer": "はいき",
    "meaning": "disposal, abandonment, scrapping, discarding, abolition, annulment, cancellation, abrogation, repeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "前例",
    "answer": "ぜんれい",
    "meaning": "precedent"
  },
  {
    "question": "無心",
    "answer": "むしん",
    "meaning": "innocence, insentient (i.e. plants, inanimate objects, etc.), free from obstructive thoughts, to pes"
  },
  {
    "question": "囚人",
    "answer": "しゅうじん,めしゅうど,めしうど",
    "meaning": "prisoner"
  },
  {
    "question": "傀儡",
    "answer": "かいらい,くぐつ",
    "meaning": "puppet, marionette, dummy, puppeteer, prostitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄金色",
    "answer": "こがねいろ",
    "meaning": "golden, gold-colored, gold-coloured, honey-colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "小麦粉",
    "answer": "こむぎこ",
    "meaning": "wheat flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "隊列",
    "answer": "たいれつ",
    "meaning": "rank (of troops), file, column, formation"
  },
  {
    "question": "議題",
    "answer": "ぎだい",
    "meaning": "topic of discussion, agenda"
  },
  {
    "question": "筒抜け",
    "answer": "つつぬけ",
    "meaning": "being overheard, being leaked (e.g. secrets), going in one ear and out the other"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗に",
    "answer": "あんに",
    "meaning": "implicitly"
  },
  {
    "question": "小国",
    "answer": "しょうこく",
    "meaning": "small country"
  },
  {
    "question": "岡",
    "answer": "おか",
    "meaning": "hill, height, knoll, rising ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "制約",
    "answer": "せいやく",
    "meaning": "limitation, restriction, condition, constraints"
  },
  {
    "question": "手探り",
    "answer": "てさぐり",
    "meaning": "fumbling, groping"
  },
  {
    "question": "辟易",
    "answer": "へきえき",
    "meaning": "to be fed up (with), to be tired (of), to be bored (with), to be unable to bear, to be stumped, to b"
  },
  {
    "question": "極",
    "answer": "ごく,きょく,はたて",
    "meaning": "quite, very, 10^48, quindecillion, pole, climax, extreme, extremity, culmination, height, zenith, na"
  },
  {
    "question": "出立",
    "answer": "しゅったつ",
    "meaning": "departure"
  },
  {
    "question": "科目",
    "answer": "かもく",
    "meaning": "(school) subject, curriculum, course"
  },
  {
    "question": "献上",
    "answer": "けんじょう",
    "meaning": "presenting to"
  },
  {
    "question": "全軍",
    "answer": "ぜんぐん",
    "meaning": "whole army, whole team, all armies, all teams"
  },
  {
    "question": "助手席",
    "answer": "じょしゅせき",
    "meaning": "passenger seat, assistant driver's seat"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "win, victory, beautiful scenery, scenic spot, counter for wins"
  },
  {
    "question": "毛頭",
    "answer": "もうとう",
    "meaning": "(not) in the least, (not) at all, (not) a bit"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い草",
    "answer": "いいぐさ",
    "meaning": "remarks, comments, way of talking, speaking style, excuse, topic (of conversation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "管",
    "answer": "かん,くだ",
    "meaning": "pipe, tube"
  },
  {
    "question": "基調",
    "answer": "きちょう",
    "meaning": "basic tone, underlying tone, basic theme, basis, keynote, trend"
  },
  {
    "question": "高々",
    "answer": "たかだか",
    "meaning": "very high, high up, aloft, only, merely, just, at most, at best, no more than"
  },
  {
    "question": "奴等",
    "answer": "やつら",
    "meaning": "they, those guys"
  },
  {
    "question": "後遺症",
    "answer": "こういしょう",
    "meaning": "prognostic symptoms, after-effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬愛",
    "answer": "けいあい",
    "meaning": "respect and affection, love and respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹の中",
    "answer": "はらのなか,はらのうち",
    "meaning": "in the belly, in one's heart of hearts"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い悩む",
    "answer": "おもいなやむ",
    "meaning": "to worry about, to be worried about, to fret about, to not know what to do, to be at a loss (as to w"
  },
  {
    "question": "盗み見る",
    "answer": "ぬすみみる",
    "meaning": "to steal a glance, to intercept and read (e.g. other people's email)"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖地",
    "answer": "せいち",
    "meaning": "sacred place, holy ground, the Holy Land, real-life location used as a setting in a novel, film, ani"
  },
  {
    "question": "自販機",
    "answer": "じはんき",
    "meaning": "vending machine"
  },
  {
    "question": "持続",
    "answer": "じぞく",
    "meaning": "continuation, persisting, lasting, sustaining, enduring"
  },
  {
    "question": "児",
    "answer": "こ,じ,やや",
    "meaning": "child, young (animal), young woman, young geisha, offshoot, interest, new shares, player who is not"
  },
  {
    "question": "幸",
    "answer": "さち,こう,さき",
    "meaning": "good luck, fortune, happiness, harvest, yield"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い争い",
    "answer": "いいあらそい",
    "meaning": "a quarrel, argument"
  },
  {
    "question": "長らく",
    "answer": "ながらく",
    "meaning": "long, (for a) long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "管轄",
    "answer": "かんかつ",
    "meaning": "jurisdiction, control"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び込む",
    "answer": "よびこむ",
    "meaning": "to call in, to invite, to bring in"
  },
  {
    "question": "体現",
    "answer": "たいげん",
    "meaning": "personification, impersonation, embodiment"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧弱",
    "answer": "ひんじゃく",
    "meaning": "poor, meagre, meager, feeble, scanty, shabby, insubstantial"
  },
  {
    "question": "空虚",
    "answer": "くうきょ",
    "meaning": "emptiness, hollowness, vacancy, void, inanity, pointlessness, meaninglessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "突っ切る",
    "answer": "つっきる",
    "meaning": "to cross, to go across, to go through, to cut across"
  },
  {
    "question": "再婚",
    "answer": "さいこん",
    "meaning": "second marriage, remarriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "法廷",
    "answer": "ほうてい",
    "meaning": "court (of law), courtroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "隕石",
    "answer": "いんせき",
    "meaning": "meteorite"
  },
  {
    "question": "憤る",
    "answer": "いきどおる,むずかる",
    "meaning": "to be angry, to resent, to be enraged, to be indignant, to fret, to be fretful, to be peevish"
  },
  {
    "question": "人望",
    "answer": "じんぼう",
    "meaning": "popularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "恥じらう",
    "answer": "はじらう",
    "meaning": "to feel shy, to be bashful, to blush"
  },
  {
    "question": "病む",
    "answer": "やむ",
    "meaning": "to fall ill, to suffer from (e.g. a disease), to have something wrong with (e.g. an inner organ)"
  },
  {
    "question": "不躾",
    "answer": "ぶしつけ",
    "meaning": "ill-bred, impolite, rude, impudent, insolent, blunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り",
    "answer": "とり,どり",
    "meaning": "taking, taker, collecting, collector, remover, removal, last performer of the day (usu. the star per"
  },
  {
    "question": "責め",
    "answer": "せめ",
    "meaning": "responsibility, liability, blame, torture, torment, persecution"
  },
  {
    "question": "近付ける",
    "answer": "ちかづける",
    "meaning": "to bring near, to bring close, to let go near, to associate with, to bring (people) together, to let"
  },
  {
    "question": "気を張る",
    "answer": "きをはる",
    "meaning": "to steel oneself to, to brace oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "習性",
    "answer": "しゅうせい",
    "meaning": "habit, behavior, behaviour, trait, nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "上々",
    "answer": "じょうじょう",
    "meaning": "the very best, excellent, superb"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸太",
    "answer": "まるた",
    "meaning": "log"
  },
  {
    "question": "循環",
    "answer": "じゅんかん",
    "meaning": "circulation, rotation, cycle, loop"
  },
  {
    "question": "安泰",
    "answer": "あんたい",
    "meaning": "peace, security, tranquility, tranquillity"
  },
  {
    "question": "天地",
    "answer": "てんち,あめつち",
    "meaning": "heaven and earth, the universe, nature, top and bottom, realm, sphere, world, gods of heaven and ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪人",
    "answer": "かいじん",
    "meaning": "mysterious person"
  },
  {
    "question": "苗字",
    "answer": "みょうじ",
    "meaning": "surname, family name"
  },
  {
    "question": "空振り",
    "answer": "からぶり",
    "meaning": "striking (at something) and missing, swing and a miss, vain attempt"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘え",
    "answer": "あまえ",
    "meaning": "lack of self-reliance, depending on others"
  },
  {
    "question": "脂汗",
    "answer": "あぶらあせ",
    "meaning": "cold sweat, greasy sweat"
  },
  {
    "question": "跡継ぎ",
    "answer": "あとつぎ",
    "meaning": "heir, inheritor, successor"
  },
  {
    "question": "快活",
    "answer": "かいかつ",
    "meaning": "cheerful, lively, lighthearted"
  },
  {
    "question": "総員",
    "answer": "そういん",
    "meaning": "the entire strength, all hands, all the members"
  },
  {
    "question": "通学",
    "answer": "つうがく",
    "meaning": "commuting to school, school commute"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱める",
    "answer": "よわめる",
    "meaning": "to weaken"
  },
  {
    "question": "上の空",
    "answer": "うわのそら",
    "meaning": "inattention, absent-mindedness"
  },
  {
    "question": "母様",
    "answer": "かあさま",
    "meaning": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤算",
    "answer": "ごさん",
    "meaning": "miscalculation"
  },
  {
    "question": "変質",
    "answer": "へんしつ",
    "meaning": "alteration (of character or essence), change in quality, transformation, deterioration, degeneration"
  },
  {
    "question": "屋内",
    "answer": "おくない",
    "meaning": "indoor (court, pool, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏頂面",
    "answer": "ぶっちょうづら",
    "meaning": "sour look, surly face, pout"
  },
  {
    "question": "湧き出る",
    "answer": "わきでる",
    "meaning": "to gush forth"
  },
  {
    "question": "水平",
    "answer": "すいへい",
    "meaning": "horizontal, level, even"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤差",
    "answer": "ごさ",
    "meaning": "measurement error, calculation error"
  },
  {
    "question": "統括",
    "answer": "とうかつ",
    "meaning": "unification, bringing together, generalization, control, supervision"
  },
  {
    "question": "上限",
    "answer": "じょうげん",
    "meaning": "upper limit, supremum"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い思い",
    "answer": "おもいおもい",
    "meaning": "just as (each) one likes, as (each) one pleases, as (each) one prefers, (each) in one's own way"
  },
  {
    "question": "近年",
    "answer": "きんねん",
    "meaning": "recent years"
  },
  {
    "question": "主導",
    "answer": "しゅどう",
    "meaning": "leadership, initiative, spearhead"
  },
  {
    "question": "決勝",
    "answer": "けっしょう",
    "meaning": "decision of a contest, finals (in sports)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹴飛ばす",
    "answer": "けとばす",
    "meaning": "to kick away, to kick off, to kick hard, to refuse curtly, to reject outright"
  },
  {
    "question": "諜報",
    "answer": "ちょうほう",
    "meaning": "secret information, intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "螺旋",
    "answer": "ねじ,らせん",
    "meaning": "screw, key (of a clock, watch, etc.), spring (of a clock, watch, etc.), spiral, helix"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭蓋骨",
    "answer": "ずがいこつ,とうがいこつ",
    "meaning": "skull, cranium"
  },
  {
    "question": "免許",
    "answer": "めんきょ",
    "meaning": "license, permit, licence, certificate"
  },
  {
    "question": "国中",
    "answer": "くにじゅう,こくじゅう,こくちゅう",
    "meaning": "all over the country, everywhere in the country, throughout the nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "大慌て",
    "answer": "おおあわて",
    "meaning": "great haste, mad rush"
  },
  {
    "question": "卒業生",
    "answer": "そつぎょうせい",
    "meaning": "graduate, alumnus"
  },
  {
    "question": "本意",
    "answer": "ほんい,ほい",
    "meaning": "real intention, true motive, true will, original intention, original purpose, original hope"
  },
  {
    "question": "枯渇",
    "answer": "こかつ",
    "meaning": "drying up, running dry, running out, being exhausted, being drained"
  },
  {
    "question": "予め",
    "answer": "あらかじめ",
    "meaning": "beforehand, in advance, previously"
  },
  {
    "question": "極度",
    "answer": "きょくど",
    "meaning": "maximum, extreme, utmost"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き言",
    "answer": "なきごと",
    "meaning": "complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "房",
    "answer": "ふさ,ぼう",
    "meaning": "tuft (of hair, threads, etc.), fringe, tassel, bunch (of grapes, bananas, etc.), cluster (of flowers"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い入れ",
    "answer": "おもいいれ",
    "meaning": "emotional attachment, attitude (expressing emotion), meditative pose (e.g. an actor), posing for eff"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌詞",
    "answer": "かし,うたことば",
    "meaning": "song lyrics, words of a song, libretto, words mainly used in songs or poetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "一部始終",
    "answer": "いちぶしじゅう",
    "meaning": "full particulars, the whole story, from beginning to end"
  },
  {
    "question": "記入",
    "answer": "きにゅう",
    "meaning": "entry (in a form, register, diary, etc.), filling in, filling out"
  },
  {
    "question": "施錠",
    "answer": "せじょう",
    "meaning": "locking"
  },
  {
    "question": "結う",
    "answer": "ゆう,いう",
    "meaning": "to do up (hair), to dress, to arrange, to tie, to bind, to fasten, to make (a fence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "進出",
    "answer": "しんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "advance (into a new market or stage of progress), launching (a new career or venture), expanding (in"
  },
  {
    "question": "酔っ払い",
    "answer": "よっぱらい",
    "meaning": "drunkard"
  },
  {
    "question": "人助け",
    "answer": "ひとだすけ",
    "meaning": "act of mercy, helping another person"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪勢",
    "answer": "ごうせい",
    "meaning": "grand, luxurious, lavish, sumptuous, great, large, big (e.g. storm)"
  },
  {
    "question": "副官",
    "answer": "ふくかん,ふっかん",
    "meaning": "adjutant, aide, aide-de-camp"
  },
  {
    "question": "少量",
    "answer": "しょうりょう",
    "meaning": "small quantity, small amount, narrowmindedness"
  },
  {
    "question": "口癖",
    "answer": "くちぐせ",
    "meaning": "pet saying, favorite phrase (favorite), stock phrase, manner of talking"
  },
  {
    "question": "水道",
    "answer": "すいどう",
    "meaning": "water supply, water service, waterworks, channel, strait, water course, waterway"
  },
  {
    "question": "王道",
    "answer": "おうどう",
    "meaning": "righteous government, just rule, kingship, rule of right, noble path, easy method, simple approach,"
  },
  {
    "question": "共存",
    "answer": "きょうぞん,きょうそん",
    "meaning": "coexistence"
  },
  {
    "question": "全長",
    "answer": "ぜんちょう",
    "meaning": "over-all length, span"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い争う",
    "answer": "いいあらそう",
    "meaning": "to quarrel, to dispute"
  },
  {
    "question": "義",
    "answer": "ぎ",
    "meaning": "morality, righteousness, justice, honour (honor), meaning, teachings, doctrine, nonconsanguineous re"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛙",
    "answer": "かえる,かわず,かいる",
    "meaning": "frog, kajika frog (Buergeria buergeri)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天蓋",
    "answer": "てんがい",
    "meaning": "canopy, dome, priestly minstrel's reed hood, reed hood worn by Komuso priests"
  },
  {
    "question": "校則",
    "answer": "こうそく",
    "meaning": "school regulations"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝間着",
    "answer": "ねまき",
    "meaning": "sleep-wear, nightclothes, pyjamas, pajamas, nightgown, nightdress"
  },
  {
    "question": "手製",
    "answer": "てせい",
    "meaning": "handmade"
  },
  {
    "question": "芸当",
    "answer": "げいとう",
    "meaning": "performance, trick, feat, stunt, extraordinary deed, daring act, bold move"
  },
  {
    "question": "桜色",
    "answer": "さくらいろ",
    "meaning": "cherry blossom (colour, color)"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤の他人",
    "answer": "あかのたにん",
    "meaning": "complete stranger, total stranger"
  },
  {
    "question": "王立",
    "answer": "おうりつ",
    "meaning": "royal"
  },
  {
    "question": "脚本",
    "answer": "きゃくほん",
    "meaning": "script, screenplay, scenario"
  },
  {
    "question": "吊るす",
    "answer": "つるす",
    "meaning": "to hang, to hang up"
  },
  {
    "question": "別室",
    "answer": "べっしつ",
    "meaning": "separate room, another room, special room, concubine (of a noble)"
  },
  {
    "question": "非力",
    "answer": "ひりき",
    "meaning": "powerless, helpless, incompetent"
  },
  {
    "question": "美術館",
    "answer": "びじゅつかん",
    "meaning": "art gallery, art museum"
  },
  {
    "question": "調和",
    "answer": "ちょうわ",
    "meaning": "harmony, accord, reconciliation, agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "三分",
    "answer": "さんぶん,さんぷん",
    "meaning": "to divide into three (parts), to trisect, three minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "流出",
    "answer": "りゅうしゅつ",
    "meaning": "discharge, outward flow, efflux, effluence, haemorrhage, hemorrhage, bleeding (e.g. ink into paper),"
  },
  {
    "question": "売買",
    "answer": "ばいばい,ばいかい",
    "meaning": "trade, buying and selling, trafficking (e.g. of humans, arms, drugs), dealing, crossing (shares)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷え切る",
    "answer": "ひえきる",
    "meaning": "to become completely chilled"
  },
  {
    "question": "山賊",
    "answer": "さんぞく",
    "meaning": "bandit, brigand"
  },
  {
    "question": "末裔",
    "answer": "まつえい,ばつえい",
    "meaning": "descendant"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜け道",
    "answer": "ぬけみち",
    "meaning": "byway, bypath, byroad, secret path, way of escape, loophole, excuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅葉",
    "answer": "こうよう,もみじ",
    "meaning": "autumn colours, fall colors, leaves changing color (colour), leaves turning red, red leaves, layered"
  },
  {
    "question": "饒舌",
    "answer": "じょうぜつ,にょうぜつ",
    "meaning": "talkativeness, garrulity, loquacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "後戻り",
    "answer": "あともどり",
    "meaning": "going backward, turning back, backtracking, doubling back, retrogression, relapse, returning to a ba"
  },
  {
    "question": "格上",
    "answer": "かくうえ",
    "meaning": "higher rank, better position"
  },
  {
    "question": "最上",
    "answer": "さいじょう,もがみ",
    "meaning": "best"
  },
  {
    "question": "忘れ去る",
    "answer": "わすれさる",
    "meaning": "to forget completely, to leave behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛躍",
    "answer": "ひやく",
    "meaning": "leaping, activity, leapfrog (over a problem), making a leap (e.g. in logic), making great strides, m"
  },
  {
    "question": "内密",
    "answer": "ないみつ",
    "meaning": "privacy, secrecy, confidentiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬鹿野郎",
    "answer": "ばかやろう",
    "meaning": "goddamn idiot, moron, nitwit"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼称",
    "answer": "こしょう",
    "meaning": "naming, giving a name, designation, denomination, nominal"
  },
  {
    "question": "気を引く",
    "answer": "きをひく",
    "meaning": "to attract someone's affection, to sound out somebody, to get one's hooks into"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩道",
    "answer": "ほどう",
    "meaning": "footpath, walkway, sidewalk"
  },
  {
    "question": "家名",
    "answer": "かめい",
    "meaning": "family name, house name, family honour, family honor"
  },
  {
    "question": "決め込む",
    "answer": "きめこむ",
    "meaning": "to take for granted, to assume, to pretend (to be), to act as if one were ..., to fancy oneself as b"
  },
  {
    "question": "定期",
    "answer": "ていき",
    "meaning": "fixed period, fixed term, regular, periodic, periodical, fixed-term commuter pass, fixed-term deposi"
  },
  {
    "question": "気品",
    "answer": "きひん",
    "meaning": "elegance, refinement, grace, dignity, aroma"
  },
  {
    "question": "糞",
    "answer": "ばば,くそ,ふん",
    "meaning": "shit, crap, pooh-pooh, poop, something dirty, bullshit, damn, feces, excrement, dung, damned, blaste"
  },
  {
    "question": "備品",
    "answer": "びひん",
    "meaning": "fixtures, furnishings, equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "分け",
    "answer": "わけ",
    "meaning": "sharing, division, draw, tie"
  },
  {
    "question": "小麦",
    "answer": "こむぎ",
    "meaning": "wheat"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼少",
    "answer": "ようしょう",
    "meaning": "infancy, childhood, tender age"
  },
  {
    "question": "境界線",
    "answer": "きょうかいせん",
    "meaning": "boundary line"
  },
  {
    "question": "強欲",
    "answer": "ごうよく",
    "meaning": "greedy, avaricious, rapacious, insatiable"
  },
  {
    "question": "付き添い",
    "answer": "つきそい",
    "meaning": "attendance (on), chaperonage, attendant, escort, entourage, chaperon, retinue"
  },
  {
    "question": "自作",
    "answer": "じさく",
    "meaning": "one's own work, making by oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "同族",
    "answer": "どうぞく",
    "meaning": "same family (race, tribe)"
  },
  {
    "question": "武士",
    "answer": "ぶし,もののふ",
    "meaning": "warrior, samurai"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆恨み",
    "answer": "さかうらみ",
    "meaning": "being resented (by someone one holds resentment towards), thinking ill of a person based on a misund"
  },
  {
    "question": "見繕う",
    "answer": "みつくろう",
    "meaning": "to choose (a thing) at one's own discretion, to use one's discretion in choosing"
  },
  {
    "question": "死闘",
    "answer": "しとう",
    "meaning": "life or death struggle, mortal combat, struggle to the death"
  },
  {
    "question": "手錠",
    "answer": "てじょう",
    "meaning": "handcuffs, manacles"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊厳",
    "answer": "そんげん",
    "meaning": "dignity, majesty, sanctity"
  },
  {
    "question": "投影",
    "answer": "とうえい",
    "meaning": "projection"
  },
  {
    "question": "設計図",
    "answer": "せっけいず",
    "meaning": "plan, blueprint"
  },
  {
    "question": "柳",
    "answer": "やなぎ,りゅう",
    "meaning": "willow (any tree of genus Salix), weeping willow (Salix babylonica), Chinese 'Willow' constellation"
  },
  {
    "question": "断じる",
    "answer": "だんじる",
    "meaning": "to draw the conclusion that ..., to conclude"
  },
  {
    "question": "合コン",
    "answer": "ごうコン",
    "meaning": "joint party (e.g. by students from several colleges), combined party, mixer, two or more groups, esp"
  },
  {
    "question": "本社",
    "answer": "ほんしゃ,ほんじゃ",
    "meaning": "head office, main office, headquarters, parent company, main shrine, this company, this shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "三時",
    "answer": "さんじ",
    "meaning": "3 o'clock, afternoon snack (eaten around 3 o'clock), three ages of Buddhism (following the death of"
  },
  {
    "question": "爽快",
    "answer": "そうかい",
    "meaning": "refreshing, exhilarating, invigorating, bracing"
  },
  {
    "question": "小川",
    "answer": "おがわ",
    "meaning": "stream, brook, creek"
  },
  {
    "question": "全域",
    "answer": "ぜんいき",
    "meaning": "the whole area"
  },
  {
    "question": "強情",
    "answer": "ごうじょう",
    "meaning": "obstinate, stubborn, headstrong"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き渡る",
    "answer": "いきわたる,ゆきわたる",
    "meaning": "to diffuse, to spread throughout, to prevail, to become widespread, to reach everyone"
  },
  {
    "question": "俊敏",
    "answer": "しゅんびん",
    "meaning": "quick-witted and agile, keen and nimble"
  },
  {
    "question": "傷付く",
    "answer": "きずつく",
    "meaning": "to be wounded, to get injured, to get hurt feelings, to get damaged, to get chipped, to get scratche"
  },
  {
    "question": "否む",
    "answer": "いなむ,いやむ",
    "meaning": "to refuse, to decline, to deny, to detest, to dislike"
  },
  {
    "question": "司会",
    "answer": "しかい",
    "meaning": "leading a meeting, presiding over a meeting, officiating at a ceremony, chairmanship, chairman, pres"
  },
  {
    "question": "先決",
    "answer": "せんけつ",
    "meaning": "deciding first, settling (a matter) first, first priority"
  },
  {
    "question": "着々",
    "answer": "ちゃくちゃく",
    "meaning": "steadily"
  },
  {
    "question": "気兼ね",
    "answer": "きがね",
    "meaning": "constraint, reserve, feeling hesitant, being afraid of troubling someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶好調",
    "answer": "ぜっこうちょう",
    "meaning": "in perfect form, going swimmingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "利害",
    "answer": "りがい",
    "meaning": "advantages and disadvantages, interests (of parties)"
  },
  {
    "question": "麻",
    "answer": "あさ,お",
    "meaning": "cannabis (Cannabis sativa), hemp (plant), hemp (fiber), linen, flax, jute"
  },
  {
    "question": "自滅",
    "answer": "じめつ",
    "meaning": "self-destruction, ruining oneself, natural decay, perishing naturally"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑しい",
    "answer": "いやしい",
    "meaning": "lowborn, humble, lowly, vulgar, coarse, crude, mean, base, vile, shabby, greedy, gluttonous, avarici"
  },
  {
    "question": "映画館",
    "answer": "えいがかん",
    "meaning": "movie theatre, movie theater, cinema"
  },
  {
    "question": "男前",
    "answer": "おとこまえ",
    "meaning": "handsome man, man's looks, good looks, manliness"
  },
  {
    "question": "端正",
    "answer": "たんせい",
    "meaning": "handsome, shapely, clean-cut (features), decent, proper, correct, upright, graceful"
  },
  {
    "question": "金曜日",
    "answer": "きんようび",
    "meaning": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "question": "勲章",
    "answer": "くんしょう",
    "meaning": "decoration, order, medal"
  },
  {
    "question": "到来",
    "answer": "とうらい",
    "meaning": "arrival, coming (e.g. something awaited), advent"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾分",
    "answer": "いくぶん",
    "meaning": "somewhat, to some extent, to some degree, some, part, portion"
  },
  {
    "question": "五月",
    "answer": "ごがつ,さつき",
    "meaning": "May, fifth month of the lunar calendar, satsuki azalea (Rhododendron indicum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹筋",
    "answer": "ふっきん,ふくきん,はらすじ",
    "meaning": "sit-up, abdominal muscles, abs"
  },
  {
    "question": "浪費",
    "answer": "ろうひ",
    "meaning": "waste, extravagance"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦難",
    "answer": "くなん",
    "meaning": "suffering, distress, hardship, trial"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗者",
    "answer": "はいしゃ",
    "meaning": "loser, defeated person, the defeated"
  },
  {
    "question": "火球",
    "answer": "かきゅう",
    "meaning": "fireball, bolide"
  },
  {
    "question": "制裁",
    "answer": "せいさい",
    "meaning": "sanctions, punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲がり角",
    "answer": "まがりかど",
    "meaning": "street corner, road turn, bend in the road, turning point, watershed"
  },
  {
    "question": "抽出",
    "answer": "ちゅうしゅつ",
    "meaning": "extraction, abstraction, selection (from a group), sampling"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩兵",
    "answer": "ほへい,ふひょう",
    "meaning": "infantry, infantryman, foot soldier, pawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "負い目",
    "answer": "おいめ",
    "meaning": "(feeling of) indebtedness, feeling obliged"
  },
  {
    "question": "炎上",
    "answer": "えんじょう",
    "meaning": "going up in flames, destruction by fire (esp. of a large building), stirring up a storm of criticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "満載",
    "answer": "まんさい",
    "meaning": "fully loaded, full load, loaded condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "塗れる",
    "answer": "まみれる,まぶれる",
    "meaning": "to be smeared, to be covered"
  },
  {
    "question": "手ぶら",
    "answer": "てぶら",
    "meaning": "empty-handed"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒猫",
    "answer": "くろねこ",
    "meaning": "black cat"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑怯者",
    "answer": "ひきょうもの",
    "meaning": "coward, dastard"
  },
  {
    "question": "味気ない",
    "answer": "あじけない,あじきない",
    "meaning": "wearisome, insipid, dull, irksome, wretched, vain"
  },
  {
    "question": "省略",
    "answer": "しょうりゃく",
    "meaning": "omission, abbreviation, abridgment, abridgement"
  },
  {
    "question": "新米",
    "answer": "しんまい",
    "meaning": "new rice, first rice crop of the year, novice, beginner, newcomer, new hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "不当",
    "answer": "ふとう",
    "meaning": "injustice, impropriety, unreasonableness, undeserved, unfair, invalid"
  },
  {
    "question": "声援",
    "answer": "せいえん",
    "meaning": "(shout of) encouragement, cheering, rooting, support"
  },
  {
    "question": "衛星",
    "answer": "えいせい",
    "meaning": "(natural) satellite, moon, (artificial) satellite"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒸気",
    "answer": "じょうき",
    "meaning": "steam, vapour, vapor, steamboat, steam locomotive"
  },
  {
    "question": "無我夢中",
    "answer": "むがむちゅう",
    "meaning": "being absorbed in, losing oneself in, losing control of oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "送り",
    "answer": "おくり",
    "meaning": "seeing off, sending off, funeral, escapement"
  },
  {
    "question": "性に合う",
    "answer": "しょうにあう",
    "meaning": "to be congenial, to agree with one, to be in one's nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠居",
    "answer": "いんきょ",
    "meaning": "retirement (from work), leading a quiet life (after retirement), retired person, retiree, surrenderi"
  },
  {
    "question": "手軽",
    "answer": "てがる",
    "meaning": "easy, simple, informal, offhand, cheap"
  },
  {
    "question": "逸る",
    "answer": "はぐる,はやる",
    "meaning": "to stray from, to get lost, to be impatient, to be eager, to be restless, to be rash, to be impetuou"
  },
  {
    "question": "牧場",
    "answer": "ぼくじょう,まきば",
    "meaning": "farm (livestock), stock farm, ranch, station, pasture, meadow, grazing land"
  },
  {
    "question": "換える",
    "answer": "かえる",
    "meaning": "to replace, to exchange, to interchange, to substitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠足",
    "answer": "えんそく",
    "meaning": "excursion, outing, trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "昼下がり",
    "answer": "ひるさがり",
    "meaning": "early afternoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "即刻",
    "answer": "そっこく",
    "meaning": "immediately, at once, instantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "傍目",
    "answer": "おかめ,はため",
    "meaning": "looking on from the side, looking on by an outsider, outsider's perspective, as seen by an observer"
  },
  {
    "question": "厳格",
    "answer": "げんかく",
    "meaning": "strict, severe, stern, rigid, rigorous, tough"
  },
  {
    "question": "具現化",
    "answer": "ぐげんか",
    "meaning": "embodiment, realization, materialization"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し置く",
    "answer": "さしおく",
    "meaning": "to leave as is, to let alone, to disregard"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き虫",
    "answer": "なきむし",
    "meaning": "crybaby, blubberer"
  },
  {
    "question": "迫り来る",
    "answer": "せまりくる",
    "meaning": "to be imminent, to loom, to be approaching, to be impending"
  },
  {
    "question": "罰する",
    "answer": "ばっする",
    "meaning": "to punish, to penalize, to penalise"
  },
  {
    "question": "別れ際",
    "answer": "わかれぎわ",
    "meaning": "at parting, on parting"
  },
  {
    "question": "直球",
    "answer": "ちょっきゅう,ちょくきゅう",
    "meaning": "straight ball (pitch), direct (e.g. question), blunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "物珍しい",
    "answer": "ものめずらしい",
    "meaning": "curious, strange, unusual"
  },
  {
    "question": "戯れ",
    "answer": "たわむれ",
    "meaning": "play, sport, fun, caprice, joke, jest, flirtation"
  },
  {
    "question": "容貌",
    "answer": "ようぼう",
    "meaning": "looks, personal appearance, features"
  },
  {
    "question": "商談",
    "answer": "しょうだん",
    "meaning": "business discussion, negotiation"
  },
  {
    "question": "北方",
    "answer": "ほっぽう",
    "meaning": "the north, northward, northern direction, northern part (e.g. of a country), northern district"
  },
  {
    "question": "屋外",
    "answer": "おくがい,やど",
    "meaning": "outdoors, outside, outside near the door to one's home"
  },
  {
    "question": "思い立つ",
    "answer": "おもいたつ",
    "meaning": "to set one's mind on doing, to get the idea of doing, to make up one's mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇声",
    "answer": "きせい",
    "meaning": "strange voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠出",
    "answer": "とおで",
    "meaning": "trip, excursion, outing"
  },
  {
    "question": "両断",
    "answer": "りょうだん",
    "meaning": "bisection"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞こえ",
    "answer": "きこえ",
    "meaning": "being able to hear something (clearly), clearness of a sound, reception (e.g. of a radio station), r"
  },
  {
    "question": "姿形",
    "answer": "すがたかたち",
    "meaning": "appearance, figure, shape, form"
  },
  {
    "question": "晩飯",
    "answer": "ばんめし",
    "meaning": "dinner, evening meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "出陣",
    "answer": "しゅつじん",
    "meaning": "going into battle, departure for the front"
  },
  {
    "question": "一途",
    "answer": "いっと,いちず",
    "meaning": "way, course, the only way, wholehearted, earnest, determined, intent, single-minded, straightforward"
  },
  {
    "question": "任",
    "answer": "にん",
    "meaning": "obligation, duty, charge, responsibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "新手",
    "answer": "あらて,しんて",
    "meaning": "fresh troops, fresh players, newcomer, new employee, new worker, new method, new way, new type"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄生",
    "answer": "きせい",
    "meaning": "parasitism"
  },
  {
    "question": "画策",
    "answer": "かくさく",
    "meaning": "planning, scheming, maneuvering, manoeuvring"
  },
  {
    "question": "太刀打ち",
    "answer": "たちうち",
    "meaning": "crossing swords, competing against, contending with, fighting against"
  },
  {
    "question": "勤しむ",
    "answer": "いそしむ",
    "meaning": "to work hard at, to devote oneself to, to be diligent in"
  },
  {
    "question": "根に持つ",
    "answer": "ねにもつ",
    "meaning": "to hold a grudge, to hold something against somebody"
  },
  {
    "question": "堕落",
    "answer": "だらく",
    "meaning": "depravity, corruption, degradation"
  },
  {
    "question": "緩慢",
    "answer": "かんまん",
    "meaning": "slow, sluggish, dull, lax, sloppy, lenient"
  },
  {
    "question": "人一倍",
    "answer": "ひといちばい",
    "meaning": "(much) more than others, exceedingly, extremely, unusually"
  },
  {
    "question": "政策",
    "answer": "せいさく",
    "meaning": "political measures, policy"
  },
  {
    "question": "本末転倒",
    "answer": "ほんまつてんとう",
    "meaning": "failing to properly evaluate the (relative) importance (of), putting the cart before the horse, mist"
  },
  {
    "question": "百合",
    "answer": "ゆり,ゆる",
    "meaning": "lily (Lilium spp.), yuri, genre of comics and novels about female homosexuality"
  },
  {
    "question": "連呼",
    "answer": "れんこ",
    "meaning": "calling repeatedly (e.g. someone's name), pronouncing successively (usu. repeating a syllable with v"
  },
  {
    "question": "挑発的",
    "answer": "ちょうはつてき",
    "meaning": "provocative, incendiary, inflammatory, suggestive, lascivious, risqué"
  },
  {
    "question": "譲渡",
    "answer": "じょうと",
    "meaning": "transfer, assignment, conveyance"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄格子",
    "answer": "てつごうし",
    "meaning": "iron grill, iron grille, iron lattice, iron bars, prison"
  },
  {
    "question": "停車",
    "answer": "ていしゃ",
    "meaning": "stopping (of a train, car, etc.), stop"
  },
  {
    "question": "中世",
    "answer": "ちゅうせい",
    "meaning": "Middle Ages (in Japan esp. the Kamakura and Muromachi periods), medieval times, mediaeval times"
  },
  {
    "question": "強靭",
    "answer": "きょうじん",
    "meaning": "tough, strong, stiff, tenacious"
  },
  {
    "question": "離宮",
    "answer": "りきゅう",
    "meaning": "imperial villa, royal villa, detached palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "個々",
    "answer": "ここ",
    "meaning": "individual, one by one, separate, each"
  },
  {
    "question": "閲覧",
    "answer": "えつらん",
    "meaning": "inspection, reading, perusal, browsing (the web)"
  },
  {
    "question": "濃度",
    "answer": "のうど",
    "meaning": "concentration, thickness, density, cardinality"
  },
  {
    "question": "比喩",
    "answer": "ひゆ",
    "meaning": "simile, metaphor, allegory, parable"
  },
  {
    "question": "踊らす",
    "answer": "おどらす",
    "meaning": "to manipulate, to let one dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩場",
    "answer": "いわば",
    "meaning": "rocky area, rocky tract, rocky stretch (of a climb), wall (of rock)"
  },
  {
    "question": "珠",
    "answer": "たま",
    "meaning": "ball, sphere, globe, orb, bead (of sweat, dew, etc.), drop, droplet, ball (in sports), pile (of nood"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆笑",
    "answer": "ばくしょう",
    "meaning": "roar of laughter (from multiple people), burst of laughter, uproarious laughter, laughing hard (by a"
  },
  {
    "question": "擬態",
    "answer": "ぎたい",
    "meaning": "mimesis, mimicry, camouflage"
  },
  {
    "question": "東側",
    "answer": "ひがしがわ,とうそく",
    "meaning": "east side, east bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "全土",
    "answer": "ぜんど",
    "meaning": "whole nation, whole land, whole country"
  },
  {
    "question": "相方",
    "answer": "あいかた",
    "meaning": "partner (esp. in manzai), companion, partner for the night (e.g. at a brothel)"
  },
  {
    "question": "富む",
    "answer": "とむ",
    "meaning": "to be rich in, to abound in, to be abundant in, to be full of, to be rich, to be wealthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "摘まむ",
    "answer": "つまむ",
    "meaning": "to pinch, to hold (between one's fingers), to pick up (with chopsticks, tweezers, etc.), to pick up"
  },
  {
    "question": "無自覚",
    "answer": "むじかく",
    "meaning": "unaware, unmindful, unconscious, blind, apathetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "所望",
    "answer": "しょもう",
    "meaning": "desire, request, wish"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴動",
    "answer": "ぼうどう",
    "meaning": "insurrection, rebellion, revolt, riot, uprising"
  },
  {
    "question": "過度",
    "answer": "かど",
    "meaning": "excessive, immoderate"
  },
  {
    "question": "物色",
    "answer": "ぶっしょく",
    "meaning": "looking for a particular person or thing, searching high and low, hunting for, rummaging, scouring ("
  },
  {
    "question": "至福",
    "answer": "しふく",
    "meaning": "beatitude, supreme bliss"
  },
  {
    "question": "墓場",
    "answer": "はかば",
    "meaning": "graveyard, cemetery"
  },
  {
    "question": "通訳",
    "answer": "つうやく",
    "meaning": "interpretation (i.e. oral translation), interpreter"
  },
  {
    "question": "入念",
    "answer": "にゅうねん",
    "meaning": "careful, elaborate, scrupulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗記",
    "answer": "あんき",
    "meaning": "memorization, memorisation, learning by heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "刈る",
    "answer": "かる",
    "meaning": "to cut (grass, hair, etc.), to mow, to clip, to trim, to prune, to shear, to reap, to harvest"
  },
  {
    "question": "選別",
    "answer": "せんべつ",
    "meaning": "selection, classification, sorting, screening, triage"
  },
  {
    "question": "飲ます",
    "answer": "のます",
    "meaning": "to make someone drink, to force someone to drink, to let someone drink, to serve (alcohol), to treat"
  },
  {
    "question": "一頭",
    "answer": "いっとう",
    "meaning": "one large animal (horses, cattle, etc.), head (of cattle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "松明",
    "answer": "たいまつ,しょうめい",
    "meaning": "torch (made of pine, bamboo, reed, etc.), flambeau, torchlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶やす",
    "answer": "たやす",
    "meaning": "to exterminate, to eradicate, to wipe out, to put an end to, to let (fire) go out, to let die (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "優越感",
    "answer": "ゆうえつかん",
    "meaning": "superiority complex, sense of superiority"
  },
  {
    "question": "硬質",
    "answer": "こうしつ",
    "meaning": "hardness, stiffness"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛嬌",
    "answer": "あいきょう,あいぎょう",
    "meaning": "charm, attractiveness, amiability, winsomeness, courtesy, ingratiating behaviour, entertainment, amu"
  },
  {
    "question": "此度",
    "answer": "このたび,こたび",
    "meaning": "this occasion, at this time, now"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り扱う",
    "answer": "とりあつかう",
    "meaning": "to handle, to operate (a machine, etc.), to use, to deal with (an issue), to manage, to treat (someo"
  },
  {
    "question": "詰む",
    "answer": "つむ",
    "meaning": "to become fine (of fabric), to be checkmated, to be hard pressed, to be at a loss, to reach the limi"
  },
  {
    "question": "復習",
    "answer": "ふくしゅう",
    "meaning": "review (of learned material), revision"
  },
  {
    "question": "単調",
    "answer": "たんちょう",
    "meaning": "monotony, monotone, dullness, monotonic"
  },
  {
    "question": "四月",
    "answer": "しがつ,よつき",
    "meaning": "April, fourth month in the lunar calendar, four months"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧血",
    "answer": "ひんけつ",
    "meaning": "anemia, anaemia"
  },
  {
    "question": "豆腐",
    "answer": "とうふ",
    "meaning": "tofu, bean curd, beancurd"
  },
  {
    "question": "家屋",
    "answer": "かおく",
    "meaning": "house, building"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶",
    "answer": "きょう",
    "meaning": "bad luck, bad fortune, evil, wickedness"
  },
  {
    "question": "負け犬",
    "answer": "まけいぬ",
    "meaning": "loser, failure, underdog, unsuccessful person, non-achiever, loser dog, unmarried and childless olde"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅貨",
    "answer": "どうか",
    "meaning": "copper coin"
  },
  {
    "question": "集会",
    "answer": "しゅうかい",
    "meaning": "meeting, assembly, gathering, congregation, convention, rally"
  },
  {
    "question": "摩擦",
    "answer": "まさつ",
    "meaning": "friction, rubbing, chafing, discord, strife, conflict"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄汚い",
    "answer": "うすぎたない",
    "meaning": "filthy, dirty (looking), drab"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕える",
    "answer": "とらえる",
    "meaning": "to catch, to capture, to seize, to arrest, to grab, to catch hold of, to grasp (e.g. meaning), to pe"
  },
  {
    "question": "反らす",
    "answer": "そらす",
    "meaning": "to bend, to warp, to curve"
  },
  {
    "question": "刑務所",
    "answer": "けいむしょ",
    "meaning": "prison, penitentiary"
  },
  {
    "question": "重んじる",
    "answer": "おもんじる",
    "meaning": "to respect, to honor, to honour, to esteem, to prize"
  },
  {
    "question": "本職",
    "answer": "ほんしょく",
    "meaning": "principal occupation, main job, professional, an expert, specialist, I (of a government official, et"
  },
  {
    "question": "凹む",
    "answer": "へこむ,くぼむ",
    "meaning": "to be dented, to be indented, to yield, to give, to sink, to collapse, to cave in, to be beaten, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "闇雲",
    "answer": "やみくも",
    "meaning": "reckless, (at) random, haphazard, blind, sudden, abrupt"
  },
  {
    "question": "産物",
    "answer": "さんぶつ",
    "meaning": "product, produce, result, fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "野放し",
    "answer": "のばなし",
    "meaning": "pasturing, letting (an animal) run loose, letting (someone) do as they please, leaving (something) t"
  },
  {
    "question": "溺愛",
    "answer": "できあい",
    "meaning": "infatuation, adoration, blind love, doting (on a child)"
  },
  {
    "question": "忙しない",
    "answer": "せわしない",
    "meaning": "restless, fidgety, in a hurry"
  },
  {
    "question": "産業",
    "answer": "さんぎょう",
    "meaning": "industry, livelihood, occupation"
  },
  {
    "question": "非道",
    "answer": "ひどう",
    "meaning": "unjust, inhuman"
  },
  {
    "question": "公演",
    "answer": "こうえん",
    "meaning": "public performance, exhibition in a foreign country"
  },
  {
    "question": "憮然",
    "answer": "ぶぜん",
    "meaning": "disappointed, dejected, disheartened, glum, astonished, dumbfounded, indignant, angry"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚み",
    "answer": "あつみ",
    "meaning": "thickness, profundity, depth"
  },
  {
    "question": "愉悦",
    "answer": "ゆえつ",
    "meaning": "joy, pleasure, delight"
  },
  {
    "question": "以て",
    "answer": "もって",
    "meaning": "with, by, by means of, because of, on account of, for, due to, on (a day, date), at (a time), as of"
  },
  {
    "question": "全面",
    "answer": "ぜんめん",
    "meaning": "whole surface, entire"
  },
  {
    "question": "経験者",
    "answer": "けいけんしゃ",
    "meaning": "experienced person, person who has had a particular experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "口付け",
    "answer": "くちづけ",
    "meaning": "kiss"
  },
  {
    "question": "譲歩",
    "answer": "じょうほ",
    "meaning": "concession, conciliation, compromise"
  },
  {
    "question": "生半可",
    "answer": "なまはんか",
    "meaning": "superficial, half-hearted, shallow"
  },
  {
    "question": "助け合う",
    "answer": "たすけあう",
    "meaning": "to help each other, to cooperate"
  },
  {
    "question": "詐欺師",
    "answer": "さぎし",
    "meaning": "swindler, imposter, crook, cheater"
  },
  {
    "question": "主体",
    "answer": "しゅたい,チュチェ",
    "meaning": "main constituent, core, nucleus, subject (philosophical), protagonist, Juche (North Korean political"
  },
  {
    "question": "絵になる",
    "answer": "えになる",
    "meaning": "to make a lovely picture, to be perfect for a picture, picture-perfect, picturesque"
  },
  {
    "question": "寛容",
    "answer": "かんよう",
    "meaning": "tolerance, open-mindedness, forbearance, generosity, magnanimity"
  },
  {
    "question": "通じ合う",
    "answer": "つうじあう",
    "meaning": "to be understood by each other (of thoughts, feelings, etc.), to be comprehended, to exchange with e"
  },
  {
    "question": "含み",
    "answer": "ふくみ",
    "meaning": "implication, hidden meaning, latitude, atmosphere, tone, sentiment, inclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬指",
    "answer": "くすりゆび",
    "meaning": "ring finger, fourth finger"
  },
  {
    "question": "無害",
    "answer": "むがい",
    "meaning": "harmless"
  },
  {
    "question": "一回転",
    "answer": "いちかいてん,いっかいてん",
    "meaning": "one revolution, one rotation"
  },
  {
    "question": "規制",
    "answer": "きせい",
    "meaning": "regulation, (traffic) policing, control, restriction"
  },
  {
    "question": "忌避",
    "answer": "きひ",
    "meaning": "evasion, avoidance, shirking, recusation (of a judge), taking exception (to a judge), challenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "整然",
    "answer": "せいぜん",
    "meaning": "orderly, regular, systematic, well-organized, well-organised, trim, tidy, accurate"
  },
  {
    "question": "兆し",
    "answer": "きざし",
    "meaning": "signs, omen, symptoms"
  },
  {
    "question": "動物園",
    "answer": "どうぶつえん",
    "meaning": "zoo, zoological gardens"
  },
  {
    "question": "点滅",
    "answer": "てんめつ",
    "meaning": "switching on and off (of a light), flashing, blinking, flickering"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝借",
    "answer": "はいしゃく",
    "meaning": "borrowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "普及",
    "answer": "ふきゅう",
    "meaning": "diffusion, spread, popularization, promulgation, familiarization"
  },
  {
    "question": "飼育",
    "answer": "しいく",
    "meaning": "breeding, raising, rearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "優先順位",
    "answer": "ゆうせんじゅんい",
    "meaning": "priority, order of precedence"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗だく",
    "answer": "あせだく",
    "meaning": "dripping with sweat, bathed in perspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り替え",
    "answer": "きりかえ",
    "meaning": "exchange, conversion, replacement, switching (to), switchover"
  },
  {
    "question": "出し入れ",
    "answer": "だしいれ",
    "meaning": "deposit and withdraw, taking in and out"
  },
  {
    "question": "重宝",
    "answer": "ちょうほう,じゅうほう",
    "meaning": "convenient, useful, handy, helpful, finding useful, coming in handy, using often, (priceless) treasu"
  },
  {
    "question": "人脈",
    "answer": "じんみゃく",
    "meaning": "personal connections"
  },
  {
    "question": "癪",
    "answer": "しゃく",
    "meaning": "cause of offense, cause of offence, annoyance, peeve, spasms, convulsions, cramps"
  },
  {
    "question": "削除",
    "answer": "さくじょ",
    "meaning": "deletion, elimination, erasure, striking out"
  },
  {
    "question": "開口一番",
    "answer": "かいこういちばん",
    "meaning": "at the very beginning of one's speech, the first thing (one) says after opening the mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山",
    "answer": "かざん",
    "meaning": "volcano"
  },
  {
    "question": "数度",
    "answer": "すうど",
    "meaning": "several times, several degrees"
  },
  {
    "question": "騒音",
    "answer": "そうおん",
    "meaning": "noise, din"
  },
  {
    "question": "日数",
    "answer": "にっすう,ひかず",
    "meaning": "a number of days"
  },
  {
    "question": "赦す",
    "answer": "ゆるす",
    "meaning": "to permit, to allow, to approve, to consent to, to forgive, to pardon, to excuse, to tolerate, to ex"
  },
  {
    "question": "三つ編み",
    "answer": "みつあみ",
    "meaning": "braid (hair, cord. etc.), plait"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸部",
    "answer": "きょうぶ",
    "meaning": "chest, breast"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑みる",
    "answer": "かんがみる",
    "meaning": "to take into account, to bear in mind, to consider, to learn from, to take warning from"
  },
  {
    "question": "首肯",
    "answer": "しゅこう",
    "meaning": "assent, consent"
  },
  {
    "question": "見当違い",
    "answer": "けんとうちがい",
    "meaning": "wrong (guess or estimate), misdirected, irrelevant, off the point"
  },
  {
    "question": "公務",
    "answer": "こうむ",
    "meaning": "official business, public business"
  },
  {
    "question": "無遠慮",
    "answer": "ぶえんりょ",
    "meaning": "rude, outspoken, presumptuous, cheeky"
  },
  {
    "question": "製品",
    "answer": "せいひん",
    "meaning": "manufactured goods, finished goods, product"
  }
]}